<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<texts>
	<text id="0">Normal</text>
	<text id="1">Athletic</text>
	<text id="2">Aggressive (Manual)</text>
	<text id="3">Discreet</text>
	<text id="4">Aggressive (Auto)</text>
	<text id="5">Fly with the Proto-Pack</text>
	<text id="6">Put away the Proto-Pack</text>
	<text id="7">Volume - Music</text>
	<text id="8">Volume - Sound effects</text>
	<text id="9">Volume - CD</text>
	<text id="10">Volume - Line In</text>
	<text id="11">Volume - Master</text>
	<text id="12">Return to game</text>
	<text id="13">Save parameters</text>
	<text id="14">New game</text>
	<text id="15">Continue saved game</text>
	<text id="16">Quit</text>
	<text id="17">Option menu</text>
	<text id="18">Cancel</text>
	<text id="19">Return to previous menu</text>
	<text id="20">Quit game</text>
	<text id="21">Continue</text>
	<text id="22">Volume settings</text>
	<text id="23">Polygon detail (Full)</text>
	<text id="24">Shadows (All)</text>
	<text id="25">Scenery Zoom On</text>
	<text id="26">Polygon detail (Medium)</text>
	<text id="27">Character shadows</text>
	<text id="28">Scenery Zoom On</text>
	<text id="29">Polygon detail (Low)</text>
	<text id="30">No shadows</text>
	<text id="31">No Scenery Zoom</text>
	<text id="32">Create new player:</text>
	<text id="33">Copy saved game</text>
	<text id="34">Type your name:</text>
	<text id="35">This player already exists! Try again.</text>
	<text id="36">Enter new name</text>
	<text id="37">Delete saved game</text>
	<text id="38">Saved games management</text>
	<text id="39">Advanced Options</text>
	<text id="40">Delete</text>
	<text id="41">Speech files transfer.</text>
	<text id="42">Copying speech files on hard disk, please wait...</text>
	<text id="43">RELENTLESS Twinsen&apos;s Adventure</text>
	<text id="44">Original idea by Frédérick Raynal</text>
	<text id="45">Produced by Adeline Software Int.</text>
	<text id="46">Programming:</text>
	<text id="47">ÿÿÿÿFrédérick Raynal</text>
	<text id="48">ÿÿÿÿLaurent Salmeron</text>
	<text id="49">ÿÿÿÿSerge Plagnol</text>
	<text id="50">ÿÿÿÿFrantz Cournil</text>
	<text id="51">ÿÿÿÿOlivier Lhermite</text>
	<text id="52">3D Objects  Animation:</text>
	<text id="53">ÿÿÿÿDidier Chanfray</text>
	<text id="54">Scenery Graphics:</text>
	<text id="55">ÿÿÿÿYaël Barroz</text>
	<text id="56">ÿÿÿÿJean-Marc Torroella</text>
	<text id="57">Story  Design:</text>
	<text id="58">ÿÿÿÿJean-Jacques Poncet</text>
	<text id="59">Dialogs:</text>
	<text id="60">Story Coding:</text>
	<text id="61">ÿÿÿÿSébastien Viannay</text>
	<text id="62">Video Sequences:</text>
	<text id="63">ÿÿÿÿFrédéric Taquet</text>
	<text id="64">Music:</text>
	<text id="65">ÿÿÿÿPhilippe Vachey</text>
	<text id="66">Testing:</text>
	<text id="67">ÿÿÿÿEmmanuel Oualid</text>
	<text id="68">ÿÿÿÿNicolas Viannay</text>
	<text id="69">ÿÿÿÿAlexis Madinier</text>
	<text id="70">ÿÿÿÿLionel Chaze</text>
	<text id="71">ÿÿÿÿVijay Maharaj</text>
	<text id="72">Quality Control:</text>
	<text id="73">Sound FX:</text>
	<text id="74">ÿÿÿÿLittle Phil V.</text>
	<text id="75">Directed by Frédérick Raynal</text>
	<text id="76">Little Big Adventure</text>
	<text id="77">You&apos;ve just rediscovered your Holomap! You can use it by going through your inventory with the (SHIFT) key or access it directly with the (H) key.</text>
	<text id="78">You&apos;ve just rediscovered your Magic Ball! Try using it on the clones!</text>
	<text id="79">You&apos;ve just stolen Dr. FunFrock&apos;s saber!</text>
	<text id="80">You&apos;ve just found Gawley&apos;s Horn, an object left for you by your ancestors.</text>
	<text id="81">You&apos;ve just earned the first level of Magic by finding the Tunic left for you by your ancestors. You will be able to store up magic with it.</text>
	<text id="82">You&apos;ve just earned the second level of Magic by finding the Book of Bù.</text>
	<text id="83">You&apos;ve just earned the third level of Magic by finding Sendell&apos;s Medallion.</text>
	<text id="84">You&apos;ve just earned the fourth level of Magic by filling up your flask with Clear Water.</text>
	<text id="85">You now have the Red Magnetic Card.</text>
	<text id="86">With this card you are the fourth member of the Elves club. Anyway, its your own business!</text>
	<text id="87">You&apos;ve just rediscovered your ID card.</text>
	<text id="88">You now have the Architect&apos;s pass.</text>
	<text id="89">You now have the Proto-Pack.</text>
	<text id="90">The Kamis have given you a Snowboard.</text>
	<text id="91">You have a Meca-Penguin.</text>
	<text id="92">You&apos;ve just replenished some of your gas supply.</text>
	<text id="93">You&apos;ve just stolen a Pirate&apos;s Flag.</text>
	<text id="94">You&apos;ve just found a Magic Flute.</text>
	<text id="95">The wise man gave you the Space Guitar.</text>
	<text id="96">You&apos;ve just bought a hair dryer.</text>
	<text id="97">You&apos;ve just found the key lost by your ancestor Hégésippe.</text>
	<text id="98">You&apos;ve just found a Bottle of Syrup!</text>
	<text id="99">The bottle is now empty.</text>
	<text id="100">You have a Ferry Ticket.</text>
	<text id="101">You just received a keypad that controls a digital locking system.</text>
	<text id="102">You now possess a coffee pot.</text>
	<text id="103">M. Lanktir gave you his list.</text>
	<text id="104">Holomap (H) key. The Holomap shows your position on the planet. The arrows represent important places that were pointed out to you during your quest. They will disappear once you have completed your task in each of the corresponding places. The Holomap rotates by pressing simultaneously (CTRL) and the arrow keys. By pressing only the arrow keys, you can scroll through text corresponding to the arrows visible on the Holomap.</text>
	<text id="105">Magic Ball (ALT) key. Each time you reach a higher level of magic, the Magic Ball&apos;s striking power will increase. Its trajectories will also become more effective with each new level, as long as you have enough magic in stock! The Ball will use up magic each time it is thrown.</text>
	<text id="106">Magic Saber, once the Saber is in hand (ENTER key), (ALT) key to strike. It is the most powerful weapon on this planet. You can use the Magic Ball again by reselecting it.</text>
	<text id="107">Gawley&apos;s Horn: (ENTER) key. For use on the Seals of Sendell. It will allow you to break them open, which will subsequently allow you to access new places.</text>
	<text id="108">Tunic. With this magical symbol, you have just earned the first level of power.</text>
	<text id="109">Book of Bù (and PROPHECY). (ENTER) key. Used to read the prophecy. @ With this magical symbol, you have just earned the second level of power. You can now also read runes and talk to animals.</text>
	<text id="110">Sendell&apos;s Medallion. With this magical symbol, you have just earned the third level of power.</text>
	<text id="111">Sendell&apos;s Medallion. @ It will allow you to earn the third level of power.</text>
	<text id="112">Flask of Clear Water. With this magical symbol, you have just earned the fourth level of power.</text>
	<text id="113">Flask of Clear Water. @ It will allow you to earn the fourth level of power.</text>
	<text id="114">Red Magnetic Card. It will allow you to open the doors with a red lock.</text>
	<text id="115">The Elves Club Blue Card. This card is coated with star powder and will allow you to open the doors with blue locks.</text>
	<text id="116">Twinsen&apos;s ID card. This card allows you to identify yourself to the authorities. Your smile is especially attractive on the photo!</text>
	<text id="117">M. Mies van der Rooh&apos;s pass. This pass will grant you access to the Teleportation Center. You will still have to use Gawley&apos;s Horn on the left, after the first guard post.</text>
	<text id="118">Proto-Pack. It is controlled with the arrow keys.</text>
	<text id="119">Snowboard. Can only be used in the Himalayi, near the ski lift. Place yourself in between any two flags before using.</text>
	<text id="120">Meca-Penguin. Red clones just hate this stupid toy.</text>
	<text id="121">Gas, extract of molasses. You cannot use vehicles when your gas gauge is at zero.</text>
	<text id="122">Pirate Flag. You can attach it to a boat.</text>
	<text id="123">Magic Flute. The enchanted melodies produced by this instrument can melt frozen Clear Water and make flowers grow in the desert.</text>
	<text id="124">Space Guitar. It was found in the middle of an asteroid that landed in the White Leaf Desert. It brought new harmonics to Twinsun.</text>
	<text id="125">Hair dryer</text>
	<text id="126">Ancestral Key. Opens the secret compartment in Twinsen&apos;s house.</text>
	<text id="127">Bottle of Syrup. This bottle contains 50cl of very concentrated red syrup.</text>
	<text id="128">Empty Bottle</text>
	<text id="129">Ferry Ticket</text>
	<text id="130">Keypad that controls a digital locking system. Once placed on one door inside the Teleportation Center, it allows access to a room filled with Meca-Penguins.</text>
	<text id="131">Coffee Pot. You must return it to one Lanktir who lives next to the bazaar on Proxima island.</text>
	<text id="132">Bonuses List: (ENTER) key to read it.</text>
	<text id="133">Lucky Clover Leaf (ENTER) key: using this clover leaf will use up one of your chances to revitalise yourself to a maximum.</text>
	<text id="134">Empty Space</text>
	<text id="135">Twinsun is a relatively new planet on the outskirts of a remote galaxy. It&apos;s rotational plane has stabilized between two suns. @ There is a huge mountain range running along its equator, that divides the planet in half; each hemisphere is warmed by a single sun. @ The Northern hemisphere, with its orange sky, is warmer than the Southern hemisphere. Except for a polar region, the planet&apos;s climate is clement. The formation of life forms on the planet was thus favorable. Four species developed over the course of the centuries: The Spheros, the Rabbibunnies, the Quetches and the Grobos. They all lived in harmony until a tyrant named Dr. FunFrock reared his ugly head.</text>
	<text id="136">Ever since FunFrock&apos;s rise to power, the population has been living under a reign of terror. FunFrock set up a police state where suspicion is omnipresent. He is all powerful and controls the people with an iron fist. He has at his disposal two high tech weapons that insure his power: cloning and teleportation. @ He can clone any of the species at will, and subsequently recruit these clones into his ranks. He can then deploy these clones instantly through a network of telepods that are dispersed over the entire planet.</text>
	<text id="137">A few years ago, under the guise of protecting the population, Dr. FunFrock herded the planet&apos;s habitants into the southern hemisphere. The repression is harsh. Every day brings more and more arrests, and the people slowly begin to lose hope. @ In an effort to keep their spirits up, the people sometimes evoke an ancient legend along with the name of a goddess, Sendell. The mentioning of the legend or Sendell has since been forbidden by Dr. FunFrock. @ @ Meanwhile... a young quetch named Twinsen has been having strange dreams...</text>
	<text id="138">&quot;The day will come when someone from the present or future species will rise up and say, @ &apos;This world is mine from now on, and the key to all powers belongs to me!&apos; @ This day will surely come because avarice and violence harbor in the hearts of all species of the universe. If the peril on this day is too great, the Chosen One will come forth. He will rise up against the tyrant and overthrow him. He will free and reunite the people, because throughout the years, the Chosen One&apos;s ancestors will have prepared him for his victory. They will have left information and weapons in his dwelling. The Chosen One, also known as the Heir, will, however, have to gather together four magical symbols if he hopes to be victorious: the Tunic, the Book of Bù, Sendell&apos;s Medallion and a Flask of Clear Water. On the day of peril Sendell will visit the Heir in his sleep and announce the coming of the final combat. The Heir will then have to go to the Well of Sendell where the goddess will endow her powers on him! &quot;</text>
	<text id="139">Locations of several clover leaves and boxes: @ There is a box for clover leaves in the sewers of Citadel island, and another in the basement of the tavern; one clover leaf is guarded by a soldier who is located behind sandbags. Another is guarded by a clone in the middle of the ruins on Principal island. Another one is on the roof of the Maritime Museum. Another is guarded by a groboclone to the right of the Teleportation Center&apos;s entrance. Another is guarded by a soldier in front of FunFrock&apos;s fortress.</text>
	<text id="140">&quot; To find Captain LeBorgne&apos;s treasure, the voyager who arrives at the port of Proxima island must use the closest mooring post as a guide. With his back to the docked boats, he must follow these instructions in DISCREET mode: @ 6 steps to the North (straight ahead), then 6 steps to the East (to his right), following the gradual slope. 2 steps to the North (straight ahead) until he reaches the metal garbage can, 3 steps to the East (to his right) until he arrives at a light post. He must stand EXACTLY between the 2 lamp posts, and then take 8 steps to the North until he arrives at a gate. Captain LeBorgne&apos;s treasure is in the building behind the gate.&quot;</text>
	<text id="141">Citadel Island</text>
	<text id="142">Principal Island</text>
	<text id="143">White Leaf Desert</text>
	<text id="144">Proxima Island</text>
	<text id="145">Rebellion Island</text>
	<text id="146">Hamalayi Range</text>
	<text id="147">Tippett Island</text>
	<text id="148">Brundle Island</text>
	<text id="149">Fortress Island</text>
	<text id="150">Polar Island</text>
	<text id="151">Clear Water Lake @ (The Hamalayi mountains)</text>
	<text id="152">Water Tower @ (Principal island)</text>
	<text id="153">Twinsen&apos;s house @ (Citadel island)</text>
	<text id="154">Forger&apos;s Cell @ (Principal island)</text>
	<text id="155">Drug store @ (Citadel island)</text>
	<text id="156">Forger&apos;s house @ (Proxima island)</text>
	<text id="157">Dr FunFrock&apos;s headquarters @ (Principal island)</text>
	<text id="158">Teleportation Center @ (Brundle island)</text>
	<text id="159">Maritime Museum @ (Proxima island)</text>
	<text id="160">Cloning Center  Fortress @ (Fortress island)</text>
	<text id="161">Runic Stone @ (Proxima island)</text>
	<text id="162">Drug store @ (Citadel island)</text>
	<text id="163">Runic Stone</text>
	<text id="164">Mr. Mies Van der Rooh the architect&apos;s house. Bug street @ (Citadel island)</text>
	<text id="165">Well of Sendell @ (Polar island)</text>
	<text id="166">Library @ (Principal Island)</text>
	<text id="167">Port-Belooga @ (Principal Island)</text>
	<text id="168">Proxim-City @ (Proxima Island)</text>
	<text id="169">Mutant Factory @ (The Hamalayi mountains)</text>
	<text id="170">What are you doing here? This sector is off limits to the public.</text>
	<text id="171">Halt!</text>
	<text id="172">Stop squirming, prisoner Twinsen!</text>
	<text id="173">Hey, you! You&apos;re not one of my nurses! Sound the alarm!</text>
	<text id="174">Good day, fellow nurse.</text>
	<text id="175">A prisoner has escaped! @ Sound the alarm!</text>
	<text id="176">&quot;RULE# 1024-GH : @ Dr. FunFrock reminds you that it is absolutely forbidden to make any allusion whatsoever to the so called Legend.&quot;</text>
	<text id="177">&quot;Long live the venerable Dr. FunFrock, the one who saved us from all the superstitions.&quot;</text>
	<text id="178">Hmmmmm... what if I try to get the guard&apos;s attention?</text>
	<text id="179">Good day</text>
	<text id="180">You&apos;ve returned at last, my love! Come inside quickly - all the clones must be looking for you.</text>
	<text id="181">Twinsen, where were you? I was worried sick!</text>
	<text id="182">I&apos;ve just escaped from the asylum. They think that I am a trouble maker because of the strange dreams I have, the ones where Sendell is calling me. I spoke to you about them on several occasions.</text>
	<text id="183">I rummage around here as there&apos;s no one guarding this place. I hide in the truck so that the guards won&apos;t see me. You just have to jump into the pile of garbage and be VERY DISCREET about it.</text>
	<text id="184">Hi! What are you doing there? Did you know that you can read the posters? All you have to do is move in front of one and use the ACTION command while in normal mode.</text>
	<text id="185">Uhhh ... How&apos;s it going?</text>
	<text id="186">I know where they went and I&apos;ll help you if you buy me a drink. Ask the waiter about it.</text>
	<text id="187">You&apos;re being held here because you are a trouble maker. An informant told us that you claim to have prophetic dreams. @ Calm down, we&apos;re going to dissect... uh, I mean... take care of you!</text>
	<text id="188">Ok, I just have to wait for the truck to move into place.</text>
	<text id="189">It is forbidden to travel outside the Citadel in that kind of attire!</text>
	<text id="190">Twinsen! What are you doing here? I heard you were arrested only yesterday!</text>
	<text id="191">They let me out early for good behavior!</text>
	<text id="192">Impossible! Nobody gets out of the Citadel alive!</text>
	<text id="193">&quot;ANNOUNCEMENT #357-G: @ A new automatic surveillance device is now operating in the city. All citizens must remain motionless if one of these devices is in their vicinity.&quot;</text>
	<text id="194">It is forbidden to use that robot !</text>
	<text id="195">You look kind of lost, Mr. Nurse. Use your holomap if you don&apos;t know how to get back home!</text>
	<text id="196">Welcome aboard! You have picked a wonderful day for travelling, the weather is beautiful!</text>
	<text id="197">I think it&apos;s time to make use of what you hid in the house.</text>
	<text id="198">Open up! We know you&apos;re in there!</text>
	<text id="199">You are charged with aiding an escapee. Follow us!</text>
	<text id="200">I&apos;m looking for a young girl. She is being escorted by two groboclones.</text>
	<text id="201">Sound the alarm! It&apos;s the escapee!</text>
	<text id="202">I believe that you can read all the posters. All you have to do is move in front of one and use the ACTION command while in normal mode. I can&apos;t really help you out, because I don&apos;t know how to read!</text>
	<text id="203">I haven&apos;t seen them. @ Sorry!</text>
	<text id="204">I saw them at the port a little while ago. They were leaving for another island. It&apos;s strange, because prisoners usually stay at the Citadel.</text>
	<text id="205">You need a ticket to board the ferry. You can buy one next door.</text>
	<text id="206">Good day, one ticket for... Sound the alarm! It&apos;s the escapee!</text>
	<text id="207">I&apos;ve had it up to my trunk! There are 4 crates in the warehouse that I cannot seem to arrange on the 4 crosses painted on the ground. I would gladly give a ferry ticket to anyone who could help me out of this mess.</text>
	<text id="208">Hey! You over there, come here!</text>
	<text id="209">I can&apos;t open this chest with this blasted trick back of mine! Gimme a hand and I&apos;ll let you keep some of what&apos;s inside. All you have to do is move in front of the chest while in normal mode and use the ACTION command. You can do the same for rummaging through lots of things like cupboards, garbage cans, etc...</text>
	<text id="210">My son and I fixed the ventilation flap in your chimney. We&apos;ll put up a fence later. It&apos;s odd that it is so far away from your house! According to my son, who is an architect, there are a lot of strange things about your house!</text>
	<text id="211">You know, don&apos;t worry about putting up a fence around the chimney. I&apos;ve thought about it and I prefer to keep it as it is.</text>
	<text id="212">Good day.</text>
	<text id="213">Try the tavern, you never know...</text>
	<text id="214">The crates are arranged correctly this time. Thank you, and please accept this ferry ticket as a token of my gratitude.</text>
	<text id="215">I&apos;m on special assignment for the good Dr. FunFrock, and am looking for the plans of the Teleportation Center.</text>
	<text id="216">Come in friend! We will look at them together because they are rather complicated.</text>
	<text id="217">I was put in charge of verifying this building because it was built over ruins that are marked with a strange symbol. It seems that a mad man is attacking different sites also marked with this same symbol. All this extra work has really ruined my weekend! @ We&apos;re really worried about the Teleportation Center: it&apos;s weak point is situated on the left, right after the first guard post.</text>
	<text id="218">You will need my card to get into the center. It is on the drawing table. If you do succeed in catching this vandal with his weird Horn, I would appreciate it if you would kick his rear end for me!</text>
	<text id="219">Go ask my son, he has come home from work. Sorry about your house: the clones came with an attack tank, and they were looking for you!</text>
	<text id="220">I would like to buy a drink for the grobo upstairs.</text>
	<text id="221">Very good sir, but that will cost you 10 Kashes per drink.</text>
	<text id="222">Hide! They have itchy trigger fingers!</text>
	<text id="223">&quot;Keep the planet clean!&quot;</text>
	<text id="224">Let&apos;s see now, where did I put my key?</text>
	<text id="225">Dad! Do you have a key with you?</text>
	<text id="226">All you have to do is ask.</text>
	<text id="227">I&apos;ve got to get into the Teleportation Center.</text>
	<text id="228">You don&apos;t have to be aggressive all the time. I don&apos;t talk to pushy people!</text>
	<text id="229">10 Kashes! That&apos;s too expensive!</text>
	<text id="230">You&apos;ve just got back all the objects that were in your inventory!</text>
	<text id="231">Don&apos;t ever try teleporting yourself - it&apos;s very dangerous! Only the clones can do it.</text>
	<text id="232">&quot;Welcome to Lupin-Burg @ (Citadel Island).&quot;</text>
	<text id="233">Yeah, the clones already confiscated the key to my cellar, so don&apos;t be surprised when they come back to close down the tavern!</text>
	<text id="234">&quot;Welcome to Citadel Island&quot;</text>
	<text id="235">We are going to close this tavern down. Get out of here!</text>
	<text id="236">Good day, this talk about the Legend is strange, don&apos;t you think?</text>
	<text id="237">The 4 crates are not on the 4 crosses, try again!</text>
	<text id="238">I don&apos;t know anything about it, and it is forbidden to talk about it!</text>
	<text id="239">I saw them! They left for another island, but I don&apos;t know which one.</text>
	<text id="240">It is forbidden to talk about it!</text>
	<text id="241">Bah! That doesn&apos;t interest me. Go see at the library or go drown your sorrows at the tavern; or even better, do it the other way around.</text>
	<text id="242">What&apos;s strange is that you&apos;re talking about it. That&apos;s forbidden, you know!</text>
	<text id="243">I don&apos;t know. The books that mention it have been confiscated and sent to Principal Island.</text>
	<text id="244">It is forbidden to talk about that!</text>
	<text id="245">Prisoner Twinsen, I&apos;ve already had enough of seeing you here, so don&apos;t make any more problems for yourself!</text>
	<text id="246">A piece of advice: surrender instead of trying to provoke us.</text>
	<text id="247">You are not going to get away by evoking that subversive propaganda.</text>
	<text id="248">I&apos;m a bartender, you know, so I&apos;ve have had my fill of bar jokes and strange stories!</text>
	<text id="249">I don&apos;t know anything about it, but the tavern will soon be closed down. That&apos;s been confirmed!</text>
	<text id="250">Good day</text>
	<text id="251">Well, I don&apos;t know anything about it. But you could offer me a drink anyway?</text>
	<text id="252">&quot;This room contains information and weapons that were amassed for generations to help the Heir who will, one day, be chosen from our descendants. The key to the room was passed down from generation to generation, but our ancestor Hégésippe was the last family member to retain the key. He was attacked and killed by the ruthless pirate LeBorgne during a sea voyage. Nobody knows where Leborgne&apos;s treasure, which undoubtedly contains the golden key to the room, is today.&quot; </text>
	<text id="253">&quot; You who read this text, know that there are 3 Runic Stones in this world. Their locations are now indicated on your Holomap. They are large menhirs with runic text written on them. They will help the Heir in his quest for Sendell. The third stone will show the exact location of the Well of Sendell. In addition to the help provided by the text, each stone conceals a secret.&quot;</text>
	<text id="254">&quot;Bug street @ (Citadel Island).&quot;</text>
	<text id="255">It&apos;s ok, let&apos;s go!</text>
	<text id="256">You don&apos;t have enough Kashes, come back later!</text>
	<text id="257">Good day</text>
	<text id="258">&quot;Life candy: do you want 10 hearts for 10 Kashes?&quot;</text>
	<text id="259">Ok, I&apos;ll take them.</text>
	<text id="260">No, thank you.</text>
	<text id="261">Not enough Kashes!</text>
	<text id="262">Good day, I would like some information about LeBorgne the pirate.</text>
	<text id="263">&quot;L.B.A. @ Lupin-Burg sewer service @ Little Vachond street&quot;</text>
	<text id="264">&quot;L.B.A. @ Lupin-Burg sewer service @ Dr FunFrock Square&quot;</text>
	<text id="265">Halt!</text>
	<text id="266">Hey, you! You&apos;re not one of my nurses! Sound the alarm!</text>
	<text id="267">Good day, fellow nurse.</text>
	<text id="268">Good day, fellow nurse.</text>
	<text id="269">A prisoner is escaping! @ Sound the alarm!</text>
	<text id="270">A prisoner is escaping! @ Sound the alarm!</text>
	<text id="271">A prisoner is escaping! @ Sound the alarm!</text>
	<text id="272">Good day, neighbor.</text>
	<text id="273">Good day, neighbor.</text>
	<text id="274">Good day</text>
	<text id="275">Good day</text>
	<text id="276">Good day</text>
	<text id="277">Hey buddy!</text>
	<text id="278">Good day</text>
	<text id="279">Good day</text>
	<text id="280">You are being held here because you are a trouble maker.</text>
	<text id="281">Hey, Mr. Nurse! Use your holomap if you&apos;re lost.</text>
	<text id="282">You know, the holomap is activated by the &quot;H&quot; key. And you&apos;d better try to get it back or buy another one at the bazaar on Principal Island.</text>
	<text id="283">I haven&apos;t seen them. @ @ Sorry!</text>
	<text id="284">I&apos;d like to help you, but I haven&apos;t seen them.</text>
	<text id="285">I haven&apos;t seen them. @ @ Sorry!</text>
	<text id="286">Didn&apos;t see &apos;em. I ain&apos;t budged an inch!</text>
	<text id="287">I didn&apos;t see them. Try at the tavern, you never know...</text>
	<text id="288">I haven&apos;t seen anyone, but ask inside the tavern.</text>
	<text id="289">You need a ticket to board the ferry. You can buy one next door.</text>
	<text id="290">Leave me alone, I have nothing to say to you.</text>
	<text id="291">Try the tavern, you never know.</text>
	<text id="292">Try the tavern, that sounds like something they would be familiar with.</text>
	<text id="293">Don&apos;t get all excited, son! I prefer talking calmly.</text>
	<text id="294">Calm down quickly! If you are going to be like that, I won&apos;t speak to you any more.</text>
	<text id="295">Did you know that the telepods are dangerous for all species? Only the clones can use them!</text>
	<text id="296">A piece of advice: surrender instead of provoking us.</text>
	<text id="297">Quiet!</text>
	<text id="298">Thanks, mate!</text>
	<text id="299">I was trying to dig a tunnel, but the noise tipped them off!</text>
	<text id="300">Where do you want to go?</text>
	<text id="301">To Principal Island</text>
	<text id="302">To the White Leaf Desert</text>
	<text id="303">To Proxima Island</text>
	<text id="304">To Rebellion Island</text>
	<text id="305">I&apos;m staying here!</text>
	<text id="306">Bah! That doesn&apos;t interest me.</text>
	<text id="307">Hi!</text>
	<text id="308">Sorry, I haven&apos;t seen her!</text>
	<text id="309">I don&apos;t know what those things are!</text>
	<text id="310">Yes... Hey, stop talking about it, ok? That&apos;s a sure way to wind up in the Citadel.</text>
	<text id="311">I don&apos;t know what that is all about.</text>
	<text id="312">I know that LeBorgne had some kind of a captain&apos;s log written for him (he was practically illiterate), and the boss of the tavern on Principal Island knows where it is!</text>
	<text id="313">They took a fast boat a little while ago. Destination unknown.</text>
	<text id="314">One day, one of my swabs claimed that LeBorgne was an ancestor of mine and... well, you know how dramatic burials at sea can be!</text>
	<text id="315">I can&apos;t help you out, my friend. Don&apos;t know what you&apos;re talking about.</text>
	<text id="316">That&apos;s none of your business!</text>
	<text id="317">Ask the sailor, he would have know who LeBorgne was.</text>
	<text id="318">Not me!</text>
	<text id="319">Bah, you think so? And in the first place, I don&apos;t know it.</text>
	<text id="320">Asks one of my colleagues working in the warehouse on the port. He will know about this LeBorgne.</text>
	<text id="321">There is a library on Principal Island, but I don&apos;t know if they have any books about the Legend there.</text>
	<text id="322">I don&apos;t know anything about that story.</text>
	<text id="323">Sorry, but I don&apos;t know what that could be about.</text>
	<text id="324">Don&apos;t know him!</text>
	<text id="325">I was not informed about this mission!</text>
	<text id="326">Really! Well that&apos;s too bad, but I don&apos;t know anything about it.</text>
	<text id="327">I&apos;ve never seen those plans.</text>
	<text id="328">What legend? I don&apos;t know about any legend!</text>
	<text id="329">Good day</text>
	<text id="330">Ask a sailor that type of question.</text>
	<text id="331">Sorry, I don&apos;t know where they are.</text>
	<text id="332">Bah! That holds little interest for me.</text>
	<text id="333">That&apos;s in the past now, there are no pirates living today.</text>
	<text id="334">Sorry, but I don&apos;t know what that could be about.</text>
	<text id="335">I didn&apos;t see them, but try asking at the tavern.</text>
	<text id="336">Never heard anything about it!</text>
	<text id="337">I&apos;m looking for the plans of the Teleportation Center - I&apos;m on a special assignment!</text>
	<text id="338">I haven&apos;t seen them. @ @ Sorry!</text>
	<text id="339">Sorry neighbor, I don&apos;t know what you&apos;re talking about.</text>
	<text id="340">Try over at the port, all the sailors knew that pirate.</text>
	<text id="341">Good day, I&apos;m looking for a friend. She is escorted by two groboclones.</text>
	<text id="342">I didn&apos;t see her, but if she was arrested, where she is, surely isn&apos;t any of your business!</text>
	<text id="343">I don&apos;t know what you are talking about.</text>
	<text id="344">Can I see your ferry ticket please?</text>
	<text id="345">Ask a sailor, he might be able to help you.</text>
	<text id="346">I don&apos;t know where they are.</text>
	<text id="347">I haven&apos;t seen them.</text>
	<text id="348">If you still want to take the ferry, I can sell you some tickets for only 5 kashes each. I print them up myself.</text>
	<text id="349">You don&apos;t have enough Kashes, come back later.</text>
	<text id="350">No more gas.</text>
	<text id="351">Sorry, but someone came by for the robot. Apparently, they needed it at a top secret construction site.</text>
	<text id="352">Thank you for preventing them from closing down my tavern. If you see something of interest in my cellar, please help yourself.</text>
	<text id="353">Do what I do: gather up the clover leaves and the boxes. You need one box to hold each clover leaf. Each clover leaf will give you another chance when you are in an extremely dangerous situation.</text>
	<text id="354">I read some extracts from the captain&apos;s log - LeBorgne was ruthless! If you&apos;re still interested in the log, it&apos;s for sale at the Old Burg bazaar on Principal Island.</text>
	<text id="355">I don&apos;t know where they are.</text>
	<text id="356">I&apos;m not sure, but I seem to remember before, at the library, there were some books that talked about it.</text>
	<text id="357">Hi </text>
	<text id="358">On the Hamalayi</text>
	<text id="359">I can&apos;t help you, ask someone else.</text>
	<text id="360">Mercy!</text>
	<text id="361">Halt!</text>
	<text id="362">Good day, I&apos;m looking for a friend. She is escorted by two groboclones.</text>
	<text id="363">Sorry, I didn&apos;t see them but try going to the astronomer&apos;s house in the Old Burg; he knows a lot about what is going on.</text>
	<text id="364">It is forbidden to talk about that!</text>
	<text id="365">If you want to see my cousin, go in front of the sink and wash your hands! Ha ha!</text>
	<text id="366">I was arrested for sneezing in public, it&apos;s ridiculous! There&apos;s also, however, a forger in the cell to the right of general headquarters.</text>
	<text id="367">I can&apos;t help you. Except perhaps... considering the risks you&apos;ve taken, I guess I can trust you. I was arrested on this island, but earlier on I gave a fake red card to my brother who was living on Proxima island. He will give it to you if you say &quot;Amos&quot; to him (the location of the house is now indicated on your Holomap).</text>
	<text id="368">&quot;Dr. FUNFROCK&apos;s headquarters. Access IS FORBIDDEN!&quot;</text>
	<text id="369">&quot;Young male quetch seeks young female rabbibunny for friendship (and maybe more...)&quot;</text>
	<text id="370">Bah! Not interested.</text>
	<text id="371">As I live and breathe, you will never see me drink any tap water in this city, mate. And all you have to do is drink some of it to understand why!</text>
	<text id="372">That old pirate is right, the tap water tastes funny. They should be able to improve its quality, and by the way the water tower is located in the North mountains (check your holomap).</text>
	<text id="373">The Legend is a weak spot in FunFrock&apos;s power. You must discover why; it&apos;s the only way of seeing your friend again.</text>
	<text id="374">Good day, this talk about the Legend is strange, don&apos;t you think?</text>
	<text id="375">&quot;ANNOUNCEMENT #358-G : A prisoner named Twinsen has escaped from the Citadel. Anyone seeing the escapee must notify the nearest clone.&quot;</text>
	<text id="376">&quot;Opening hours for the Principal Island library: @ More or less, all the time.&quot;</text>
	<text id="377">We have some documents on the &quot;Legend&quot; somewhere in the Censored Publications Department, but you need special authorization to look at them. Let me see your ID card.</text>
	<text id="378">Good day. You need a boarding ticket to go to Citadel Island.</text>
	<text id="379">&quot; My dear and respected Dr. FunFrock, I took the plans of the Teleportation Center home with me, to work on them over the week-end. I will bring them back on Monday. Signed: Mies Van der Rooh, Architect, Bug Street, Citadel Island. &quot;</text>
	<text id="380">I&apos;m interested in the story of LeBorgne the pirate.</text>
	<text id="381">I&apos;m looking for the plans of the Teleportation Center. I&apos;m on a special assignment!</text>
	<text id="382">Sound the alarm! It&apos;s the escapee!</text>
	<text id="383">Good day</text>
	<text id="384">A ferry ticket costs 10 kashes. However as I have a WANTED poster in my office, you will have to pay 30 Kashes to make me overlook the fact that you look a lot like the guy on it.</text>
	<text id="385">Halt! You are a wanted escapee!</text>
	<text id="386">If you give me 10 Kashes I&apos;ll let you read the poster behind me.</text>
	<text id="387">I saw them a little while ago on Citadel Island. But they left on a fast boat. Destination unknown!</text>
	<text id="388">Welcome, dear customer! I don&apos;t have any more cherry flavored syrup, but there is a pharmacy open on Citadel Island. @ P Move in front of the item that interests you and use the ACTION command.</text>
	<text id="389">Mister, Mister! There&apos;s a loose stone in the back wall. I might be able to escape!</text>
	<text id="390">A loose stone? Let me see that.</text>
	<text id="391">The passage will only open when you come from my cousin&apos;s house. Now stop rummaging everywhere!</text>
	<text id="392">Sorry, but you don&apos;t have enough Kashes. Come back later.</text>
	<text id="393">Here you can&apos;t just talk to just anybody. Prove that you are not working for FunFrock. Go clobber a clone for starters!</text>
	<text id="394">Didn&apos;t see anything, but if you have any problems, you should talk to the Astronomer who is under house arrest, up above the Old Burg.</text>
	<text id="395">So you&apos;re the one that beats up on clones? Good job! I haven&apos;t seen your friend but you should go see the Astronomer. He will certainly be able to help you.</text>
	<text id="396">Leave me alone, this job is already hard enough.</text>
	<text id="397">This young girl must be someone important if that tyrant FunFrock is holding her outside of Citadel Island. Something funny is going on with this forbidding of any talk about the Legend: this must be some kind of weakness in his power! Find out what is behind this Legend, it&apos;s your only hope of seeing your friend again. If you need to leave the island, I know a friend who can help you at Port-Belooga (check your holomap). Tell him that I sent you. And be discreet in your quest.</text>
	<text id="398">Unfortunately, I don&apos;t know anything about the Legend, but I have a fisherman friend who could help you in your travels if you tell him that I sent you. He lives at Port-Belooga (check your holomap).</text>
	<text id="399">Ha ha! It&apos;s a colleague, he&apos;s looking for a wife.</text>
	<text id="400">I don&apos;t know anything about it, and anyway, it&apos;s a forbidden subject.</text>
	<text id="401">According to my doctor, I can drink only the city&apos;s tap water. But it tastes too bad. If someone could improve its taste, I would be willing to show him the Censored Publication Department, and that would be quite a privilege.</text>
	<text id="402">Hold on a minute, I&apos;m going to taste the water.</text>
	<text id="403">Hmmmmm, cherry flavor, not bad... but I would have preferred carrot. But anyway, as promised, I will show you where the documents about the &quot;Legend&quot; are.</text>
	<text id="404">Never saw &apos;em! The sea is my only concern. @ Sometimes I even take voyagers on my boat, but only people that I can trust.</text>
	<text id="405">If the Astronomer sent you, I guess I can trust you. Despite the solidarity in the resistance against FunFrock, you know, times are hard. For 10 Kashes I&apos;ll take you where you want to go.</text>
	<text id="406">I don&apos;t know yet.</text>
	<text id="407">To the White Leaf Desert.</text>
	<text id="408">I&apos;m not going to leave just yet.</text>
	<text id="409">You don&apos;t have enough Kashes to make the trip Twinsen. See you later!</text>
	<text id="410">&quot;In the distant past, when the spheros, rabbibunnies, Quetches and grobos emerged from the original primordial soup, centuries before Dr. FunFrock&apos;s coup, a prophecy was pronounced. Its text is hardly remembered today and that is why people now refer to it as the &quot;Legend&quot;. It explained how &quot;the Heir,&quot; when his time had come, would be called to overthrow a tyrant! The secret of the Legend can still be learned somewhere in the White Leaf Desert.&quot;</text>
	<text id="411">You&apos;ve just got back all the objects that were in your inventory!</text>
	<text id="412">You can come aboard sir, we were just getting underway.</text>
	<text id="413">&quot;Welcome to Principal Island.&quot;</text>
	<text id="414">I didn&apos;t see her, but I think that I can trust you now. Follow me, I know how to get to the Astronomer&apos;s home.</text>
	<text id="415">My cousin is a locksmith. He will open the unguarded door for you. Follow me!</text>
	<text id="416">I don&apos;t know if I can help you. I am a locksmith and I can open doors... but only for people that I can trust!</text>
	<text id="417">If you already know about that passage, I can open the unguarded door for you. After you!</text>
	<text id="418">I can help you get rid of the Supergro. Follow me, but wait until he moves away from the steps before going by!</text>
	<text id="419">Thief! @ Leave my money box alone!</text>
	<text id="420">You are too aggressive! Get out of here, and don&apos;t come back until you have calmed down!</text>
	<text id="421">Shut up stupid, it is forbidden to talk about it!</text>
	<text id="422">&quot; Principal island sanitation department: NO SWIMMING! &quot;</text>
	<text id="423">Where do you want to go?</text>
	<text id="424">To Port-Belooga.</text>
	<text id="425">To the water tower.</text>
	<text id="426">I&apos;m paying to see!</text>
	<text id="427">No way, this smells like a scam!</text>
	<text id="428">I can guide you through the Censored Publications Department. There is one book that talks about the Legend. I could show it to you, but first, I would like you to change the taste of the tap water, here in the city. It is the only type of water that I am allowed to drink, and it is really disgusting.</text>
	<text id="429">&quot;Old Burg @ (Principal island)&quot;</text>
	<text id="430">&quot;Peg Leg Street @ (Principal island)&quot;</text>
	<text id="431">Sorry, but you don&apos;t have enough Kashes. Come back later.</text>
	<text id="432">To Proxima Island.</text>
	<text id="433">I read some of the Captain&apos;s log - LeBorgne was ruthless! If you are still interested, the log is on sale at the Old Burg bazaar, on this island.</text>
	<text id="434">I am Bob Vortix, astronomer under house arrest. What are you doing in town, apart from beating up clones?</text>
	<text id="435">The Astronomer sent me.</text>
	<text id="436">Come back when you know where you want to go.</text>
	<text id="437">&quot; Life candy: would you like 10 hearts for 10 Kashes? &quot;</text>
	<text id="438">Ok, I&apos;ll buy.</text>
	<text id="439">No, thank you.</text>
	<text id="440">Not enough Kashes!</text>
	<text id="441">Good day. Come this way, I&apos;ll open the door for you.</text>
	<text id="442">Sound the alarm! A prisoner is escaping!</text>
	<text id="443">My poor friend! I really don&apos;t know what you are talking about.</text>
	<text id="444">You know Julia? She is a nice girl. She watches a bit too much TV, but there is some truth in her story: someone left a box for clover leaves on the islet in front of my house. It is too shallow for a boat to get there by water, and since the bridge leading to the islet has collapsed, the only way to get there is to fly.</text>
	<text id="445">Very good sir, wait here please.</text>
	<text id="446">What are you doing there, who are you?</text>
	<text id="447">I&apos;m fixing the antennas.</text>
	<text id="448">Twinsen, I&apos;m escaping.</text>
	<text id="449">Santa Claus.</text>
	<text id="450">&quot;Welcome to Port-Belooga @ (Principal Island) @ Sea calm to choppy, gusty winds.&quot;</text>
	<text id="451">I&apos;m not interested.</text>
	<text id="452">I&apos;ll buy.</text>
	<text id="453">Good day</text>
	<text id="454">&quot;L.B.A. @ Old Burg Sewer service. Emerald Moon Street.&quot;</text>
	<text id="455">Feel free to look through my stuff, creep!</text>
	<text id="456">She&apos;s not here. I would have noticed her. We don&apos;t have many readers these days.</text>
	<text id="457">I&apos;ve been all over the island today, and I haven&apos;t seen those people.</text>
	<text id="458">I didn&apos;t see her.</text>
	<text id="459">I didn&apos;t see her.</text>
	<text id="460">Sorry. I haven&apos;t seen your trio.</text>
	<text id="461">I didn&apos;t see her, but ...</text>
	<text id="462">The water is drinkable, but it is true that it tastes funny. You&apos;ll have to go to the water tower if you want to change something.</text>
	<text id="463">Good day</text>
	<text id="464">Good day, mate.</text>
	<text id="465">Bye, say hi to my cousin when you see him.</text>
	<text id="466">Good day</text>
	<text id="467">Sorry, but you don&apos;t have enough Kashes. Come back later.</text>
	<text id="468">We don&apos;t trust people easily here. Prove that you don&apos;t work for FunFrock, clobber a clone!</text>
	<text id="469">To Citadel Island.</text>
	<text id="470">To Rebellion Island.</text>
	<text id="471">Here it is: like new, good handling and fast, this catamaran is for you!... for 200 Kashes.</text>
	<text id="472">Too expensive for my blood!</text>
	<text id="473">Great, I&apos;ll take it.</text>
	<text id="474">Not enough Kashes!</text>
	<text id="475">I&apos;ve got to tell you something. It&apos;s awful! My best friend (Beatrice) is in love with Steven. But Paul, Steven&apos;s half brother, left Cindy when Linda got out of the clinic after her bobsleigh accident. But not for Linda, for Tatjana! Only Serge (who secretly admires Steven) has been trying for months to win the love of Tatjana who refuses to talk to Christy since she died. All the while Stephanie - who remarried Serge - discovered the letter from Paulina in which she explained where was the box of clover leaves left behind by Roy. So, evidently, Beatrice wonders if Linda knows about the accident. @ You get all that?</text>
	<text id="476">Wake up, I&apos;ve just found the escapee!</text>
	<text id="477">Thief! @ @ Leave my money box alone!</text>
	<text id="478">Sorry dear customer, but all that interests me is my modest concern.</text>
	<text id="479">Fool, don&apos;t do that! ANYTHING can happen now!</text>
	<text id="480">Ha, ha! You too are looking for his treasure? Well, I sure once had an old dusty book about LeBorgne, but a customer bought it this morning. It was a rabbibunny. I know that he works over at the library.</text>
	<text id="481">I have not seen this young lady. But go over to the Astronomer&apos;s house. Even though he is not allowed to leave his own house, he knows everything. He lives in the last house on the hill overlooking the city.</text>
	<text id="482">It tastes EXACTLY the same as before. I won&apos;t guide you through the library.</text>
	<text id="483">Did you know that a wise guy dumped some syrup into the island&apos;s water supply? I&apos;d like to find that guy so that I can give him a piece of my mind. You wouldn&apos;t happen to know him, would you?</text>
	<text id="484">It was me! Not bad, huh?</text>
	<text id="485">Probably another FunFrock stunt.</text>
	<text id="486">Bravo! This little twinge of cherry is fantastic. Ever since my doctor told me that I could only drink tap water and... well you know all that. In gratitude, I can show you all the ancient works that are here, even the LEGENDARY ones!</text>
	<text id="487">Oh, so Dr. FunFrock is taking care of us now. Funny, I find it hard to believe that it was him.</text>
	<text id="488">I have not seen this person.</text>
	<text id="489">My dear sir, I have been looking for Captain LeBorgne&apos;s log for years now. And would you believe that I found it today while shopping in the Old Burg? Naturally, such a piece should be consulted on site. Go look on the table in the back of the room next to the projection room.</text>
	<text id="490">Wait here, I&apos;ll go get them for you.</text>
	<text id="491">We must have something about LeBorgne. Go check with the chief librarian. You know him already, he&apos;s a rather large, orange rabbibunny.</text>
	<text id="492">Ok, I&apos;ll read you an extract from this book if you promise to leave me alone. What do you want me to read about?</text>
	<text id="493">Pirate recipes.</text>
	<text id="494">Leborgne&apos;s treasure.</text>
	<text id="495">Why LeBorgne?</text>
	<text id="496">As you know, this is a French game, and our respect for the culinary arts prevents us from revealing the ingredients used in pirate recipes. </text>
	<text id="497">&quot; To find Captain LeBorgne&apos;s treasure, the voyager who arrives at the port of Proxima island must use the closest mooring post as a guide. With his back to the docked boats, he must follow these instructions in DISCREET mode: @ 6 steps to the North (straight ahead), then 6 steps to the East (to his right), following the gradual slope. 2 steps to the North (straight ahead) until he reaches the metal garbage can, 3 steps to the East (to his right) until he arrives at a light post. He must stand EXACTLY between the 2 lamp posts, and then take 8 steps to the North until he arrives at a gate. Captain LeBorgne&apos;s treasure is in the building behind the gate.&quot;</text>
	<text id="498">&quot;That was his nickname because he was always chewing an old toothpick. One day, during a typhoon, he sneezed: he found his toothpick, but lost an eye!&quot;</text>
	<text id="499">There&apos;s no need to be aggressive, I was here before you!</text>
	<text id="500">Good day!</text>
	<text id="501">I don&apos;t know where they could be.</text>
	<text id="502">This is rebellion, it is forbidden to speak of that Legend!</text>
	<text id="503">I didn&apos;t see her, but the Astronomer will certainly be able to help you.</text>
	<text id="504">You should talk to the sailors about that kind of story.</text>
	<text id="505">I&apos;d like to help you, but I don&apos;t know where they are.</text>
	<text id="506">Hmmh! Quite a character that LeBorgne, he scoured the entire hemisphere a few hundred years ago. My fisherman friend told me that the Bazaar is selling an object that belonged to LeBorgne.</text>
	<text id="507">I don&apos;t know where they are.</text>
	<text id="508">Hiiii hi ! Bbbrrfff !</text>
	<text id="509">One of my colleagues was galloping at full speed across the White Leaf Desert and he said that he saw someone locked up in a grotto, behind a giant symbol of some kind.</text>
	<text id="510">Never heard anything about it!</text>
	<text id="511">What&apos;s a Teleportation Center?</text>
	<text id="512">Hi!</text>
	<text id="513">Ah! That LeBorgne was quite a man!</text>
	<text id="514">Ha ha, that&apos;s a good one! Sorry I don&apos;t have any with me.</text>
	<text id="515">Can&apos;t seem to sell a single hair dryer here. One of my colleagues is already out there trying his best. If this keeps up, I&apos;ll have to move on to another island.</text>
	<text id="516">I don&apos;t know where they are.</text>
	<text id="517">I cannot help you, my friend. Don&apos;t know what you are talking about.</text>
	<text id="518">Take that, rebel!</text>
	<text id="519">Move along!</text>
	<text id="520">Good day</text>
	<text id="521">Go to the tavern, they love pirate stories there!</text>
	<text id="522">Leave me alone, I have nothing to say.</text>
	<text id="523">Good day</text>
	<text id="524">It is strictly forbidden to talk about that!</text>
	<text id="525">Never heard anything about it.</text>
	<text id="526">I don&apos;t know where they are.</text>
	<text id="527">Sorry, I don&apos;t know what you&apos;re talking about.</text>
	<text id="528">Hi!</text>
	<text id="529">Calm down!</text>
	<text id="530">I didn&apos;t see her.</text>
	<text id="531">Look, you seem like a nice guy, but you&apos;re a big boy now. Figure it out for yourself, I&apos;m not a library!</text>
	<text id="532">I don&apos;t know anything about all that.</text>
	<text id="533">I didn&apos;t see her.</text>
	<text id="534">I don&apos;t know where they could be.</text>
	<text id="535">Pirates, phooey! Those sailors will say anything to get someone to buy them a drink!</text>
	<text id="536">Good day</text>
	<text id="537">30 Kashes for a hair dryer, how about that? I normally sell them door to door, but customers are sparse, and you seem nice enough.</text>
	<text id="538">Come in!</text>
	<text id="539">Good day, my good sir.</text>
	<text id="540">No. Not at all.</text>
	<text id="541">Go see Beatrice and tell her that Julia sent you. She&apos;ll explain all that better than I can. She lives on the outskirts of the Old Burg, in a house next to the sea, on Peg Leg Street.</text>
	<text id="542">Julia spoke a lot about you.</text>
	<text id="543">I don&apos;t know anything about pirating, try talking to the sailors instead.</text>
	<text id="544">I don&apos;t know where they are, kind sir.</text>
	<text id="545">Good day, young quetch.</text>
	<text id="546">I didn&apos;t see her.</text>
	<text id="547">I don&apos;t know what you&apos;re talking about!</text>
	<text id="548">They say that the tap water tastes better now. Great! Another publicity stunt from the anti-alcohol foundation.</text>
	<text id="549">I never saw &apos;em</text>
	<text id="550">I don&apos;t know her, but go see Wadbull over at the bazaar. And be careful... normally it is forbidden to talk about that!</text>
	<text id="551">Ah, I never heard that one. But the one about the pirate that had rheumatisms in one leg and termites in the other cracks me up every time!</text>
	<text id="552">Hi mate!</text>
	<text id="553">I don&apos;t know where they are.</text>
	<text id="554">LeBorgne! Since he didn&apos;t know how to read, he had his cook write the Captain&apos;s log. I know that it is for sale at the bazaar next door.</text>
	<text id="555">Sorry, I don&apos;t know anything about that.</text>
	<text id="556">This super Holomap costs only 20 Kashes (you will find that it is very useful!).</text>
	<text id="557">Gas for 10 voyages costs 30 Kashes.</text>
	<text id="558">15 hearts of life powder will cost you 30 Kashes.</text>
	<text id="559">10 flasks of magic powder will cost you 30 Kashes.</text>
	<text id="560">A meca-penguin will cost you 3 Kashes.</text>
	<text id="561">I didn&apos;t see her.</text>
	<text id="562">Sorry, I never heard anything about that.</text>
	<text id="563">Hi friend.</text>
	<text id="564">I don&apos;t know where they are.</text>
	<text id="565">Good day</text>
	<text id="566">Ask the boss or the sailor at the table.</text>
	<text id="567">You know that it is forbidden to talk about that! But this is your lucky day: I&apos;d most happily turn you in, but that would deprive me of a chance to line my pockets with your Kashes.</text>
	<text id="568">Good day</text>
	<text id="569">I&apos;m a huge STAR WARS fan. The saga&apos;s sequel should be released soon, so I already reserved my seat in the movie theater!</text>
	<text id="570">I&apos;d like to help you, but I really don&apos;t know much, except about movies. Good luck!</text>
	<text id="571">I found this page ripped out of a book. It says &quot;... pull the middle lever ONCE, then pull the right lever ONCE.&quot; This must be the answer to some kind of puzzle!</text>
	<text id="572">I don&apos;t know where they are. Sorry.</text>
	<text id="573">Good day</text>
	<text id="574">Ask the rabbibunny with the yellow T-shirt, he&apos;s the librarian.</text>
	<text id="575">Ow! But I found this page on the ground, I didn&apos;t rip it out. I promise!</text>
	<text id="576">According to the book I have, there is a &quot;Clear water&quot; lake in the Hamalayi mountains, somewhere to the North West of Principal Island. Did you know that the Hamalayi range is impossible to cross? It marks the border with the Northern hemisphere, the one that Dr. FunFrock cleared out. The sun is too hot for us over there: the temperature is unbearable, and the changes in climate caused the development of mutant monsters. And despite the fact that the good doctor spared us from all that, there are still rebels out there who want to overthrow him - it&apos;s shameful!</text>
	<text id="577">Sorry, I don&apos;t know what you&apos;re talking about.</text>
	<text id="578">Ask the librarian, he knows a lot about the history of LeBorgne.</text>
	<text id="579">Did you know that Dr. FunFrock installed busts of his effigy to protect us? The ones that don&apos;t have a pedestal are placed on ancient seals. Since these symbols were indestructible, at least the busts hide them now!</text>
	<text id="580">I don&apos;t know where they are.</text>
	<text id="581">Go see the librarian.</text>
	<text id="582">I never saw him, but try a little further up at the Bazaar. Wadbull knows a lot and he SELLS A BIT OF EVERYTHING!</text>
	<text id="583">Nobody remembers that nowadays. I even wonder if the library still has books about the Legend.</text>
	<text id="584">I don&apos;t know her. Sorry.</text>
	<text id="585">I don&apos;t know anything about it, but some people say that there used to be some books over at the library that spoke of it.</text>
	<text id="586">Stop doing that, you&apos;re going to put ashes everywhere!</text>
	<text id="587">Don&apos;t know where they are, but forget about it! Teleportation makes me sick.</text>
	<text id="588">Ewwwww! Teleportation makes me nauseous.</text>
	<text id="589">No more gas.</text>
	<text id="590">By the way - thanks, I have the red card!</text>
	<text id="591">You can&apos;t imagine what it&apos;s like to be locked up! @ It&apos;s awful... just awful!</text>
	<text id="592">I doubt that she is being held here.</text>
	<text id="593">Never heard anything about it.</text>
	<text id="594">They say that he was never captured!</text>
	<text id="595">Sorry, but I really don&apos;t know anything about it.</text>
	<text id="596">&quot;Drinking water for Principal Island: DO NOT THROW ANYTHING IN THE TANK!&quot;</text>
	<text id="597">Sorry dear customer, but this is a bazaar here, not a library!</text>
	<text id="598">No one remembers that stuff today, that&apos;s just a lot of bunk.</text>
	<text id="599">Well ... I don&apos;t know, but someone in the Old Burg must know something about this stupid Legend.</text>
	<text id="600">She&apos;s not being held here. But if you want my red card, go and see my brother. Our house&apos;s location is marked on your holomap.</text>
	<text id="601">I was just thinking as well, that I&apos;ve seen this quetch somewhere before!</text>
	<text id="602">Go try at the Old Burg tavern, and talk to the bar tender.</text>
	<text id="603">Hi, I&apos;ve just returned from a trip around this hemisphere and I&apos;m selling my boat. Follow me if you&apos;re interested.</text>
	<text id="604">Good day, so you&apos;ve been around the hemisphere? Watch out for the icebergs near the Hamalayi mountains!</text>
	<text id="605">You might get into trouble with the authorities if you carry this flag. It&apos;s a rebel&apos;s emblem.</text>
	<text id="606">Come here! Now that&apos;s a real sailor! LeBorgne had a log that must have contained the location of his treasure somewhere.</text>
	<text id="607">Never seen &apos;em, don&apos;t even know what you&apos;re talking about.</text>
	<text id="608">Well, well, what do we have here? A snooper? Twinsen I presume. I would like to know what you&apos;re doing here.</text>
	<text id="609">There&apos;s a treasure on this island: you must blow into a magic horn in front of FunFrock&apos;s bust to gain access to it.</text>
	<text id="610">I am not familiar with that story.</text>
	<text id="611">I don&apos;t know what that could be all about.</text>
	<text id="612">Good day</text>
	<text id="613">Good day</text>
	<text id="614">Hello</text>
	<text id="615">Good day dear friend.</text>
	<text id="616">Ah, those plans are not present in our books.</text>
	<text id="617">To the Hamalayi mountains.</text>
	<text id="618">Wherever you go, come back soon. We are waiting for the imminent return of a solitary navigator, and he will sell his boat.</text>
	<text id="619">Don&apos;t know anything about it!</text>
	<text id="620">It&apos;s kind of you to help me, but I managed to steal the guard&apos;s key. Take it, I don&apos;t need it any more.</text>
	<text id="621">I just discovered a secret passage by using the ACTION command, incredible! Do you like my red card otherwise?</text>
	<text id="622">Ah, it&apos;s impossible to open it without a red card.</text>
	<text id="623">Ah, it&apos;s impossible to open it without a blue card.</text>
	<text id="624">To the military camp.</text>
	<text id="625">Peg Leg Street.</text>
	<text id="626">I am cured. I don&apos;t kown what you poured in the water this time but my kidney stone vanished. Thank you!</text>
	<text id="627">Hello</text>
	<text id="628">One day, one of my swabs claimed that LeBorgne was an ancestor of mine and... well, you know how dramatic burials at sea can be!</text>
	<text id="629">Here&apos;s your book.</text>
	<text id="630">Good day</text>
	<text id="631">Good day, all this talk about the Legend is strange, don&apos;t you think?</text>
	<text id="632">Very strange indeed. I&apos;m just an old fool who would like to grow flowers in the desert, but... I know about this Legend that Dr. FunFrock forbade. I&apos;ll tell you what I know if you bring me a sacred book. It is in the Temple of Bù which was buried by a violent sand storm. You can still get in, however, through one of the ventilation shafts still visible just behind me. But be careful: there is danger everywhere!</text>
	<text id="633">&quot; This book is a keeper of knowledge. It allows you to read the rocks and to talk to the animals. &quot;</text>
	<text id="634">To Principal Island.</text>
	<text id="635">I&apos;ll leave later on.</text>
	<text id="636">I can get you to where you want to go for only 10 Kashes! Where do you want to go?</text>
	<text id="637">Sorry, Twinsen, you don&apos;t have enough Kashes.</text>
	<text id="638">To Citadel Island.</text>
	<text id="639">Thanks for opening the grotto. My name is Joe the Elf. I was locked up here because I wasn&apos;t meant to be in the story, there might have been some bugs in the game!</text>
	<text id="640">See you later, and thanks again.</text>
	<text id="641">You&apos;re too aggressive! Come back later when you&apos;ve calmed down.</text>
	<text id="642">Ow, you crazy or what? You don&apos;t deserve to be an elf, give me your membership card!</text>
	<text id="643">Where do you want to go?</text>
	<text id="644">Home.</text>
	<text id="645">Proxima island.</text>
	<text id="646">Rebellion island.</text>
	<text id="647">You are the Heir that the prophecy spoke of, Twinsen ! Find your ancestors&apos; legacy, hidden in your home, and pursue your quest. Come back and see me some time.</text>
	<text id="648">Only the Heir could have survived in that Temple! You are the Chosen One that the prophecy spoke of. You are worthy of keeping the Book of Bù, Twinsen. It will allow you to decipher the runes and to speak to the animals. The prophecy that must be accomplished is also revealed in its pages: you must overthrow Dr. FunFrock, the despot who has destroyed the harmony that once existed on this planet. In my dreams, I saw him profaning the Well of Sendell, which caused the immediate destruction of this world. You must go to the Well of Sendell to save us from Dr. FunFrock. I don&apos;t know where this well is, but your ancestors must have left instructions for you, somewhere in your home.</text>
	<text id="649">Hello fellow elf.</text>
	<text id="650">Adios! I think I&apos;m going out to discover the world. </text>
	<text id="651">You seem to be nice enough, I dub thee an honorary elf. Here&apos;s your card. It entitles you to a present.</text>
	<text id="652">Hello, quetch !</text>
	<text id="653">Good day, horse.</text>
	<text id="654">I know the story of the emerald moon, but that&apos;s all.</text>
	<text id="655">Hii, hi ! Bbbrrrff ! Brf !</text>
	<text id="656">I don&apos;t know what that could be all about.</text>
	<text id="657">Did you know that there are strange noises coming from that symbol on the rocks?</text>
	<text id="658">You were the one who freed that gnome with the hideous hat? He asked me if there was a princess that needed freeing in the neighborhood, but if you want my opinion, he doesn&apos;t have what it takes to be a hero.</text>
	<text id="659">No more gas.</text>
	<text id="660">Then you should go visit the Maritime museum on Proxima island.</text>
	<text id="661">I can&apos;t help you, sorry.</text>
	<text id="662">I&apos;m looking for the plans of the Teleportation Center.</text>
	<text id="663">They say that there are treasures hidden in a temple, somewhere in the desert.</text>
	<text id="664">I&apos;m looking for information about LeBorgne the pirate.</text>
	<text id="665">I read some excerpts from the Captain&apos;s log, that LeBorgne was ruthless! If you&apos;re still interested, the log is for sale at the Old Burg bazaar, on the Principal island.</text>
	<text id="666">I don&apos;t know where they are.</text>
	<text id="667">I don&apos;t know anything about it, but I think a while ago the library had some books that spoke of it.</text>
	<text id="668">I don&apos;t know where they are, but we elves don&apos;t need that sort of stuff. We can teleport ourselves magically! Well, I forgot how, but I&apos;m not a good example.</text>
	<text id="669">To the Hamalayi mountains.</text>
	<text id="670">I&apos;ll give you my guitar in exchange for the flute that you possess Twinsen, beforehand, though, you will have play it next to the Clear Water Lake in order to obtain the 4th magical symbol.</text>
	<text id="671">You will no longer need the flute, Twinsen. On the other hand, it might allow me to realize an old dream of mine. I&apos;ll trade you for this guitar that I found in the middle of a meteor.</text>
	<text id="672">Good day</text>
	<text id="673">&quot; Maritime Museum, rates: @ Children ... 3 Kashes @ Adults ... 5 Kashes. &quot;</text>
	<text id="674">&quot; Welcome to Proxim-City @ (Proxima Island). &quot;</text>
	<text id="675">&quot; Guard post - open 24 hours a day. Do not disturb... &quot;</text>
	<text id="676">&quot; Appropriate attire required! &quot;</text>
	<text id="677">I&apos;m looking for the plans of the Teleportation Center.</text>
	<text id="678">To Principal Island.</text>
	<text id="679">To Citadel Island.</text>
	<text id="680">We&apos;ll see about that later.</text>
	<text id="681">For 10 Kashes, where do you want to go, Twinsen ?</text>
	<text id="682">Sorry, you don&apos;t have enough Kashes. I&apos;ve got kids to feed you know!</text>
	<text id="683">Good day, a ticket for the museum costs 5 Kashes. Would you like one?</text>
	<text id="684">Yes, I&apos;ll take one.</text>
	<text id="685">No, museums put me to sleep.</text>
	<text id="686">Sorry, but you don&apos;t have enough Kashes.</text>
	<text id="687">&quot; Rear starboard propeller of the FunFrock 2. It was lost when the ship was launched from Principal island. The boat ran out of gas three days later, and finally stopped turning around in circles. &quot;</text>
	<text id="688">&quot; Captain LeBorgne&apos;s treasure. This chest contains the fruits of a lifetime of dishonesty. It was seized by the IRS, the only predator known to this terrible pirate. &quot;</text>
	<text id="689">&quot; Loan shark. This species of shark belongs to the movie producer family. &quot;</text>
	<text id="690">&quot; Reed Boat or Quffa. Primitive boat made from weaved reeds.&quot;</text>
	<text id="691">&quot; Boarding cannon. &quot;</text>
	<text id="692">&quot; Oak barrel. Barrels such as this one were used to serve up the daily rations of rum to the sailors. &quot;</text>
	<text id="693">&quot; Bùian Mermaid. A fine example of the absurdity of ancient superstitions: this statue was found in the middle of a desert. &quot;</text>
	<text id="694">&quot; Lifeboat. Do not pierce, burn, or bring into contact with an incandescent object. &quot;</text>
	<text id="695">&quot; Life candies: would you like 10 hearts for 10 Kashes? &quot;</text>
	<text id="696">Ok, I&apos;ll take them.</text>
	<text id="697">No thank you.</text>
	<text id="698">Not enough Kashes !</text>
	<text id="699">Halt. It is forbidden to touch the exhibits.</text>
	<text id="700">Sound the alarm! It&apos;s the escapee!</text>
	<text id="701">&quot; Construction work. SLOW DOWN! &quot;</text>
	<text id="702">&quot; I am the Eclipse Stone. The password for the Marked Stone is &quot;BURBS&quot;. Which word will free me? &quot;</text>
	<text id="703">&quot; I am the Marked Stone. The password for the Eclipse Stone is &quot;GIZMO&quot;. Which word will free me? &quot;</text>
	<text id="704">I don&apos;t know.</text>
	<text id="705">&quot; BURBS &quot;</text>
	<text id="706">&quot; GIZMO &quot;</text>
	<text id="707">My brother was arrested and the house is under surveillance: phony red card traffic. Wait a minute, how did you get in here? And who are you?</text>
	<text id="708">My name is Twinsen. I met your brother. He is in jail but is fine for the moment. He told me to mention the word &quot;Amos&quot; to you.</text>
	<text id="709">My name is Twinsen and I am the Heir... @ voila, voila, voila.</text>
	<text id="710">Ah! Ok. Then you might need this.</text>
	<text id="711">I&apos;m really happy for you, Twinsen! But my brother is being held in FunFrock&apos;s headquarters. His cell has a window that is right on the street. If you could tell me how he&apos;s doing, I will give you a red card in gratitude.</text>
	<text id="712">You&apos;ve just rediscovered all the objects that are in your inventory!</text>
	<text id="713">&quot; L.B.A. @ Proxim-City sewer service @ Ferry Street &quot;</text>
	<text id="714">I&apos;ve been trying to sell this hair dryer ever since I was on Principal island! Come on, I know you can use one for 30 Kashes.</text>
	<text id="715">You don&apos;t have enough Kashes, see you later.</text>
	<text id="716">I don&apos;t have anything else to sell!</text>
	<text id="717">Aah, I see that you too have come to Proxima island. You remember me, I sell hair dryers. Look, I&apos;ll sell you one for only 30 Kashes, but only because it&apos;s been a slow day.</text>
	<text id="718">Don&apos;t know what you&apos;re talking about.</text>
	<text id="719">I&apos;ve been working on a Jet-Pack prototype for days now. It&apos;s a small reactor that harnesses onto your back and allows you to fly about. My problem is that my last test flight wreaked a bit of havoc on the garden wall. It is rather difficult to fine tune the motor&apos;s power. I need a rheostat like the one you find in a hair dryer. Do you think you can find one of those for me?</text>
	<text id="720">So you found a hair dryer? Great! I&apos;ll be with you in a minute, just let me install the rheostat.</text>
	<text id="721">Well it&apos;s not a Jet-Pack yet, it&apos;s still just a Proto-Pack. I would appreciate it if you could test it out to see how it works. You should be able to fly over the water if you approach it from a gently sloping beach. But don&apos;t jump! Will you test it for 10 Kashes?</text>
	<text id="722">How&apos;s the Proto-Pack coming along? Keep testing, I have a bunch of calculations to finish up. And be careful when approaching water: you can only fly by coming in from a gently sloping beach.</text>
	<text id="723">&quot; Our heroic clone troops are responding to the rising rebel threat with a series of bombardments. &quot;</text>
	<text id="724">&quot; Skull flag. Pirate emblem belonging to the famous pirate Captain LeBorgne. &quot;</text>
	<text id="725">The museum&apos;s alarm system has been activated: we have evacuated the premises for your security. We will open up again later!</text>
	<text id="726">There was a false alarm at the museum. The only way out was through the sewers, but the grate was not moved, so we&apos;re reopening the building.</text>
	<text id="727">Good day.</text>
	<text id="728">Sorry, but you don&apos;t have enough Kashes.</text>
	<text id="729">Welcome, dear customer, and thank you for honoring my humble establishment with your presence. Move in front of the item that you desire and use the ACTION command.</text>
	<text id="730">Thief! @ @ Leave my money box alone!</text>
	<text id="731">You&apos;re too aggressive! Come back when you&apos;ve calmed down a bit!</text>
	<text id="732">Where do you want to go?</text>
	<text id="733">Citadel Island.</text>
	<text id="734">The White Leaf Desert.</text>
	<text id="735">Rebellion Island.</text>
	<text id="736">Gas for 10 voyages costs 30 Kashes.</text>
	<text id="737">15 hearts of life powder will cost you 30 Kashes.</text>
	<text id="738">10 flasks of magic powder will cost you 30 Kashes.</text>
	<text id="739">One meca-pinguin costs 3 Kashes.</text>
	<text id="740">My brother is in one of the cells that has a window on the street, in FunFrock&apos;s headquarters. And you know, if you tell me how he is doing, I&apos;ll give you a red card.</text>
	<text id="741">I&apos;m not interested.</text>
	<text id="742">I don&apos;t know where they are.</text>
	<text id="743">I don&apos;t know what you&apos;re talking about.</text>
	<text id="744">Don&apos;t touch the alarm button, the grobo is wiring it as we speak. And in any case, it is forbidden to touch it!</text>
	<text id="745">Then go to the museum. And along those lines, don&apos;t touch the alarm button on the wall! </text>
	<text id="746">Well you can believe me if you want, but the museum is well protected! I just connected this button to the alarm system: the building is evacuated as soon as it is pressed. @ Only one or two automatic guards will remain. It also sets off a series of sensors under the wooden floor that will sound the alarm as soon as they detect even the slightest weight. You would have to be able to fly to move around in there!</text>
	<text id="747">I think you&apos;re going to get hit, if you keep playing with that button!</text>
	<text id="748">I know that they have something about him in the museum.</text>
	<text id="749">That name sounds familiar. Go visit the Maritime museum, I think that they have two objects that belonged to LeBorgne.</text>
	<text id="750">Oh yes, it&apos;s great!</text>
	<text id="751">What about my test flights? I&apos;m not paying you to test your shoes!</text>
	<text id="752">I&apos;ve been working on a Jet-Pack prototype for days now. It&apos;s a small reactor that is harnessed on the back and allows its user to fly about. My problem is that my latest flight test wreaked havoc on my Southern wall. So I&apos;d like to borrow the rheostat in your hair dryer to fine tune the power of the motors (from looking at your hairdo, I don&apos;t think you really need the dryer, anyway). And if that works, I will have a job offer for you.</text>
	<text id="753">Well, well. It seems that you too have found an authentic secret map of Captain LeBorgne! Do me a favor would you? Give Lanktir, who lives next to the bazaar, back his coffee pot. I&apos;m so ashamed, I should have given it back long ago.</text>
	<text id="754">Go try at the museum.</text>
	<text id="755">Hi!</text>
	<text id="756">I&apos;m looking for information about LeBorgne the pirate.</text>
	<text id="757">No more gas.</text>
	<text id="758">I read some of the Captain&apos;s log - that LeBorgne was ruthless! If you&apos;re still interested, the log is for sale at the Old Burg bazaar, on Principal Island.</text>
	<text id="759">I don&apos;t know where they are.</text>
	<text id="760">I don&apos;t know anything about it, but it seems to me that there were some books over at the library that spoke of it.</text>
	<text id="761">&quot; For reasons of security, this sewer grate will open only from inside the Maritime Museum. &quot;</text>
	<text id="762">To the Hamalayi mountains.</text>
	<text id="763">Apparently, there was a burglary. The visits will recommence later!</text>
	<text id="764">Here, this will help you keep your strength up!</text>
	<text id="765">Apparently, there was a burglary. Alas, the thief escaped!</text>
	<text id="766">Never saw a storm like it, @ never!</text>
	<text id="767">Sorry, but I don&apos;t know where they are.</text>
	<text id="768">No more fake red cards, too dangerous, I quit. From now on, I am only going to make fake Captain LeBorgne secret maps.</text>
	<text id="769">Ah, it&apos;s impossible to open without a red card.</text>
	<text id="770">To the Eclipse Stone.</text>
	<text id="771">To the Marked Stone.</text>
	<text id="772">To Proxim-City.</text>
	<text id="773">So go in front of LeBorgne&apos;s chest, which is in the museum, and read the sign!</text>
	<text id="774">Good day</text>
	<text id="775">Sorry, I don&apos;t know anything about it.</text>
	<text id="776">Good day. Incredible huh? These objects belonging to LeBorgne that crossed through time; have you read the inscription in front of the chest?</text>
	<text id="777">Good day.</text>
	<text id="778">Don&apos;t know.</text>
	<text id="779">Don&apos;t know!</text>
	<text id="780">Good day.</text>
	<text id="781">So read the inscriptions, there are objects that belonged to LeBorgne here!</text>
	<text id="782">I cannot help you.</text>
	<text id="783">Someone made a mistake in the address and sent me this object by accident: it&apos;s a keypad that opens a door at the &quot;Teleportation Center&quot;. This opens a room full of meca-penguins.</text>
	<text id="784">If you give me back my coffee maker, I&apos;ll give you a list of certain places where you can find a rare plant and some boxes. And don&apos;t ask me where I found this list!</text>
	<text id="785">Good day.</text>
	<text id="786">I can&apos;t help you out.</text>
	<text id="787">&quot; Jérôme Baldino. Diverse Gadgets  Inventions. &quot;</text>
	<text id="788">Try at the museum.</text>
	<text id="789">Leave me alone, I have nothing to say to you.</text>
	<text id="790">§</text>
	<text id="791">Good day.</text>
	<text id="792">You must be Twinsen. Like you, we have rebelled against that madman FunFrock - and you saw what&apos;s left of the city. @ We don&apos;t believe that the Northern hemisphere has become uninhabitable like the propaganda says it has. There may even be some survivors living there who refused to be deported. This is why we have decided to take the road leading to the Okojo pass by force. It leads to the Northern hemisphere. Unfortunately, our leader, Colonel Kroptman, was captured during the attack. We believe that he is still being held in the small fort that guards the pass. Help us free him by raiding the fort. You will be able to get to the Northern hemisphere if you do so. Go back to the hangar, there is a commando waiting for you in the boat.</text>
	<text id="793">Go give your boss FunFrock this message for me, traitor!</text>
	<text id="794">Hi! If I take your flag to be representative of your intentions, I see that you too have chosen Liberty. Lieutenant Grap is down in the trench, go see him - he&apos;ll tell you where our leaders are.</text>
	<text id="795">So, young quetch, you&apos;ve come to help in the fight against FunFrock? As you can see, this city has suffered because of our rebellion. We are constantly bombed, which is why our leaders have set their camp in the center of the island. You can take my buggy to go see them.</text>
	<text id="796">&quot; Welcome to... AAARRGHH ! @ @ ... glb &quot;</text>
	<text id="797">Where do you want to go?</text>
	<text id="798">To Citadel Island.</text>
	<text id="799">To Principal Island.</text>
	<text id="800">To the White Leaf Desert.</text>
	<text id="801">To Proxima island.</text>
	<text id="802">I&apos;m staying here.</text>
	<text id="803">Go see Grap first if you want to drive. He&apos;s a rabbibunny and he&apos;s down in the trench.</text>
	<text id="804">Twinsen, you MUST SUCCEED in this mission. That fort is in a strategic position of the utmost importance. Once we&apos;ve taken it, the two hemispheres can be united once again.</text>
	<text id="805">We&apos;re going to help you take the fort: you will guide me, and I&apos;ll follow you with my grenades! Whatever you do, wait for me before you change zones and don&apos;t forget to neutralize the emitter. We won&apos;t talk during the combats and if I bite it, another rebel will come and take my place, he&apos;ll wait for you at the landing site.</text>
	<text id="806">I&apos;m looking for the plans of the Teleportation Center.</text>
	<text id="807">You&apos;re now one of us, Twinsen.</text>
	<text id="808">Be careful behind the wheel, this isn&apos;t a go cart!</text>
	<text id="809">Calm down! Save your strength for the clones.</text>
	<text id="810">Hey, you look familiar! I just came back from an infiltration mission in Proxim-City and I saw your mug on quite a few wanted posters.</text>
	<text id="811">I&apos;ve heard about an underground city that the clones use as a meeting place. It&apos;s in the Northern hemisphere, on Tippet island. You should check it out!</text>
	<text id="812">Ask Grap. He&apos;s in the trench, he&apos;ll know where to find them.</text>
	<text id="813">The end is near for FunFrock.</text>
	<text id="814">You must wait for your partner when you change zones if you want to make it through this mission.</text>
	<text id="815">Thank you Twinsen, we couldn&apos;t have done it without you.</text>
	<text id="816">Try over at Funky-Town. You can buy anything over there!</text>
	<text id="817">No more gas.</text>
	<text id="818">To the Hamalayi mountains.</text>
	<text id="819">To the rebel camp.</text>
	<text id="820">To the harbour.</text>
	<text id="821">I haven&apos;t seen them. @ Sorry!</text>
	<text id="822">Good day</text>
	<text id="823">Good day</text>
	<text id="824">Sorry, I don&apos;t know where they are.</text>
	<text id="825">Good day.</text>
	<text id="826">You need me to get into the fort. Wait there!</text>
	<text id="827">Come with me, we&apos;ll continue in the tank!</text>
	<text id="828">I&apos;ll cover you - go free the Colonel.</text>
	<text id="829">Don&apos;t jive me, my predecessor was killed in combat! Well, I guess that&apos;s life, huh? Shall we go?</text>
	<text id="830">Quick, get me out of here!</text>
	<text id="831">Hey quetch, hell of a job. If you&apos;d like to carry on down the corridor and, try to open the hatch at the end of the hall.</text>
	<text id="832">From this warehouse we send material to the other hemisphere, we use a shuttle that dates back to the old subway lines. I participated in its construction but I&apos;ve been waiting for a ferry for two years... Two years!!</text>
	<text id="833">Yes, I know, you also want me to start the transporter. Ok, stand in front of it, I&apos;ll start it up.</text>
	<text id="834">I don&apos;t know what that could be all about.</text>
	<text id="835">I&apos;m with the rebels who are fighting against FunFrock. We are currently trying to cross the Hamalayi mountains. Our leader, Colonel Kroptman, has been taken prisoner. Welcome aboard if you are joining the fight! Go see my friends on Rebellion island. They will let you dock only if you&apos;re displaying the proper emblem: a pirate flag with a skull.</text>
	<text id="836">Use the flag: attach it to your boat and you will be able to dock on Rebellion island. You will certainly be able to help us cross the Hamalayi mountains.</text>
	<text id="837">Hang on! Wait for you partner before trying to change zones. If you are having problems reaching the fort, try neutralizing the radar above the bunkers, in the zone where you landed.</text>
	<text id="838">You&apos;re a real hero, Twinsen ! Well uh ... I mean, thanks for freeing Colonel Kroptman.</text>
	<text id="839">Thanks to you, we are now in contact with the Northern hemisphere. And I&apos;ve received some information about that black-market city, Funky-Town. You will surely find some information over there!</text>
	<text id="840">Hang in there Twinsen, your quest is almost over.</text>
	<text id="841">There are still a few clones left, but with Kroptman at the helm of the tank, we&apos;ll take the fort.</text>
	<text id="842">Ask the look-out further on down the road, he&apos;ll be able to help you.</text>
	<text id="843">No more gas.</text>
	<text id="844">Ah! I don&apos;t know where those plans are. You can find information about everything in Funky-Town, but this city will soon be destroyed by FunFrock.</text>
	<text id="845">Hey, get me out of here! Find a key quick!</text>
	<text id="846">I am Raymond-the-Elf, to show my gratitude, I will indicate the location of the Clear Water Lake to you. It is to the North-West, in the Hamalayi mountains (look on your Holomap). If you play the flute there, you will find an important element of the prophecy. And if you have a membership card you can show me, I&apos;ve something else for you.</text>
	<text id="847">I am Raymond-the-Elf, to show my gratitude, I will indicate the location of the Clear Water Lake to you. It is to the North-West, in the Hamalayi mountains (look on your Holomap). If you play the flute there, you will find an important element of the prophecy. And in a grotto near the temple of Bù, you&apos;ll find one of my fellow elves, he&apos;ll be able to get you a blue card.</text>
	<text id="848">Hello fellow elf.</text>
	<text id="849">Never seen them, I don&apos;t know anything about teleportation.</text>
	<text id="850">Where do you want to go?</text>
	<text id="851">To Principal island.</text>
	<text id="852">To the White Leaf Desert.</text>
	<text id="853">To Proxima island.</text>
	<text id="854">To Rebellion island.</text>
	<text id="855">I&apos;m staying here.</text>
	<text id="856">To Citadel island.</text>
	<text id="857">I&apos;m looking for the plans for the Teleportation Center.</text>
	<text id="858">Hi, you should go see one of my fellow elves who is in the White Leaf Desert. He can give you a blue card.</text>
	<text id="859">What are you doing there? They&apos;re letting anyone in here now! I even captured an elf a little while ago. I don&apos;t know what to do with him, officially, that doesn&apos;t even exist!</text>
	<text id="860">Surrender!</text>
	<text id="861">Do you prefer to die on an empty stomach, or do you want something special for your last meal?</text>
	<text id="862">Too bad!</text>
	<text id="863">Not hungry!</text>
	<text id="864">You have not achieved a sufficient level of power to defeat the red clones. We will wait for your return.</text>
	<text id="865">Sound the alarm! A prisoner is escaping!</text>
	<text id="866">You&apos;ve just rediscovered all the objects in your inventory!</text>
	<text id="867">I don&apos;t know where they are.</text>
	<text id="868">I&apos;m looking for information about LeBorgne the pirate.</text>
	<text id="869">Good day.</text>
	<text id="870">You have no business here, this factory is top secret!</text>
	<text id="871">Don&apos;t touch those buttons!</text>
	<text id="872">Hey, you, don&apos;t touch our kitchen!</text>
	<text id="873">Noble stranger, we will open the Door of the Sacred Carrot for you if you sabotage the mutant factory, from where the monsters that infest this hemisphere emerge. This door leads to the shore, and from there you can access all of this part of the planet.</text>
	<text id="874">The passage that I&apos;m opening for you leads to a port, where the old subway that crossed the Hamalayi used to leave from.</text>
	<text id="875">Hey, you! Don&apos;t touch our k... oh, it&apos;s you! @ Good work, you have disabled the mutant factory! No more new monsters are being produced. By the way, what is your name, brave stranger?</text>
	<text id="876">No more gas.</text>
	<text id="877">Greetings! Our village is harassed by the mutants. But these monsters are not a result of the climate - they are produced in a nearby factory built by FunFrock.</text>
	<text id="878">This is not really a good time!</text>
	<text id="879">Thanks for your help. And, whatever you do, destroy the eggs if you are going in the factory! If you don&apos;t, new monsters will be produced and will come and attack the village.</text>
	<text id="880">I don&apos;t know what that could be all about.</text>
	<text id="881">Good day.</text>
	<text id="882">New monsters are still coming to the village: the factory has not been completely disabled!</text>
	<text id="883">And now, brave stranger Twinsen, follow me to the Door of the Sacred Carrot.</text>
	<text id="884">Twinsen</text>
	<text id="885">Thank you for saving this village, brave stranger Twinsen.</text>
	<text id="886">I don&apos;t know what that could be all about, brave stranger Twinsen.</text>
	<text id="887">It&apos;s so much calmer since you&apos;ve come, do you really have to leave?</text>
	<text id="888">I&apos;d like so much to help you, Twinsen.</text>
	<text id="889">Help!</text>
	<text id="890">Whew, safe!</text>
	<text id="891">Carrot, open up!</text>
	<text id="892">I&apos;m looking for the plans for the Teleportation Center.</text>
	<text id="893">Did you know that there is a Clear Water lake very near here. It is located close to the Door of the Sacred Carrot and it has a close connection with a prophecy.</text>
	<text id="894">You will have to interrogate traffickers, people that are in this hemisphere in any case.</text>
	<text id="895">Where do you want to go?</text>
	<text id="896">To Tippett island.</text>
	<text id="897">To Fortress island.</text>
	<text id="898">To Brundle island.</text>
	<text id="899">I&apos;m staying here.</text>
	<text id="900">Where do you want do go, Twinsen?</text>
	<text id="901">Ah, it&apos;s impossible to open without a blue card.</text>
	<text id="902">To the rabbibunny village.</text>
	<text id="903">To the mutant factory.</text>
	<text id="904">Leave me alone! I&apos;ve got work to do, and no time to play!</text>
	<text id="905">Use your red card to use the skilift.</text>
	<text id="906">Sorry, I don&apos;t know where they are.</text>
	<text id="907">I don&apos;t know where they are.</text>
	<text id="908">Good day.</text>
	<text id="909">Catch anything?</text>
	<text id="910">I&apos;m trying to find my bracelet...</text>
	<text id="911">Hold on, I&apos;ve got something!</text>
	<text id="912">I know this hemisphere very well, for 10 Kashes I&apos;ll tell you what FunFrock is concocting here.</text>
	<text id="913">Our leaders don&apos;t know that we come here, it&apos;s the only place where we can put these blasted helmets down. I&apos;m here for business only: I can sell you information about anything. See you later...</text>
	<text id="914">Did you know that there is a means of getting to Fortress island in my basement? I&apos;ll let you in there if you improve the quality of the show. The atmosphere is terrible nowadays, the patrons are bummed out.</text>
	<text id="915">That&apos;s much better, go on it! But be careful - there are still a few giant crabs. Thanks again!</text>
	<text id="916">With an atmosphere like this, I&apos;m gonna be rich!</text>
	<text id="917">Our group is sort of lacking: we don&apos;t have half the material we need, and we&apos;re eight hit songs short of an album. I&apos;m begging you: find a guitar for me!</text>
	<text id="918">I must be hallucinating, look, he found the Space Guitar!</text>
	<text id="919">I think we&apos;ve got a hit here, thanks pal!</text>
	<text id="920">No more gas.</text>
	<text id="921">&quot; L.B.A. @ Funky-Town sewer service &quot;</text>
	<text id="922">&quot; L.B.A. @ Funky-Town sewer service @ Swindler street &quot;</text>
	<text id="923">&quot; L.B.A. @ Funky-Town sewer service @ Dino-Fly street &quot;</text>
	<text id="924">Good day. Let&apos;s see, you can talk to me and you&apos;re wearing the Medallion of Sendell: you must be the Heir! I&apos;ve been waiting for you for centuries and I&apos;ve got a backache so we&apos;ll go carefully. The Hamalayi mountains are too high for me but I can lead you through this entire hemisphere, except for Polar island: it is too well guarded by FunFrock. Where do you want to go?</text>
	<text id="925">Where do you want to go Twinsen?</text>
	<text id="926">I don&apos;t know where they are.</text>
	<text id="927">Where do you want to go?</text>
	<text id="928">To Brundle island.</text>
	<text id="929">To Fortress island.</text>
	<text id="930">To the Hamalayi mountains.</text>
	<text id="931">I&apos;m staying here.</text>
	<text id="932">Ask one of the helmet-less groboclones, they come here to traffic and listen to music.</text>
	<text id="933">I&apos;m non-violent.</text>
	<text id="934">Ha ha, I was the watchman on the construction site of the Teleportation Center. So for 50 Kashes I can tell you EXACTLY where those plans are.</text>
	<text id="935">Thief, that&apos;s too expensive!</text>
	<text id="936">Sold!</text>
	<text id="937">You don&apos;t have enough Kashes, my poor little quetch.</text>
	<text id="938">The plans for this center are in FunFrock&apos;s personal safe. In his headquarters on Principal island. But to get in you must be able to defeat the Supergros (the nurses equipped with tablet launchers!).</text>
	<text id="939">Hi, nice weather huh?</text>
	<text id="940">I refuse to fight when I&apos;m not on duty.</text>
	<text id="941">So, which one of FunFrock&apos;s factories do you want information about?</text>
	<text id="942">I don&apos;t givre credit, come back when you&apos;re richer!</text>
	<text id="943">The mutant factory.</text>
	<text id="944">FunFrock cleared out the populations from this hemisphere but there are still a few people that resist like here in Funky-Town. He produces mutant insects in his factory at the foot of the Hamalayi mountains to exterminate us. The factory was supposedly sabotaged, but there are still monsters in the sewers: they were produced before the sabotage. In fact, you can jump on the giant crabs!</text>
	<text id="945">The Teleportation Center.</text>
	<text id="946">It is located on Brundle island, from there FunFrock&apos;s cohorts control all the planet&apos;s teleportations! The entrance is guarded but they will let you in if you act like one of them.</text>
	<text id="947">The Cloning center.</text>
	<text id="948">The center where all the planet&apos;s clones are produced is inside FunFrock&apos;s Fortress. It&apos;s his headquarters when he is in this hemisphere. Be careful because I heard that he is working on some VERY special clones, it&apos;s on Fortress island.</text>
	<text id="949">See you later.</text>
	<text id="950">That type of information is too specific, ask one of the helmet-less groboclones that are here instead.</text>
	<text id="951">Your hydroglider is great! But you won&apos;t make it to Fortress island or to Polar island with it. They are isolated by the currents, no ship can find them. You need a Dino-Fly to go there.</text>
	<text id="952">Ask the rabbibunny with the sunglasses, he&apos;s an informer.</text>
	<text id="953">Good day</text>
	<text id="954">I&apos;m looking for the plans for the Teleportation Center.</text>
	<text id="955">Calm down, I&apos;ll only let you in if the audience likes the group. Work it out with the guitarist!</text>
	<text id="956">Ask the rabbibunny with the sunglasses who is at the entrance to Funky-Town, he&apos;s an informer.</text>
	<text id="957">Those guys on stage are fabulous! @ But it&apos;s too bad that they don&apos;t play anything.</text>
	<text id="958">Wow! Never heard anything like that before, they are too much!</text>
	<text id="959">Be quiet, you&apos;d do yourself a favor if you listen to that, it&apos;s fabulous!</text>
	<text id="960">I don&apos;t know what it is.</text>
	<text id="961">You don&apos;t have enough Kashes.</text>
	<text id="962">Good day, if you like an item, move in front of it and use the ACTION command.</text>
	<text id="963">Thief!</text>
	<text id="964">Ouch!</text>
	<text id="965">Gas for 10 voyages costs 40 Kashes.</text>
	<text id="966">15 hearts of life powder costs 20 Kashes.</text>
	<text id="967">10 flasks of magic powder costs 20 Kashes.</text>
	<text id="968">One meca-penguin costs 3 Kashes.</text>
	<text id="969">I don&apos;t know where they are.</text>
	<text id="970">Your Kashes!</text>
	<text id="971">Or your life!</text>
	<text id="972">Mercy!</text>
	<text id="973">Mama!</text>
	<text id="974">Let me see some identification please!</text>
	<text id="975">It&apos;s weird this sign that appears, I paint over it regularly but it comes back every time.</text>
	<text id="976">Good day.</text>
	<text id="977">Where do you want to go?</text>
	<text id="978">To Tippett island.</text>
	<text id="979">To Fortress island.</text>
	<text id="980">To the Hamalayi mountains.</text>
	<text id="981">I&apos;m staying here.</text>
	<text id="982">&quot; The telepod&apos;s activating pedals are fragile. Stop jumping on them! &quot;</text>
	<text id="983">No more gas</text>
	<text id="984">Where do you want to go Twinsen ?</text>
	<text id="985">&quot; Welcome to Brundle island. &quot;</text>
	<text id="986">Alert!</text>
	<text id="987">Go ahead!</text>
	<text id="988">Clever, now there is no longer a sign on the wall.</text>
	<text id="989">Get out of here without breaking anything and we&apos;ll take it into consideration!</text>
	<text id="990">I&apos;m looking for the plans of the Teleportation Center.</text>
	<text id="991">I don&apos;t know where they are.</text>
	<text id="992">I have you at last! I see that you appreciated the clone that I made of your friend, the original is safe. @ I suppose that you have come here to find the 3rd Runic Stone. I already found it a long time ago, but it took some time to decipher it. And as soon as I knew the location of the Well of Sendell, I began the foraging work. @</text>
	<text id="993">Not being able to destroy the stone, I built my fortress around it to dissimulate it. That reminds me, you supposedly destroyed two of my factories, but that is of little importance! I will soon possess such fantastic powers, that I will need but an instant to clone or teleport the totality of the inhabitants of the planet. I also can make you relive the worst moments of your existence indefinitely... @ Good bye, you will never realize the prophecy because I will be the one who encounters Sendell and I will inherit her powers.</text>
	<text id="994">&quot; I am the stone of the Septentrion. The Well of Sendell is located at the summit of the rocky peak that is at the center of Polar island. Only the Heir can break the seal that bars the entrance. &quot;</text>
	<text id="995">Help Twinsen ! They found the Runic Stone and I ...</text>
	<text id="996">Ah, there you are at last my love!</text>
	<text id="997">I don&apos;t know where they are, but hurry up because FunFrock is going...</text>
	<text id="998">Don&apos;t know who rigged the telepods, I just succeeded in picking the lock of my cell, and I ended up here!</text>
	<text id="999">Their teleportation thingamajig is all smashed up. I was walking, minding my own business, in the Hamalayi mountains, and suddenly I end up here!</text>
	<text id="1000">Hi</text>
	<text id="1001">Stop fidgeting prisoner Twinsen!</text>
	<text id="1002">A prisoner is escaping! @ Sound the alarm!</text>
	<text id="1003">You&apos;ve just rediscovered all the objects in your inventory!</text>
	<text id="1004">Good day.</text>
	<text id="1005">&quot; Dr FunFrock&apos;s secret Fortress. You shouldn&apos;t even be reading that! &quot;</text>
	<text id="1006">Hmmm, what if I tried to attract a guard&apos;s attention?</text>
	<text id="1007">You are being held here because you are a troublemaker. We know from an informant that you claim to have prophetic dreams. @ Calm down, we&apos;re going to dissect... uh, I mean take care of you!</text>
	<text id="1008">Uh ... Hi!</text>
	<text id="1009">&quot; Training pool. Do not throw anything to the shark! &quot;</text>
	<text id="1010">&quot; Draining valve. DO NOT TOUCH! &quot;</text>
	<text id="1011">To Tippett island.</text>
	<text id="1012">To Brundle island.</text>
	<text id="1013">To the Hamalayi mountains.</text>
	<text id="1014">I&apos;m staying here.</text>
	<text id="1015">Where do you want to go Twinsen ?</text>
	<text id="1016">I know that symbol on your medallion. Virgul, our sorcerer, told us about your coming, and we have often prayed in front of the Runic Stone, which carries the same symbol. Unfortunately, Dr. FunFrock found it and built his fortress right over it, although the Rock was supposed to be indestructible! I would dig a tunnel for you so that you could enter the building, but you must first sabotage the Teleportation Center. Go find the plans of this center, I can dig only after all the telepods have been neutralized!</text>
	<text id="1017">I don&apos;t know where they are, but with these plans you must enter the Center on Brundle island and then sabotage it. Then I can dig under the Fortress!</text>
	<text id="1018">Go to Brundle island, get in the Center and neutralize the telepods control system.</text>
	<text id="1019">Good going, the telepods are no longer working, follow me!</text>
	<text id="1020">You&apos;re the one that&apos;s making life difficult for FunFrock? He recently threw a tantrum that could be heard from here. Since then, he brought in several telepods, he&apos;s worried about his fortress.</text>
	<text id="1021">You have once again angered FunFrock, he screamed a little while ago! What did you break this time, you know that he hates you?</text>
	<text id="1022">I don&apos;t know where they are, ask your flying animal over there. In fact, can you eat that animal?</text>
	<text id="1023">We no longer fear the threat of the teleportations, but you must get rid of the guards and the assault tank for us. I will then be able to dig.</text>
	<text id="1024">Good luck!</text>
	<text id="1025">Get out!</text>
	<text id="1026">I&apos;m looking for the plans of the Teleportation Center.</text>
	<text id="1027">I don&apos;t know where they are.</text>
	<text id="1028">Twinsen help! I&apos;m not a clone, it&apos;s me, the real Zoé.</text>
	<text id="1029">You must break the seal so that I can enter the Well of Sendell. None of my machines could drill through this rock, it resists me, just like the Runic Stone. I began digging around the rocky peak, but it will take months for me to reach the center of the planet! You&apos;ll see, I will realize the prophecy myself, and I&apos;ll take good care of this planet. Break the seal and I&apos;ll spare you Twinsen, you and your friend.</text>
	<text id="1030">I will at last see Sendell&apos;s face. If everything goes as planned, I&apos;ll make you my jester when I come back. Ha, ha, ha!</text>
	<text id="1031">Before you destroy the cloning factory, I prepared THIS for you!</text>
	<text id="1032">At last, you took your time, my love. I&apos;m not escorted by two groboclones, but I promise that it&apos;s really me. Go find Sendell and then we&apos;ll go home.</text>
	<text id="1033">Good day.</text>
	<text id="1034">I am Sendell, like all of those you see here, we are all Sendells. We are here to watch over a stellar entity that is in gestation, it will come into existence in a few centuries. As we can only act from the heart of the planet, we implanted a lineage of elected creatures among the species living on the surface. You are the current descendant of this family, and when FunFrock&apos;s threat had become too great, it was me that called to you in your dreams. The entity can now finish its gestation because you rid us of FunFrock. It would have died if he had gotten to it, and this world would have imploded, thanks to you it will continue to flourish. Return now to the surface, you can now erase the final traces that he left there.</text>
	<text id="1035">Twinsen, NO! We are finished, don&apos;t let him reach us!</text>
	<text id="1036">Uh ... you might be surprised when you discover the house.</text>
	<text id="1037">What are you doing there? The route that connects the 2 islands is classified top secret.</text>
	<text id="1038">Can&apos;t start this machine without an ignition key!</text>
	<text id="1039">Here, little guy, take the ignition key and bring the bulldozer back for me - I&apos;ll appreciate it. I don&apos;t have time to do it myself.</text>
	<text id="1040">This work is not moving along fast!</text>
	<text id="1041">The job is done!</text>
	<text id="1042">Ok, then go and come back to me when you are finished.</text>
	<text id="1043">Good bye!</text>
	<text id="1044">Lets talk about something else...</text>
	<text id="1045">Show me your wares.</text>
	<text id="1046">Thanks again for the help! What can I do for you?</text>
	<text id="1047">So how is it going with my the crates?</text>
	<text id="1048">I am sooo hungry. If you find something to feed me I promise to give you a ride. What do you think?</text>
	<text id="1049">Ok I will try my best</text>
	<text id="1050">So did you find something for me?</text>
	<text id="1051">Thanks, come back as soon as you can. If I wait too long I will faint!</text>
	<text id="1052">I might have found something for you...</text>
	<text id="1053">Great, exactly what I was looking for. Thanks, and here is my promise.</text>
	<text id="1054">No no, do you want to poison me?? Go find something suitable for a horse!</text>
	<text id="1055">Bye!</text>
	<text id="1056">I see. Let&apos;s talk about something else...</text>
	<text id="1057">Do you know where I could find some food for a horse?</text>
	<text id="1058">Did you have a look in the shop in town? They have a lot of stuff in there. They might have what you are looking for.</text>
	<text id="1059">Thanks, I am going to have a look at it.</text>
	<text id="1060">Let me see your wares...</text>
	<text id="1061">I just got a new arrival of grain bags. I got a lot so I will make you a special price!</text>
	<text id="1062">Welcome to my shop! Have a look around and tell me what you need.</text>
	<text id="1063">You have to try out this Champagne. Cuvee speciale. Thats some strong stuff we got here.</text>
	<text id="1064">Its time for celebration! Come over here I might have something for you.</text>
	<text id="1065">Merry Christmas!</text>
	<text id="1066">Happy new year!!</text>
	<text id="1067">Don&apos;t mind me I am just an extra. They only put me there because I have a nice looking suit.</text>
	<text id="1068">They are throwing a pretty big party over there. You might want to have a look at it!</text>
	<text id="1069">I am stuck inside the ground ever since I uncovered this statue. Everybody is gone to the party without even noticing me! Could you please give me a hand?</text>
	<text id="1070">Santa doesn&apos;t want to give me any gift... I am sure he is keeping all of them for himself!</text>
	<text id="1071">Ho Ho Ho! Meeeery christmas kid! Have you been nice this year? Oh whatever, just choose a present and get yourself moving. The next pleeeaaase? Oh man I sooo start to hate this job...</text>
	<text id="1072">Never seen a talking snowman?? Anyway you might want to talk to santa over there.</text>
	<text id="1073">Lets talk about something else...</text>
	<text id="1074">OK show me what you have...</text>
	<text id="1075">Please please pleeeeaaaassse!! I was very nice this year...</text>
	<text id="1076">We are going to play all night! Could you go fetch me some more coffee please.</text>
	<text id="1077">This guitar is fabulous! It was totally worth the price I got from this weird ponytail guy.</text>
	<text id="1078">Don&apos;t you see you are interrupting something... Go away!</text>
	<text id="1079">Man. This is so good. I can&apos;t get enough of it!</text>
	<text id="1080">Hey sweetie! What are you waiting for? Come to dance with us!</text>
	<text id="1081">Why are you staring at me like that! Everybody needs to have a litle break from time to time. Anyway, tonight is party night. Let&apos;s dance baby!</text>
	<text id="1082">We whish you a merry christmas...</text>
	<text id="1083">Man... I have no idea what I am doing here. And this music is so loud... Anyway, want to have a drink?</text>
	<text id="1084">And an happy new year!</text>
	<text id="1085">Sorry - hips -  I don&apos;t talk to funny looking strangers. buurps! You and your twin - hips - can leave me alone!</text>
	<text id="1086">Yeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeehaaaaaah!!!!!!!</text>
	<text id="1087">I just teleported back to the reality. The Lbanet team is giving you their best wishes for the new year! Cheers!</text>
	<text id="1088">We whish you a merry christmas...</text>
	<text id="1089">No you don&apos;t have what I want, please look for it.</text>
	<text id="1090">Want to see my clothes?</text>
</texts>
