<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<texts>
	<text id="0">Please insert TWINSEN&apos;s ODYSSEY CD-ROM</text>
	<text id="1">Please insert LBA2 TWINSEN&apos;s ODYSSEY CD-ROM</text>
	<text id="2">Ok</text>
	<text id="3">Cancel</text>
	<text id="4">Pause</text>
	<text id="5">Sound volume</text>
	<text id="6">Reverse stereo channels OFF</text>
	<text id="7">Reverse stereo channels ON</text>
	<text id="8">Configure keyboard</text>
	<text id="9">Return to the game</text>
	<text id="10">Don&apos;t display text</text>
	<text id="11">Display text</text>
	<text id="12">Sound effects volume</text>
	<text id="13">Voice volume</text>
	<text id="14">Music volume</text>
	<text id="15">CD volume</text>
	<text id="16">General volume</text>
	<text id="17">Cancel</text>
	<text id="18">Return to previous menu</text>
	<text id="19">Small videos</text>
	<text id="20">Full screen videos</text>
	<text id="21">Load game</text>
	<text id="22">Type in your name</text>
	<text id="23">Player already exists! Start again.</text>
	<text id="24">Type in the new name</text>
	<text id="25">Level of detail</text>
	<text id="26">Movie camera OFF</text>
	<text id="27">Movie camera ON</text>
	<text id="28">Destroy</text>
	<text id="29">Voice file transfer</text>
	<text id="30">Copying voice files to hard disk, please wait.</text>
	<text id="31">Resume Game</text>
	<text id="32">New Game</text>
	<text id="33">Load Game</text>
	<text id="34">Save Game</text>
	<text id="35">Options Menu</text>
	<text id="36">Quit</text>
	<text id="37">Normal</text>
	<text id="38">Sporty</text>
	<text id="39">Aggressive</text>
	<text id="40">Discreet</text>
	<text id="41">Protopack</text>
	<text id="42">Twinsen with Zoe</text>
	<text id="43">Triton&apos;s Horn</text>
	<text id="44">Normal Diving Suit</text>
	<text id="45">SuperJetPack</text>
	<text id="46">Sporty Space Suit</text>
	<text id="47">Normal Space Suit</text>
	<text id="48">Sporty Space Suit</text>
	<text id="49">Forwards</text>
	<text id="50">Backwards</text>
	<text id="51">Turn left</text>
	<text id="52">Turn right</text>
	<text id="53">Use weapon</text>
	<text id="54">Behavior menu</text>
	<text id="55">Inventory</text>
	<text id="56">Behavior action</text>
	<text id="57">Talk/Search</text>
	<text id="58">Center camera/Select</text>
	<text id="59">Menus</text>
	<text id="60">Holomap</text>
	<text id="61">Pause</text>
	<text id="62">Sidestep</text>
	<text id="63">Normal Behavior</text>
	<text id="64">Sporty Behavior</text>
	<text id="65">Aggressive Behavior</text>
	<text id="66">Discreet Behavior</text>
	<text id="67">Inventory help/Keyboard configuration</text>
	<text id="68">Save</text>
	<text id="69">Load</text>
	<text id="70">Options Menu</text>
	<text id="71">Turn camera</text>
	<text id="72">Next cameral level</text>
	<text id="73">Previous camera level</text>
	<text id="74">Weapon 1</text>
	<text id="75">Weapon 2</text>
	<text id="76">Weapon 3</text>
	<text id="77">Weapon 4</text>
	<text id="78">Weapon 5</text>
	<text id="79">Weapon 6</text>
	<text id="80">Weapon 7</text>
	<text id="81">Meca-Pinguin</text>
	<text id="82">Jetpack On/Off</text>
	<text id="83">Protection spell</text>
	<text id="84">Lightning spell</text>
	<text id="85">ESC exit, ENTER Select a key</text>
	<text id="86">Press a key or ESC to cancel</text>
	<text id="87">Error: key already defined</text>
	<text id="88">Action</text>
	<text id="89">Key 1</text>
	<text id="90">Key 2</text>
	<text id="91">Default Configuration</text>
	<text id="92">Restore Previous Configuration</text>
	<text id="93">Accept Configuration</text>
	<text id="94">Num Pad 1</text>
	<text id="95">Num Pad 2</text>
	<text id="96">Num Pad 3</text>
	<text id="97">Num Pad 4</text>
	<text id="98">Num Pad 5</text>
	<text id="99">Num Pad 6</text>
	<text id="100">Num Pad 7</text>
	<text id="101">Num Pad 8</text>
	<text id="102">Num Pad 9</text>
	<text id="103">Num Pad 0</text>
	<text id="104">Num Pad .</text>
	<text id="105">Num Pad Enter</text>
	<text id="106">Num Pad Div</text>
	<text id="107">Num Pad Mul</text>
	<text id="108">Num Pad Plus</text>
	<text id="109">Num Pad Minus</text>
	<text id="110">Up</text>
	<text id="111">Down</text>
	<text id="112">Left</text>
	<text id="113">Right</text>
	<text id="114">Start</text>
	<text id="115">End</text>
	<text id="116">Page Up</text>
	<text id="117">Page Down</text>
	<text id="118">Insert</text>
	<text id="119">Del</text>
	<text id="120">Left shift</text>
	<text id="121">Right shift</text>
	<text id="122">Left Ctrl</text>
	<text id="123">Right Ctrl</text>
	<text id="124">Left Alt</text>
	<text id="125">Right Alt</text>
	<text id="126">Tab</text>
	<text id="127">Num Lock</text>
	<text id="128">Caps Lock</text>
	<text id="129">F1</text>
	<text id="130">F2</text>
	<text id="131">F3</text>
	<text id="132">F4</text>
	<text id="133">F5</text>
	<text id="134">F6</text>
	<text id="135">F7</text>
	<text id="136">F8</text>
	<text id="137">F9</text>
	<text id="138">F10</text>
	<text id="139">F11</text>
	<text id="140">F12</text>
	<text id="141">1</text>
	<text id="142">2</text>
	<text id="143">3</text>
	<text id="144">4</text>
	<text id="145">5</text>
	<text id="146">6</text>
	<text id="147">7</text>
	<text id="148">8</text>
	<text id="149">9</text>
	<text id="150">0</text>
	<text id="151">Space</text>
	<text id="152">Enter</text>
	<text id="153">Windows Left</text>
	<text id="154">Windows Right</text>
	<text id="155">Application</text>
	<text id="156">Backspace</text>
	<text id="157">Pause</text>
	<text id="158">Scroll Lock</text>
	<text id="159">Print Screen</text>
	<text id="160">Shift</text>
	<text id="161">Ctrl</text>
	<text id="162">Alt</text>
	<text id="163">You just found your Holomap! To use it, look at the inventory by pressing SHIFT or simply press TAB.</text>
	<text id="164">You just found your Magic Ball! When you wear your ancestral Tunic you&apos;ll be able to bounce it at your enemies!</text>
	<text id="165">You have found three darts.</text>
	<text id="166">You just found Sendell&apos;s Ball. Now you have reached a new level of magic: Red Ball. It will also enable Sendell to contact you in case of danger.</text>
	<text id="167">You have just found your ancestral Tunic and Sendell&apos;s Medallion. By storing Magic, it will enable you to bounce your ball at your enemies.</text>
	<text id="168">You just found the Pearl of Incandescent. These Pearls are highly prized by magicians. They will enable you to complete a spell.</text>
	<text id="169">Your neighbor just gave you a pyramid shaped key.</text>
	<text id="170">Jerome Baldino just gave you a part that Zoé needs to fix the car.</text>
	<text id="171">Empty</text>
	<text id="172">You have found a laser-pistol. It needs a rock crystal to work properly.</text>
	<text id="173">You just seized the emperor&apos;s sword. Now you can face the hussars guarding the Emperor&apos;s palace.</text>
	<text id="174">You just found a Wannie&apos;s Glove. Use it to repell the fireballs your enemies throw at you.</text>
	<text id="175">You just found the Proto-Pack. Put it on and you&apos;ll fly a few inches above the ground.</text>
	<text id="176">You have a ferry ticket.</text>
	<text id="177">You just acquired a superb Nitro-Meca-Penguin. Select it in the inventory and it&apos;ll explode a few seconds later.</text>
	<text id="178">You just found a can of Gazogem. This fuel will allow you to get your new super jet-pack.</text>
	<text id="179">You just found the Ring of Dissidents. It&apos;s their identification sign, and it will allow you to be identified by all the dissidents that you meet.</text>
	<text id="180">You just found a flask of gallic acid. It&apos;s often used to restore ancient documents.</text>
	<text id="181">You just learned the ferryman&apos;s song. It will help you to get to Mosquibee Island.</text>
	<text id="182">You just found the customer&apos;s umbrella</text>
	<text id="183">You just picked up a gem.</text>
	<text id="184">You own the Horn of the Blue Triton, you can use it to heal yourself or someone else.</text>
	<text id="185">You now have a blowgun. It fires darts fast and accurately.</text>
	<text id="186">You have found a itinary token. You can now use an Esmer shuttle.</text>
	<text id="187">You just found a slice of tart!</text>
	<text id="188">You now own a portable radio. You can now receive calls from your friends.</text>
	<text id="189">You just picked a Garden Balsam plant.</text>
	<text id="190">You now own a Magic Slate, which allows you to keep a copy of all kinds of images.</text>
	<text id="191">You have found a translator. Now you&apos;ll be able to understand the Esmer language.</text>
	<text id="192">You just received your wizard&apos;s diploma. Plus you just earned a new level of magic: Green Ball.</text>
	<text id="193">You now own the Francos key fragment.</text>
	<text id="194">You now own the Sups key fragment.</text>
	<text id="195">You now own the Mosquibees key fragment.</text>
	<text id="196">You now own the Wannies key fragment.</text>
	<text id="197">You just found the key of the passage which leads to island CX.</text>
	<text id="198">You just bought a pick-ax. Use it to dig or detach rocks and pieces of crystal.</text>
	<text id="199">You just found the Francos Burgermaster&apos;s key.</text>
	<text id="200">You just found the Francos Burgermaster&apos;s notes. They&apos;ll help you find the Francos fragment.</text>
	<text id="201">You now own a protective spell.</text>
	<text id="202">You now own the key to Dark Monk&apos;s temple. Plus you just reached your last level of magic: Fire Ball.</text>
	<text id="203">You just found a memory viewer.</text>
	<text id="204">You just found the blowtron. Use it to shoot faster and more powerfully.</text>
	<text id="205">You just found a parade outfit for the wizards. It&apos;ll make you look like an old wizard.</text>
	<text id="206">Jerome just gave you the super-jetpack. It will allow you to reach places you couldn&apos;t get to using the proto-pack.</text>
	<text id="207">You just found a piece of the Crystal of Celebration. Now you can reload your laser-pistol.</text>
	<text id="208">You now own a laser-pistol in working condition. It gives you enough firepower to reach distant targets that your magical ball cannot reach..</text>
	<text id="209">You just found the Ring of Lightning! Use it to find Sendell&apos;s Ball.</text>
	<text id="210">Holomap</text>
	<text id="211">Magic Ball</text>
	<text id="212">Darts</text>
	<text id="213">Sendell&apos;s Ball</text>
	<text id="214">Tunic and Sendell&apos;s Medallion</text>
	<text id="215">Incandescent pearl</text>
	<text id="216">Pyramid shaped key</text>
	<text id="217">Part for the car</text>
	<text id="218">Kashes</text>
	<text id="219">Pisto-Laser</text>
	<text id="220">Emperor&apos;s Sword</text>
	<text id="221">Wannie&apos;s glove</text>
	<text id="222">Proto-Pack</text>
	<text id="223">Ferry Ticket</text>
	<text id="224">Nitro-Meca-Penguin</text>
	<text id="225">Can of GazoGem</text>
	<text id="226">Dissidents&apos; Ring</text>
	<text id="227">Gallic acid</text>
	<text id="228">Ferryman&apos;s Song</text>
	<text id="229">Ring of Lightning</text>
	<text id="230">Customer&apos;s umbrella</text>
	<text id="231">Gems</text>
	<text id="232">Horn of the Blue Triton</text>
	<text id="233">Blowgun</text>
	<text id="234">Travel Token</text>
	<text id="235">Slice of Tart</text>
	<text id="236">Portable Radio</text>
	<text id="237">Garden Balsam</text>
	<text id="238">Magic Slate</text>
	<text id="239">Translator</text>
	<text id="240">Wizard&apos;s Diploma</text>
	<text id="241">Fragment of the Francos</text>
	<text id="242">Fragment of the Sups</text>
	<text id="243">Fragment of the Mosquibees</text>
	<text id="244">Fragment of the Wannies.</text>
	<text id="245">Key for the passage to CX</text>
	<text id="246">Pick-ax</text>
	<text id="247">Franco Burgermaster&apos;s Key</text>
	<text id="248">Franco Burgermaster&apos;s Notes</text>
	<text id="249">Protective Spell</text>
	<text id="250">Green Magic Ball</text>
	<text id="251">Red Magic Ball</text>
	<text id="252">Fire Magic Ball</text>
	<text id="253">Zlitos</text>
	<text id="254">Dark Monk&apos;s Key</text>
	<text id="255">Memory Viewer</text>
	<text id="256">Blowtron</text>
	<text id="257">Wizard&apos;s Parade Tunic</text>
	<text id="258">Super Jet-Pack</text>
	<text id="259">Piece of the Crystal of Celebration.</text>
	<text id="260">Pisto-Laser in working condition.</text>
	<text id="261">Green Ring of Lightning</text>
	<text id="262">Red Ring of Lightning</text>
	<text id="263">Ring of Lightning, level Fire</text>
	<text id="264">Lucky Clover Leaf</text>
	<text id="265">The Holomap is a 3-D map system. You may use several zoom factors to determine your position on the planet. There are also arrows which can point to the location of tasks to be accomplished, after some characters have given you certain information.</text>
	<text id="266">You can throw the Magic Ball and make it bounce in different ways: For that, you need the Tunic since it allows you to store Magic power that the Ball consumes at each throw.</text>
	<text id="267">You can throw these darts at any time by selecting them in the inventory. To retrieve them, you only have to touch them.</text>
	<text id="268">Thanks to Sendell&apos;s Ball, you just reached your third level of magic: red ball. With its help, Sendell can come and talk to you in case of danger.</text>
	<text id="269">This Tunic, bequeathed by your ancestors, will help you store Magic power. Some is consumed each time you use a magical object, such as your ball. In order to use them, you must find enough Magic and carry it with you.</text>
	<text id="270">By dipping this pearl in the Weather Wizard&apos;s cauldron, you will be able to create a ring of lightning.</text>
	<text id="271">This Pyramid is a key. If you put it in the right place, it will activate a mechanism giving you access to a secret place.</text>
	<text id="272">After a few adjustmenta and once Zoé fits the part, the car will be ready to go.</text>
	<text id="273">It is the exchange currency of your planet Twinsun. It allows you to buy the articles you are interested in.</text>
	<text id="274">This gun shoots straight, far reaching rays. But, after each use, it needs some time to reload.</text>
	<text id="275">With the emperor&apos;s sword, you can now face the hussars of the imperial guard.</text>
	<text id="276">With this Wannie&apos;s glove, you can now touch the fire. This will allow you to throw back the fire balls that the monsters from the gas hurl at you.</text>
	<text id="277">It was designed by Jerome Baldino. In order to fly above water, you must approach at a low angle. Otherwise, you will sink with your Proto-Pack.</text>
	<text id="278">This ticket allows you to travel aboard the ferry which links Citadel Island and White Leaf Desert Island.</text>
	<text id="279">You can use the Nitro-Meca-Penguins by placing them in a level and unencumbered area.</text>
	<text id="280">After you give it to Jerome, this can of gazogem will allow your friend to turn your proto-pack into a super-jetpack.</text>
	<text id="281">This ring is made and worn only by the dissidents. It is their identification sign. It will allow you to be recognized as one of them and to make contact with them.</text>
	<text id="282">Gallic acid is used to restore ancient documents. It allows you to brighten up the areas where the ink has faded.</text>
	<text id="283">If you sing it at the end of the ferryman&apos;s wharf, you will see him emerge from the mist and come to offer to take you to another island.</text>
	<text id="284">Be careful, the devastating power of this ring consumes a great deal of Magic.</text>
	<text id="285">This umbrella belongs to a pharmacy customer.</text>
	<text id="286">The gems are commonly used by the Francos to produce gazogem. But you can use it to pay for the ferryman&apos;s services.</text>
	<text id="287">It lets you draw in hearts (Life points) and store them. You can then use them to treat yourself or someone else.</text>
	<text id="288">The Blowgun provides rapid firepower. You can reload it with small projectiles, such as berries.</text>
	<text id="289">The travel token allows to program the destination of an Esmer shuttle. Without it, the spacecraft cannot take off.</text>
	<text id="290">You don&apos;t like this tart, but you must give this slice to someone who appreciates it more than you.</text>
	<text id="291">This portable radio allows you to dialogue with Baldino and Zoé when they are listening and if they are not out of range.</text>
	<text id="292">You must bring this flower to the Rector of the School of Magic.</text>
	<text id="293">By using the Action command in front of a plan, a print or any other illustration, you immediately create a copy with the Magic Slate. You can consult it at any time by selecting the Slate in the inventory.</text>
	<text id="294">This translator allows you to understand everything said by the visitors from Space. In discreet mode, you can even spy on conversations.</text>
	<text id="295">Your diploma in magic has allowed you to reach the green ball level of magic.</text>
	<text id="296">This fragment of the Francos&apos; key is one of the elements which will permit you to piece together the key to Dark Monk&apos;s temple.</text>
	<text id="297">This fragment of the Sups&apos; key is one of the elements which will permit you to piece together the key to Dark Monk&apos;s temple.</text>
	<text id="298">This fragment of the Mosquibees&apos; key is one of the elements which will permit you to piece together the key to Dark Monk&apos;s temple.</text>
	<text id="299">This fragment of the Wannies&apos; key is one of the elements which will permit you to piece together the key to Dark Monk&apos;s temple.</text>
	<text id="300">This key will allow you to open the doors of the passage, whose entrance is in the village of the Mosquibees, and which will allow you to go up to islet CX.</text>
	<text id="301">This pick-ax will allow you to dig into the ground or harder materials. With it, you can now locate objects buried underground, or extract materials.</text>
	<text id="302">It is the key that the burgermaster lost before he was eaten by a monster from the gas. Nobody has ever used it since.</text>
	<text id="303">These notes contain the enigma which leads to the fragment of the Francos. They give a clue to the location where the fragment was buried is revealed.</text>
	<text id="304">This Tunic, bequeathed by your ancestors, now gives you protection besides storing Magic. To use the shielding spell, press Enter from the Inventory. This spell consumes some Magic, just like throwing the Ball and using several other magic objects.</text>
	<text id="305">You can throw the Magic Ball and have it bounce in many different ways. The green ball level allows you to inflict more damage upon your enemies.</text>
	<text id="306">You can throw the Magic Ball and have it bounce in many different ways. The red ball level allows you to inflict more damage upon your enemies.</text>
	<text id="307">You can throw the Magic Ball and have it bounce in many different ways. The fire ball level allows you to inflict more damage upon your enemies.</text>
	<text id="308">It is the exchange currency of planet Zeelich. With it, you can buy the articles you are interested in on planet Zeelich.</text>
	<text id="309">Once the four fragments are reunited, you will have the key to Dark Monk&apos;s temple. According to the prophecy, it will allow you to make the statue come out of the volcano&apos;s crater, and to open the doors of the temple built in it.</text>
	<text id="310">The memory viewer allows you to review the sequences which have punctuated your adventure.</text>
	<text id="311">With the blowtron, you now dispose of a much higher firing rate.</text>
	<text id="312">This parade outfit is accessible only to Twinsun&apos;s graduated wizards. It makes of you a bona fide magician.</text>
	<text id="313">It was put together by Jerome Baldino. It allows now you to access new locations and to follow some grades that were impracticable with the proto-pack.</text>
	<text id="314">This piece of the Crystal of Celebration is of unmatched purity. It will allow you to operate a pisto-Laser.</text>
	<text id="315">This pisto-Laser shoots horizontal rays. They will allow you to hit enemies who are at a great distance.</text>
	<text id="316">Be careful, the devastating power of this ring consumes a great deal of Magic.</text>
	<text id="317">Be careful, the devastating power of this ring consumes a great deal of Magic.</text>
	<text id="318">Be careful, the devastating power of this ring consumes a great deal of Magic.</text>
	<text id="319">This Lucky Clover Leaf gives you the benefit of an additional life.</text>
	<text id="320">Citadel Island.</text>
	<text id="321">Downtown Pharmacy.</text>
	<text id="322">Tent of the Weather Wizard.</text>
	<text id="323">Baggage claim building.</text>
	<text id="324">Miss Bloop&apos;s Private Museum.</text>
	<text id="325">House of Twinsen and Zoé.</text>
	<text id="326">Dome of the Slate.</text>
	<text id="327">Dino-Fly.</text>
	<text id="328">Incandescent Pearl.</text>
	<text id="329">empty</text>
	<text id="330">Well of Sendell.</text>
	<text id="331">White Leaf Desert.</text>
	<text id="332">J. Baldino&apos;s House.</text>
	<text id="333">House of Ker&apos;aooc the Healer.</text>
	<text id="334">Balsam Plant.</text>
	<text id="335">School of Magic.</text>
	<text id="336">Esmer Base.</text>
	<text id="337">Emerald Moon.</text>
	<text id="338">Baldino&apos;s Cell.</text>
	<text id="339">Otringal.</text>
	<text id="340">Space Shuttle.</text>
	<text id="341">Rick&apos;s Café.</text>
	<text id="342">Imperial Hotel.</text>
	<text id="343">Souvenir Shop.</text>
	<text id="344">Sups&apos; fragment.</text>
	<text id="345">Celebration.</text>
	<text id="346">Crystal.</text>
	<text id="347">Dark Monk&apos;s Temple.</text>
	<text id="348">Wannies.</text>
	<text id="349">Wannies&apos; fragment.</text>
	<text id="350">Island of the Mosquibees.</text>
	<text id="351">Queen of the Mosquibees.</text>
	<text id="352">Mosquibees&apos; fragment.</text>
	<text id="353">Francos.</text>
	<text id="354">Gazogem Refinery.</text>
	<text id="355">Francos&apos; fragment.</text>
	<text id="356">Islet CX.</text>
	<text id="357">Elevator to the under-gas.</text>
	<text id="358">Under Celebration.</text>
	<text id="359">With my eyes focused on the center of the bazaar, my back is glued to a natural parasol where I&apos;d love to take a nap, but I must keep a sportive mood. It seems there are enough light posts and arches in the village to count the correct number of steps. Once there, the fences to my left point in the wrong direction. It&apos;s on the other side, down in the basin near the gas that my buried treasure lies.</text>
	<text id="360">An action/adventure game on PC CD_ROM SVGA/DirectDraw graphics</text>
	<text id="361">Detail-packed 3D isometric interior rendering mode.</text>
	<text id="362">Revolutionary true 3D texture-mapped exterior rendering mode.</text>
	<text id="363">Explore over 220 places on 3 different planets.</text>
	<text id="364">Meet over 300 fascinating characters.</text>
	<text id="365">Incredibly smooth real-time animation with texture mapping and lighting.</text>
	<text id="366">15 minutes of stunning movie sequences.</text>
	<text id="367">Thousands of stereo sound effects and two and a half hours of spoken dialogue.</text>
	<text id="368">Voices in French, English and German. (Subtitles in French, English, German, Italian and Spanish).</text>
	<text id="369">30 minutes of soft, enchanting music.</text>
	<text id="370">Laughter all the way in this storyline that will keep you amused for more than 60 hours of play.</text>
	<text id="371">Yes, the family will soon be larger.</text>
	<text id="372">Let&apos;s go to the lighthouse!</text>
	<text id="373">Could you help me treat my injured Dino-Fly ?</text>
	<text id="374">How&apos;re you doing, Dino buddy?</text>
	<text id="375">I&apos;m looking for something to cure my injured Dino-fly.</text>
	<text id="376">OK, I&apos;ll buy it!</text>
	<text id="377">No, I am not interested.</text>
	<text id="378">OK!</text>
	<text id="379">10 Life points! Cool!</text>
	<text id="380">10 Magic points! All right!</text>
	<text id="381">All right Zoé, I&apos;ll take you back.</text>
	<text id="382">Hello?</text>
	<text id="383">This is the text of the ancient prophecy. It is intended for my family, in case my descendants are also called by Sendell. Hopefully, I&apos;ll never need it again. @ And that&apos;s all I&apos;ve got left from the house that FunFrock razed.</text>
	<text id="384">I freed him!</text>
	<text id="385">Hey, this looks like a map. But I can&apos;t read it!</text>
	<text id="386">The umbrella please.</text>
	<text id="387">Give me my tunic back!</text>
	<text id="388">Errr, ... nothing. See ya.</text>
	<text id="389">To knock you out!</text>
	<text id="390">&quot;To the glory of Dr. FunFrock.&quot;. This bust makes an excellent target.</text>
	<text id="391">Master, how do you explain a storm in this season?</text>
	<text id="392">Just looking.</text>
	<text id="393">To Woodbridge island.</text>
	<text id="394">I&apos;m going back to Lupin-Bourg.</text>
	<text id="395">To the wizard&apos;s lane.</text>
	<text id="396">They claim to be peaceful but let&apos;s be careful, they look sort of aggressive to me.</text>
	<text id="397">We are ready, Master.</text>
	<text id="398">Hello Luc.</text>
	<text id="399">Hello miss.</text>
	<text id="400">&quot;Dome of the Slate.&quot;</text>
	<text id="401">&quot;Ruins of the old citadel.&quot;</text>
	<text id="402">&quot;Beach headland.&quot;</text>
	<text id="403">&quot;Lupin-Bourg.&quot;</text>
	<text id="404">&quot;Ridge of the Flowers Circle.&quot;</text>
	<text id="405">&quot;Cliffs of the Woodbridge.&quot;</text>
	<text id="406">&quot;Lighthouse at the end of the island.&quot;</text>
	<text id="407">&quot;Harbor of Citadel Island.&quot;</text>
	<text id="408">&quot;Wizard&apos;s lane.&quot;</text>
	<text id="409">&quot;To the lighthouse at the end of the island.&quot;</text>
	<text id="410">&quot;To the Weather Wizard. &quot;</text>
	<text id="411">&quot;To the cliffs of the Woodbridge.&quot;</text>
	<text id="412">&quot;Downtown.&quot;</text>
	<text id="413">&quot;Access to the cliffs.&quot;</text>
	<text id="414">&quot;To the harbor.&quot;</text>
	<text id="415">&quot;Honey Bee&quot;</text>
	<text id="416">&quot;LBA&apos;s Theme&quot;</text>
	<text id="417">&quot;The Empire&quot;</text>
	<text id="418">&quot;When on Desert Island, visit the Temple of Bù, an eventful episode in the history of Twinsen.&quot;</text>
	<text id="419">&quot;Diploma of Elementary-Weather Magic. The Wizard Bersimon has proven his talents as a master of the elements. He has reached the rank of Grand Master of sea winds and tornadoes. &quot;</text>
	<text id="420">&quot;In the secret room, in the center of the sewers, there is an enchanted globe. The Weather Wizard put it there. According to him, it has to do with the Prophecy of Sendell. I preferred to lock this room : it can be opened only with the small pyramid.&quot;</text>
	<text id="421">&quot;To my future descendants: I have lent to Miss Bloop&apos;s private museum, the Medallion and the Ancestral Tunic which rightfully belong to you. Signed: Twinsen.&quot;</text>
	<text id="422">&quot;Representation of our planet Twinsun, in stable orbit between 2 suns.&quot;</text>
	<text id="423">&quot;I really like this image of my trusty Dino-Fly.&quot;</text>
	<text id="424">A portrait of me, back when I was charged with the power of Sendell...</text>
	<text id="425">Hey, a portrait of Sendell! They must have used my descriptions to make it.</text>
	<text id="426">&quot;Cross-section of Twinsun. @ @ 1: Sendell @ @ 2: Well of Sendell @ @ 3: Temple of Bù @ @</text>
	<text id="427">&quot;Personnel only.&quot;</text>
	<text id="428">&quot;Vial which once contained the Clear Water. &quot;</text>
	<text id="429">&quot;Rock from the Temple of Bù.&quot;</text>
	<text id="430">&quot;Book of Bù. It allows me to speak with the animals of Twinsun.&quot;</text>
	<text id="431">&quot;Horn of Gawley.&quot;</text>
	<text id="432">Aha !, Sendell&apos;s Medallion and my Ancestral Tunic.</text>
	<text id="433">&quot;Safeguard Street&quot;</text>
	<text id="434">&quot;Green Corulla Street&quot;</text>
	<text id="435">Hello.</text>
	<text id="436">Hi.</text>
	<text id="437">I am looking for the lighthouse keeper.</text>
	<text id="438">It&apos;s locked.</text>
	<text id="439">Good day, Master</text>
	<text id="440">Aha! a sign from Sendell. They are venerated by all the wizards.</text>
	<text id="441">I&apos;m staying here.</text>
	<text id="442">I don&apos;t have enough Kashes.</text>
	<text id="443">Hi kiddo!</text>
	<text id="444">Hello miss Bloop.</text>
	<text id="445">Hello Tim.</text>
	<text id="446">Hello Mr. Paul.</text>
	<text id="447">Hello neighbor.</text>
	<text id="448">Hello Mrs. Brune.</text>
	<text id="449">Hello Mr. Bazoo.</text>
	<text id="450">Hi Felix.</text>
	<text id="451">Hello Bob.</text>
	<text id="452">Hi Zed.</text>
	<text id="453">Hello little one.</text>
	<text id="454">Do you know where I can find Raph the lighthouse keeper ?</text>
	<text id="455">I don&apos;t see my buddy Dino-Fly. He must have landed a little further away.</text>
	<text id="456">This portrait of Zoé is magnificent.</text>
	<text id="457">This statue pays tribute to Zoé and me. Without her, I could have never defeated the infamous FunFrock.</text>
	<text id="458">So, miss, Raph is not here?</text>
	<text id="459">I was told to go see the healing wizard on Desert Island. He&apos;ll be able to help my Dino.</text>
	<text id="460">No, not yet.</text>
	<text id="461">Desert Island.</text>
	<text id="462">The island of the Dome of the Slate.</text>
	<text id="463">Take me back home.</text>
	<text id="464">The island across from the hacienda.</text>
	<text id="465">And nobody did anything?</text>
	<text id="466">But what can I do? How do I find the trail of the lost children?</text>
	<text id="467">What happened, miss?</text>
	<text id="468">Don&apos;t forget to finish the lightning potion. To do so, go to the Desert Island to find a pearl of incandescence.</text>
	<text id="469">Joe? What are you doing here?</text>
	<text id="470">Don&apos;t worry miss, I&apos;ll find the kids!</text>
	<text id="471">He told me the ball of Sendell would help me find the children. I&apos;ve got to find it.</text>
	<text id="472">But how can I do that, you left on your spaceship and I don&apos;t have one.</text>
	<text id="473">The car&apos;s not working. Zoé said there&apos;s still a part she needs. She asked Baldino to make it for her.</text>
	<text id="474">Geez, the counter-clerk is as smart as ever, he never recognizes me. What&apos;s more, he always charges me admission.</text>
	<text id="475">I want to get back my Tunic and my Sendell&apos;s Medallion.</text>
	<text id="476">But I saw the keeper! He&apos;s being held prisoner inside a cave under the cliff! I&apos;ve got to get him free!</text>
	<text id="477">I&apos;m still looking for a cure. Don&apos;t worry, I&apos;ll find one.</text>
	<text id="478">Desert Island.</text>
	<text id="479">The Dome of the Slate.</text>
	<text id="480">Strange, this looks like a keyhole.</text>
	<text id="481">No, not yet.</text>
	<text id="482">No, I&apos;ve got to find the school of magic first. They&apos;re the only ones who can help me cure him!</text>
	<text id="483">I&apos;ve decided to become a wizard so that I can help Dino-Fly myself.</text>
	<text id="484">By graduating from magic school, I&apos;ve earned this horn that I can use to treat Dino-Fly.</text>
	<text id="485">Could you help me find the school of magic?</text>
	<text id="486">All thanks to you. Without your help, Sendell and I would never have been able to push the moon back.</text>
	<text id="487">Most important of all, peace is restored ! !</text>
	<text id="488">Hi there Joe! Still having problems with your magical powers?</text>
	<text id="489">Hi!</text>
	<text id="490">You&apos;ll need a baggage check to claim anything stored here.</text>
	<text id="491">Ah, Mr. Twinsen. Your friend Baldino left me a crate for you. It&apos;s in the basement, a brown crate with a big label on top. Just follow the arrows, bring it back here, and I&apos;ll open it. If you need help, ask my colleagues downstairs.</text>
	<text id="492">Go ahead, Mr. Twinsen. It&apos;s your property, isn&apos;t it?</text>
	<text id="493">You again Mr. Twinsen? But I don&apos;t have anything left to give you!</text>
	<text id="494">He left work? Hmm! I&apos;ll bet he went to play his guitar by the cliffs again!</text>
	<text id="495">Get out of the way!!</text>
	<text id="496">Excuse him, he is a nice Grobo. You know, he only gives himself airs.</text>
	<text id="497">You showed up at the right time. The door at the top of the stairs is jammed. We need to find a way to go upstairs to release it and free the bell which protects your tunic.</text>
	<text id="498">Thank you for releasing the door, Twinsen. Use your tunic with wisdom.</text>
	<text id="499">By the way, don&apos;t forget that the trajectory of your magic ball changes with your behavior!</text>
	<text id="500">What? The lighthouse keeper? Ah, no! No, no I didn&apos;t see him!</text>
	<text id="501">Ah Twinsen ! Still here?</text>
	<text id="502">Oh Twinsen !! You look so cute as a wizard!!</text>
	<text id="503">Hello !</text>
	<text id="504">The price of admission is 15 Kashes! Interested?</text>
	<text id="505">Here, sir, we have a collection devoted to the great Twinsen and to the development of Magic on the planet. Don&apos;t hesitate to educate yourself!</text>
	<text id="506">Know, sir, that I alone have the right to press this button!! You must pay to enter!</text>
	<text id="507">I don&apos;t know this character!</text>
	<text id="508">Hey!... you know, you look like the guy in the picture!</text>
	<text id="509">I am not from here, you see... I don&apos;t know him.</text>
	<text id="510">Mr. Twinsen! Free me, quick!! I am Raph! You know, the lighthouse keeper!! I&apos;ve been caught by the Tralü, he wants to turn me into a rabbibunny-melba.</text>
	<text id="511">Help!</text>
	<text id="512">Please, Mr. Twinsen, go get your fetching little costume and your magic ball. Be our hero again! Come back to save me from the Tralü. I&apos;m scared he&apos;s gonna eat me!!</text>
	<text id="513">Thank you, Mr. Twinsen! I was rehearsing a new tune when this filthy Tralü chewed up my guitar. Besides, it looks like he got others before me!! Well, back to the lighthouse, otherwise I&apos;ll get in hot water.</text>
	<text id="514">This storm...I wanted to get rid of it but the lighthouse was closed and I can&apos;t find the keeper anywhere. Only he could help me reach the top of the building where I have the view I need to utter a conjuration. It&apos;s the only way to stop this storm that neutralizes the island. But I need the lighthouse keeper.</text>
	<text id="515">Please, don&apos;t touch the container on the stove. OK? It contains a terrible creature!</text>
	<text id="516">Hmm...er... don&apos;t mention it please, it&apos;s only... well just a kind of a small personal experiment.</text>
	<text id="517">Don&apos;t touch that! I &apos;m trying to create an enchanted ring and this pot must not boil. Once I get myself an pearl of incandescence, I &apos;ll be able to call the lightning!</text>
	<text id="518">I just bumped into the keeper who was going back to the lighthouse. He told me that a true hero had just saved him from a voracious monster.</text>
	<text id="519">Bravo! And now, if you appreciate Great Art, let&apos;s meet at the lighthouse. You&apos;ll see what you&apos;ll see!</text>
	<text id="520">Ah yes! It is on Desert Island. You&apos;ll find it easely, the entry is inside the cemetery !</text>
	<text id="521">Follow me!</text>
	<text id="522">Unbelievable, this whole extratwinsunians scare. The storm I chased off has let them land here among us. The second I have less work on my hands, I&apos;ll have to go see what they&apos;re up to.</text>
	<text id="523">Ah! No!!</text>
	<text id="524">Twinsen, rush to the downtown pharmacy and find a cure for the Dino-Fly ! He has just crashed in the garden and looks injured.</text>
	<text id="525">&quot;Zoé&apos;s diary @ @ Dear diary: Today, I tell you the story of the Adventure that I had with Twinsen under the dictatorship of Dr. FunFrock: @ It was long, long ago. This Dr. FunFrock, a quetch, was oppressing the populace with terrible violence thanks to the techniques of cloning and mutation, but mostly through his mastery of teleportation. His power dominated everyone! He even had the northern hemisphere evacuated in order to execute his plan. This plan consisted of a gigantic drilling operation aimed at reaching the heart of Twinsun and grabbing the magic energy of the Sendells. Without the providential intervention of Twinsen who eliminated FunFrock, this demented project would have resulted in the implosion of the planet and the destruction of the Stellar Entity living in its center. @ Twinsen had hardly practiced Magic since this &quot;Day of Triumph&quot;, when Sendell exceptionally entrusted him with his immense Power ...&quot; @</text>
	<text id="526">I am going to see the Dino-Fly, it just landed behind the house. Don&apos;t forget that you can change the perspective by pressing &quot;ENTER&quot;.</text>
	<text id="527">Twinsen, what are you doing? I am counting on you to take care of the Dino-Fly, and milord is seeking adventures in the underground instead. It&apos;s beyond your control, you have to play the hero!</text>
	<text id="528">Not through there.</text>
	<text id="529">No, not through there. First Let&apos;s go over to the lighthouse and visit the Weather Wizard.</text>
	<text id="530">I don&apos;t know where he is. Try the lighthouse.</text>
	<text id="531">We are so happy you know. It&apos;s our first and it should come anytime now.</text>
	<text id="532">By the way, would you be kind enough to go to Baldino&apos;s? I am missing a part for the car.</text>
	<text id="533">Twinsen, I met that nice lady who works for Ker&apos;aooc, the healing wizard. She said he knows how to cure the Dino-Fly. He lives on the Desert Island. You should go see him.</text>
	<text id="534">Gee, thanks, Twinsen! Now I&apos;ll be able to finish up the car. Oh, Baldino called recently -- he says he forgot to give you a portable radio and he wants you to come by to pick it up.</text>
	<text id="535">I&apos;m worried, Twinsen. These visitors from the sky look weird to me. They act almost too friendly. And get this, I&apos;ve seen some of them hide in the garbage cans.</text>
	<text id="536">Hello! Twinsen ! Zoé here! Come quickly to the house, some very strange things are going on!!</text>
	<text id="537">Ah Twinsen, you are here! It&apos;s horrible. The Esmers have kidnapped the children aboard a shuttle. Nobody knows where they are or how to find them!! You have to go look for them!</text>
	<text id="538">No, Baldino left a little earlier for the emerald moon, where he&apos;d noticed something was wrong. He left the proto-pack in working order downtown at the baggage claim, where you can pick it up.</text>
	<text id="539">You should go to the school of magic. Now that you&apos;re a wizard, they can probably help you!</text>
	<text id="540">Twinsen, did you see the dean of the school of magic?</text>
	<text id="541">Twinsen, did you find the children&apos;s trail?</text>
	<text id="542">Bravo!!</text>
	<text id="543">Twinsen, did you find the healing wizard?</text>
	<text id="544">Tell me Twinsen , did you find something to cure the Dino-Fly?</text>
	<text id="545">Twinsen, is that it, you have become a wizard?!</text>
	<text id="546">Twinsen, as soon as I fix the car, I&apos;ll call you on the walkie-talkie!</text>
	<text id="547">By the way, did you pick up the portable radio at Baldino&apos;s?</text>
	<text id="548">Hello! Twinsen? Baldino here! How are you? Looks like this transmitter works! If you swing by, I have a portable radio to give you. Also, I will have the proto-pack finished soon. It will allow you to fly in complete safety. Over.</text>
	<text id="549">Twinsen, I am on Emerald Moon. I have uncovered a diabolical plot organized by the Esmers!! The kidnapping of the wizards and the children was only a small part of their plan. They are about to destroy our planet!!! Listen Twinsen, you must meet me!!</text>
	<text id="550">The Esmers have set up a base somewhere on Desert Island. Find it and steal a shuttle!! You are the only one who can save Twinsun!!!</text>
	<text id="551">I&apos;ve got enough problems without you touching stuff...so get lost!</text>
	<text id="552">Ouch!</text>
	<text id="553">Pfew, I&apos;m totally exhausted moving all these crates.</text>
	<text id="554">Hey mister! If you want, I can carry your crate up to the exit for 102 little Kashes!</text>
	<text id="555">Go back upstairs. You&apos;ll get your crate, I&apos;m sending it directly to the reception!</text>
	<text id="556">Hi, Twinsen. With this storm, I&apos;ve got lots of customers and I don&apos;t have one minute to myself.</text>
	<text id="557">I don&apos;t have the time, Twinsen. Ask Luc, the boss!</text>
	<text id="558">Thief!</text>
	<text id="559">Thank you!</text>
	<text id="560">Twinsen, you have no business being here!</text>
	<text id="561">What a story, those guys showing up from the Emerald Moon, what a story!</text>
	<text id="562">If you are lost, go back and get your holomap.</text>
	<text id="563">If you want Life or Magic points, you can get some from one of the vending machines on the bar.</text>
	<text id="564">Better ask his buddies Pat or Fab. They&apos;re upstairs. Haven&apos;t moved since it started raining.</text>
	<text id="565">Hello, Twinsen my friend.</text>
	<text id="566">Howdy kiddo! How goes it?</text>
	<text id="567">He said he wanted to practice a new piece on his guitar. He usually hides out on the cliffs for peace and quiet. But not this long usually.</text>
	<text id="568">Thanks for having freed my buddy Raph, kiddo. Without you, his goose was cooked for sure.</text>
	<text id="569">These &quot;Esmers&quot; look quite nice, they ask lots of questions though. Everything interests them.</text>
	<text id="570">Waiter!</text>
	<text id="571">Cool!! That music rocks! Don&apos;t you think?</text>
	<text id="572">Raph? With him and Fab, we put together a killer combo to play some funky rock&apos;n rave! But since he didn&apos;t show at the last rehearsal, no way I can tell you where he is now!</text>
	<text id="573">It&apos;s great that our buddy Raph is back at the lighthouse. But the arrival of these space aliens, that&apos;s some thin-I-never-seen-before.</text>
	<text id="574">I sure dig those &quot;extra-twinsunians&quot;. Their civilization is more advanced than ours, but they are still way cool.</text>
	<text id="575">Hey!, we need some music here!</text>
	<text id="576">If you go to the cellar, be [hic!]... be careful! I been there my own self... just to get in a couple snorts on the sly: well there&apos;s a [hic!] there&apos;s a hole smack in the middle. Yessir, smack in the middle! Oh, that falllll, yowza!</text>
	<text id="577">Darn, I had seen some pink grobos before, but green chaps from outer space, that&apos;s a first!</text>
	<text id="578">Waiter!</text>
	<text id="579">Not being from here, I find your island rather strange. I don&apos;t understand why your Weather Wizard does nothing about this storm. By the way, do you know that it&apos;s possible to search the garbage cans, the vases and the closets by standing in front of them and doing &quot;ACTION&quot;?</text>
	<text id="580">Sorry, I am not from here.</text>
	<text id="581">Waiter!</text>
	<text id="582">Sorry, but I don&apos;t have anything for a Dino-Fly.</text>
	<text id="583">Personally, I have nothing for your Dino-Fly, but the client said she could help you.</text>
	<text id="584">If you are interested in an item, stand in front of it and do &quot;ACTION&quot;.</text>
	<text id="585">Don&apos;t touch my cash register!</text>
	<text id="586">You know, even though he is my brother, I don&apos;t give a hoot about his whereabouts, this lazy bum thinks about nothing but playing his guitar on the cliffs.</text>
	<text id="587">You know, since people are scared, there are only a few shops left open. The Esmers are looking for you, they even had your museum closed down!</text>
	<text id="588">But I have a customer who works for a healing wizard named Ker&apos;aooc. He lives on Desert Island. According to my friend, he treats everybody for everything.</text>
	<text id="589">The foul weather prevents the boats from leaving the harbor. There&apos;s nothing to do, all maritime activity is paralyzed. Let me tell you, Mr. Twinsen, only the Weather Wizard could set things straight!!</text>
	<text id="590">You need a ticket to board the ferry, Mr. Twinsen.</text>
	<text id="591">What?? Very funny!! Now this good-for-nothing abandons the lighthouse right in the middle of the storm! What a shame!!</text>
	<text id="592">Your ticket is in order, Mr. Twinsen, you may board. Have a nice trip!</text>
	<text id="593">By the way, the missus was looking for you. She tells you to go see Ker&apos;aooc, the healing wizard, on Desert island. He knows how to cure your Dino-Fly.</text>
	<text id="594">The Esmers have forbidden all maritime service.. There is nobody left to hop from island to island anyway. They are too scared of the Esmers.</text>
	<text id="595">There is still no maritime service, but I have the impression that there are less Esmers on our island.</text>
	<text id="596">Insert 5 Kashes if you want 10 Magic points.</text>
	<text id="597">Insert 5 Kashes if you want 10 Life points.</text>
	<text id="598">Insert 5 Kashes if you want to listen to a title:</text>
	<text id="599">For 3 Kashes, do you want to use the telescope?</text>
	<text id="600">Hi, Twinsen. Far as I&apos;m concerned, I like it when it rains. The grass gets nicely thick. Makes it taste better.</text>
	<text id="601">Yeah, actually I saw him pass by a while back. He was holding his guitar, heading for the cliffs.</text>
	<text id="602">Since the good weather&apos;s back, my bird friends are much less on edge. Oh, and be careful, there&apos;s a weirdo hiding behind the trees.</text>
	<text id="603">People from the planet Twinsun, we come to you in a spirit of peace. @ Thank you for dispersing this storm which prevented us from landing. We have observed your planet for many cycles now and have decided to come and study your culture on the spot. We have traveled through Space solely with the goal of discovering your civilization.</text>
	<text id="604">Greetings, Twinsunian. We are your friends. We come in peace to your planet. We wish only to know you and to share our knowledge with you. @ Have trust in our friendship!</text>
	<text id="605">Greetings, Master. You should go to Desert Island. Towards the hacienda, near the Bald Mountain, we are organizing a little gathering for the wizards. You will probably find it interesting.</text>
	<text id="606">Thank you, Twinsen. Without you, who knows what would have happened to our planets.</text>
	<text id="607">Do not mention it. You have realized our prophecy. Our planet is once again the paradise it was at creation, you have saved Zeelich from the dictatorship that our emperor was preparing, and best of all, by preventing the impostor FunFrock from executing his plans, you have saved both our worlds!!!</text>
	<text id="608">Hello Twinsen!</text>
	<text id="609">I am updating the works of my defunct son. Certain plans here date back from the time when he rebuilt the island&apos;s network of sewers.</text>
	<text id="610">Here we have a very instructive map of the sewers. Before you can consult it, you must wait until I restore it. For that, I need a vial of gallic acid. Unfortunately, there&apos;s none left on the island.</text>
	<text id="611">Yes, that&apos;s exactly what I needed. I am going to use it on the map of the sewers.</text>
	<text id="612">The gallic acid has revealed a text previously invisible. It mentions a small pyramid that was in my possession. Here! It&apos;s yours!</text>
	<text id="613">Ah yes, the pharmacist&apos;s younger brother. No, I don&apos;t know where he is.</text>
	<text id="614">I&apos;m still busy with my son&apos;s documents here. Everybody seems to be terrorized by these few costumed strangers. At my age, one has seen worse!!</text>
	<text id="615">Thanks again for your help, Twinsen. These maps begin to make sense. You should look at them, they talk of things that would interest you.</text>
	<text id="616">Hello Mr. Twinsen.</text>
	<text id="617">This rain, will it ever end! Between my kids who were supposed to go on a field trip and my oldest son who keeps forgetting his umbrella...I hope that they&apos;re not outside in this weather.</text>
	<text id="618">Personally, I don&apos;t know where he is, but go look at the pharmacy. His sister might be able to help you.</text>
	<text id="619">The weather&apos;s improving. Now the kids can go on their class outing.</text>
	<text id="620">Welcome to the Inter-islands Ferry, Mr. Twinsen!</text>
	<text id="621">You can board as soon as the storm is over.</text>
	<text id="622">Why don&apos;t you read the posters. And if you are interested in a destination, you tell me.</text>
	<text id="623">What can I do for you?</text>
	<text id="624">For 10 Kashes, wher...where do you want to go?</text>
	<text id="625">Last time I saw him, he was hanging around in town.</text>
	<text id="626">Sorry sir, our ferries do not serve that island.</text>
	<text id="627">If you&apos;d care to purchase something, you just have to stand in front of it and do &quot;ACTION&quot;.</text>
	<text id="628">A Nitro-Meca-Penguin costs 4 Kashes.</text>
	<text id="629">I heard he likes to &quot;seek inspiration&quot; by &quot;The Cliffs of the Woodbridge&quot;. That place is dangerous, if half of what I&apos;ve heard about the Tralü&apos;s for real. Don&apos;t go if you are unarmed.</text>
	<text id="630">A holomap costs 10 kashes.</text>
	<text id="631">Three darts cost 4 Kashes.</text>
	<text id="632">Don&apos;t do that, you fool, it&apos;s going to blow up!</text>
	<text id="633">Nobody touches the cash register!</text>
	<text id="634">Welcome, Mr. Twinsen!</text>
	<text id="635">You&apos;ve seen the visitors. They are Esmers. Supposedly, they&apos;re peaceloving and just want to trade us their technology for some of the wisdom of our wizards.</text>
	<text id="636">Oh what a fall, I&apos;m hurt badly. Under normal conditions, I could have taken you for a spin in the air. But this time, you will have to treat me first.</text>
	<text id="637">Oh! I don&apos;t know where he is. But if he&apos;d done his job, I&apos;d have seen his light and wouldn&apos;t have crashed.</text>
	<text id="638">Aahhh, thank you! I think I can fly now and take you where you want.</text>
	<text id="639">Where do you want to go, Twinsen?</text>
	<text id="640">Twinsen ! Did you see Zoé? She is looking for you everywhere! She has something very important to tell you!!</text>
	<text id="641">That alien jalopy&apos;s easy on the eyes, but it looks difficult to park.</text>
	<text id="642">I don&apos;t take anybody in the storm, I hate this weather. And why doesn&apos;t the Weather Wizard intervene, heh? By the way, did you notice that you could jump while you are running?</text>
	<text id="643">Mmm, it&apos;s been a while since I last saw him. Not surprising with this blasted storm!!</text>
	<text id="644">So, for 8 Kashes, where do I drop you?</text>
	<text id="645">Hang on!</text>
	<text id="646">I just can&apos;t believe these visitors coming from another planet, let alone just to offer us their technology! I hope they are not going to start competing with me ...</text>
	<text id="647">Ouch!!!!</text>
	<text id="648">I don&apos;t talk to nutcases, Mr. Twinsen!!</text>
	<text id="649">What a pain these sewers! What a stink and I still have oodles of manhole covers to update. Phew!! I have had it up to here!!</text>
	<text id="650">Well, I am certain he is not in the sewers, I would have seen him.</text>
	<text id="651">Hello.</text>
	<text id="652">But I have an idea how you can help your friend!</text>
	<text id="653">Thief!</text>
	<text id="654">Here&apos;s the deal. I will tell you how to treat your Dino-Fly, if you would bring back my umbrella. Use your smarts but remember that, in life, haste makes waste...</text>
	<text id="655">Ah you are so kind. Go see Ker&apos;aooc the healer on my behalf on Desert Island. I work for him and, believe me, he knows tricks that would cure anything, even a Dino-Fly...</text>
	<text id="656">I don&apos;t know. I live on Desert Island.</text>
	<text id="657">I don&apos;t understand why the lighthouse is closed and turned off. What could my fiancé Raph, be doing? By the way, Mr. Twinsen, did you know you can jump over the rocks if you are trapped ?</text>
	<text id="658">Infortunately, he&apos;s disappeared, Mr. Twinsen! I hope he hasn&apos;t gone on another of his strolls on the cliffs! One of these days it might be nasty, with all these rumors about the Tralü...</text>
	<text id="659">My pretty bunny has come back, thanks to you!! Oh thank you, Mr. Twinsen!!</text>
	<text id="660">Ohhh...I am definitely getting too old for these acrobatics!</text>
	<text id="661">Now then, meet me at the School of Magic. I&apos;ve got a surprise for you.</text>
	<text id="662">Twinsen, your performance was exemplary; here&apos;s your reward, this slate. It allows you to memorize images that you see, such as maps.</text>
	<text id="663">Mr. Twinsen! Could you tell me why you&apos;re following me?!</text>
	<text id="664">But that&apos;s my umb... Oh !!! Excuse me... I thought it was mine. Boohooo, I&apos;m so embarrassed... I keep making mistakes...</text>
	<text id="665">But, Mr. Twinsen, I assure you that I don&apos;t have your tunic. Maybe you should look at home.</text>
	<text id="666">Help!!</text>
	<text id="667">Raph ? Ah yeah, he has set up a super combo with his buddies Pat and Fab. But I don&apos;t know where he is.</text>
	<text id="668">Not again. What do you want from me now, Mr. Twinsen?</text>
	<text id="669">Greetings, Twinsunian. We are your friends. We come in peace to your planet. We only wish to know you and to share our knowledge with you. @ Have trust in our friendship.</text>
	<text id="670">Greetings, Master. You should go to Desert Island. Towards the hacienda, near the Bald Mountain, we are organizing a little gathering for the wizards. You will certainly be interested should you choose to attend.</text>
	<text id="671">Greetings, Twinsunian. We are your friends. We come in peace to your planet. We only wish to know you and to share our knowledge with you. @ Have trust in our friendship.</text>
	<text id="672">Greetings, Master. You should go to Desert Island. Towards the hacienda, near the Bald Mountain, we are organizing a little gathering for the wizards. You will certainly be interested should you choose to attend.</text>
	<text id="673">Hi Mr. Twinsen!</text>
	<text id="674">No school for me today. I&apos;d love to find the Tralü and do it in. &apos;Cause if I make the Tralü disappear, I&apos;ll become a hero and they will erect me a whole museum!!</text>
	<text id="675">I don&apos;t know where he is, but his buddies are at the pub &quot;Chez Luc&quot;.</text>
	<text id="676">Did you see those weirdoes from the sky? Mebbe they&apos;re some of the Tralü&apos;s buddies!</text>
	<text id="677">Why the disguise? You scared of getting caught by the Tralü&apos;s buddies?</text>
	<text id="678">Waaah!!!</text>
	<text id="679">Say Twinsen, did you ever see that Tralü? They say it&apos;s a monster that lives in the cliffs above Lupin-Bourg. If you take a walk up there, don&apos;t forget to carry a weapon. I mean your magic ball!</text>
	<text id="680">I don&apos;t know him very well, but try asking around at &quot;Chez Luc,&quot; that&apos;s his big hangout.</text>
	<text id="681">Hey, did you really destroy the Tralü? This monster really existed? Hail to you, may you be prosperous and may the Sendells protect your descendants!</text>
	<text id="682">I&apos;d like to take the kids to the &quot;Flowers Circle&quot;, but the weather&apos;s just too bad.</text>
	<text id="683">I don&apos;t know where he is, Mr. Twinsen.</text>
	<text id="684">Look at that, this place brings out the music in young souls. In fact, they adore Sendell.</text>
	<text id="685">Brute!</text>
	<text id="686">Hello, Mr. Twinsen!</text>
	<text id="687">[Sniff]...the children...we were at the &quot;Flowers Circle&quot; [sniff]...suddenly one of those alien ships showed up right overhead. There was this big white flash, and then...nothing. Next thing I remember, I found myself alone, the children nowhere in sight, and the ship was taking off. It&apos;s horrible, Mr. Twinsen! You have to find them! You have to!</text>
	<text id="688">[Sniff]...thank you, Mr. Twinsen, [sniff]...</text>
	<text id="689">Oh, hey, Twinsen. Did you check out my essay on my future plans? Here, I will summarize: Phase 1) Grow up. Phase 2) Become a sailor! And Phase 3) Buy a million umbrellas for my brother.</text>
	<text id="690">I don&apos;t know where he might be, but I&apos;ve always liked him, that Raph. Once he even had me over to the lighthouse. The view was impressive!</text>
	<text id="691">I think after my big brother cleans your clock, you won&apos;t act like such a big shot.</text>
	<text id="692">&quot; It&apos;s Sendell which makes her nest @ In the heart of the planet @ Sendell does her magic well @ But it might make your head swell @ Sendell is the prettiest @ FunFrock is a dirty beast.&quot;</text>
	<text id="693">Hi there, Mr. Twinsen ! Listen to our new nursery rhyme!!</text>
	<text id="694">&quot; It&apos;s Sendell which makes her nest @ In the heart of the planet @ Sendell does her magic well @ But it might make your head swell @ Sendell is the prettiest @ FunFrock is a dirty beast.&quot;</text>
	<text id="695">Never heard it.</text>
	<text id="696">I&apos;ll tell my big brother, he&apos;ll beat you up while I laugh, and that&apos;ll show you!</text>
	<text id="697">Nice to see you, Twinsen ! This storm really chaps my hide. I just can&apos;t calm down... And you, don&apos;t forget that you can change your behavior.</text>
	<text id="698">Ah, he&apos;s disappeared?! Oh, well, I never really liked him! May the Tralü take him away!!</text>
	<text id="699">So Twinsen, this li&apos;l monster, coming soon?</text>
	<text id="700">What&apos;s up with these Esmers? Couldn&apos;t they have stayed home?</text>
	<text id="701">Since the weather outside is horrible, the teacher said I could jump rope in the classroom. See?</text>
	<text id="702">Ow! My big brother&apos;s gonna take care of you.</text>
	<text id="703">Oh yeah, I know him, he&apos;s the one always playing his guitar!!</text>
	<text id="704">&quot; It&apos;s Sendell which makes her nest @ In the heart of the planet @ Sendell does her magic well @ But it might make your head swell @ Sendell is the prettiest @ FunFrock is a dirty beast.&quot;</text>
	<text id="705">H&apos;lo, Mr. Twinsen. I&apos;m being punished &apos;cause I ate a whole box of chalk.</text>
	<text id="706">I can&apos;t help you, Mr. Twinsen.</text>
	<text id="707">Don&apos;t care, not at all! But my big brother, he&apos;ll avenge me.</text>
	<text id="708">&quot; It&apos;s Sendell which makes her nest @ In the heart of the planet @ Sendell does her magic well @ But it might make your head swell @ Sendell is the prettiest @ FunFrock is a dirty beast.&quot;</text>
	<text id="709">The pharmacist, she is so pretty! I don&apos;t know what else to buy in order to see her. One day I ... I&apos;ll dare talk to her.</text>
	<text id="710">My eyes see no one else but the pharmacist, my heart beats for nobody but her. If I dared, I&apos;d scale the cliffs to fetch her the music I have often heard over there.</text>
	<text id="711">And now, with these aliens showing up in their big fancy ships, there&apos;s no way she&apos;ll notice me, my beloved pharmacist...</text>
	<text id="712">Ah Twinsen, with this rain, I found plenty of mushrooms!</text>
	<text id="713">Last time I heard him play his guitar, he was probably on the Cliffs. I was looking for mushrooms at that time.</text>
	<text id="714">The Esmers should come here. It feels so good to look for mushrooms. By the way, I wouldn&apos;t try to go swimming, it gets deep very rapidly.</text>
	<text id="715">I had hidden in the shuttle when you left the planet of the strange people. But now, I would like to go back. We left the wizards all alone up there, and they must be getting bored stiff.</text>
	<text id="716">&quot;No thanks, seems to be OK now...&quot;</text>
	<text id="717">Hooooo !!!</text>
	<text id="718">Unused</text>
	<text id="719">OK by me!</text>
	<text id="720">I&apos;m not interested.</text>
	<text id="721">I would like to treat my Dino-fly first!</text>
	<text id="722">Looking for a costume or Magic accessories? Well, Chedil Amiradoo has a deal that&apos;ll make your head spin. Low, low prices and after-sales service. Currently doing the rounds on your island.</text>
	<text id="723">&quot;Qwelt ik M?lg&apos;b - ~oc  ~&apos;c # %-) ~Big TsS-steel-jenr, (dulkug) hanfin tuwouah koa xdocd &quot; ö&quot;</text>
	<text id="724">Disappeared?? Master, this is grave news. I&apos;ll do all in my power to find them. Trust me!!</text>
	<text id="725">&quot;Learning also means completing old problems with new methods.&quot;</text>
	<text id="726">&quot;Honor roll of most recent wizard graduates: Aril van Koow, Hougo Dolphar, Carnogeel.&quot;</text>
	<text id="727">What should I do, Master?</text>
	<text id="728">Hey, Jerome.</text>
	<text id="729">&quot;Visit Temple-Park. Just one step from Bald Mountain, relive a pivotal episode in Twinsun&apos;s glorious history by exploring the Temple of Bù.&quot;</text>
	<text id="730">&quot;Jerome Baldino. @ Miscellaneous Gadgets  Inventions.&quot;</text>
	<text id="731">&quot;Von Kournil tour. @ (Island of the White Leaf Desert) &quot;</text>
	<text id="732">&quot;Port-Ludo @ (Island of the White Leaf Desert). &quot;</text>
	<text id="733">&quot;You are at the harbor @ (Island of the White Leaf Desert). &quot;</text>
	<text id="734">&quot;To the harbor.&quot;</text>
	<text id="735">&quot;To the Temple of Bù.&quot;</text>
	<text id="736">&quot;To the Hacienda del Monte-Pelado.&quot;</text>
	<text id="737">&quot;You are at Bald Mountain.&quot;</text>
	<text id="738">&quot;To the cemetery.&quot;</text>
	<text id="739">Hello.</text>
	<text id="740">Hi.</text>
	<text id="741">It&apos;s locked.</text>
	<text id="742">Good day, Master</text>
	<text id="743">I don&apos;t have enough Kashes.</text>
	<text id="744">I am looking for the healing wizard, I must treat my Dino-Fly.</text>
	<text id="745">Do you happen to know where he lives?</text>
	<text id="746">But... the healing wizard!!</text>
	<text id="747">I&apos;m trying to find the school of magic.</text>
	<text id="748">Do you know where to find the school of magic?</text>
	<text id="749">Did you see a wizard walk this way recently?</text>
	<text id="750">Do you know where the wizards are?</text>
	<text id="751">&quot;Honor roll of most recent wizard graduates: Aril van Koow, Hougo Dolphar, Carnogeel, Twinsen.&quot;</text>
	<text id="752">Hello?</text>
	<text id="753">Master, the children of Twinsun have been kidnapped by the Esmers. Can you help? Maybe a spell to help us know where they were taken?</text>
	<text id="754">Where could I find it?</text>
	<text id="755">I read a message from the Weather Wizard. He needs a pearl of incandescence to finish his lightning spell. Where can I get one?</text>
	<text id="756">Master, I found a strange pearl in a cave, not far from Port-Ludo.</text>
	<text id="757">Citadel Island.</text>
	<text id="758">The island of the Dome of the Slate.</text>
	<text id="759">I&apos;m staying here.</text>
	<text id="760">The island across from the Hacienda.</text>
	<text id="761">The oasis in the desert.</text>
	<text id="762">I don&apos;t know what Jerome&apos;s cooking up, but there&apos;s a demonic machine under there.</text>
	<text id="763">It seems Baldino is working on the proto-pack, maybe he&apos;s trying to improve it?</text>
	<text id="764">Hmmm,. these must be the plans for the machine that was hidden under that tarp. Baldino must have used it to get to Emerald Moon.</text>
	<text id="765">You are at Temple Park, the ancient site of the Temple of Bù.</text>
	<text id="766">&quot;You are at the Hacienda del Monte-Pelado.&quot;</text>
	<text id="767">I happen to be looking for him.</text>
	<text id="768">Do you know where the wizards could be?</text>
	<text id="769">Where are you taking me, Moya?</text>
	<text id="770">I didn&apos;t know about this cave.</text>
	<text id="771">Citadel Island.</text>
	<text id="772">The Dome of the Slate.</text>
	<text id="773">I&apos;m staying here.</text>
	<text id="774">Another tourist minibus. Man, that Temple of Bù really packs &apos;em in!</text>
	<text id="775">Aha! a sign from Sendell. They are venerated by all the wizards.</text>
	<text id="776">No, not yet.</text>
	<text id="777">No, I have to find the school of magic.</text>
	<text id="778">By passing the school&apos;s magic tests, I&apos;ve gotten this horn to help me treat Dino-Fly.</text>
	<text id="779">I&apos;ve decided to become a wizard so that I can treat Dino-Fly myself.</text>
	<text id="780">He gave it to me already. I&apos;ll bring it over to you.</text>
	<text id="781">They claim to be peaceful... but let&apos;s be careful, they look sort of aggressive to me.</text>
	<text id="782">Master, I figured out why the wizards disappeared. The Esmers invited them over to their planet for some kind of cultural and scientific exchange. I wonder what that&apos;s all about...</text>
	<text id="783">ER ioergouerg - erioufmqer o-u tu zejkhze jkhqdsqdsl iklds klqdfjn !!</text>
	<text id="784">OFFICIAL NOTICE ... all shuttles going to the moon base... new password... without which the soldiers will intervene... operation GREEN MOON !!</text>
	<text id="785">There&apos;s a piece missing here, something disc-shaped. I guess it allows the shuttle to take off.</text>
	<text id="786">Hello? Twinsen? That&apos;s it, I fixed the car... You should give it a whirl... I&apos;m bringing it to Desert Island...</text>
	<text id="787">Twinsen, if you want to try out the car, just go to the racetrack or the desert. As long as I&apos;m here, I&apos;m going to catch up on a little shopping. I&apos;ll meet you back at the house.</text>
	<text id="788">Twinsen, Did you find the healing wizard?</text>
	<text id="789">Well Twinsen , did you find something to treat the Dino-Fly?</text>
	<text id="790">By the way, could you ask Baldino for the car-part he promised me?</text>
	<text id="791">I&apos;m worried sick, Twinsen. These space visitors look pretty spooky, and their niceness seems...I don&apos;t know, phony? Did I mention I&apos;ve seen some of them hiding in garbage cans?</text>
	<text id="792">Here! Here&apos;s the part that Zoé needs for your car.</text>
	<text id="793">Here, this is that portable radio I forgot to give you. Sorry about the mixup, but I think you&apos;ll agree it was worth waiting for!</text>
	<text id="794">Hello, Twinsen.</text>
	<text id="795">I could&apos;ve called it an &quot;integrated super dynamo circuitry mechanism&quot; but I decided to go with &quot;portable radio&quot;. A little catchier, huh? Incidentally, I&apos;ll let you know when the Proto-Pack is ready, it&apos;ll let you fly around in complete safety.</text>
	<text id="796">In spite of my powerful telescope, I saw only a couple of flying saucers pass behind the Moon. The Esmers must live on the hidden side.</text>
	<text id="797">Good day, Master, but... is that you Twinsen? You look terrific as a wizard, congratulations.</text>
	<text id="798">I never realized there was an actual School of Magic! I guess I should get out of my shop more often.</text>
	<text id="799">I don&apos;t know where they are, Twinsen.</text>
	<text id="800">You need a ticket to board the ferry there, Mr. Twinsen.</text>
	<text id="801">Your ticket&apos;s in order, Mr. Twinsen, you may board. Have a nice trip!</text>
	<text id="802">You may board, Master.</text>
	<text id="803">&quot;Do you want to use the telescope for 2 Kashes?&quot;</text>
	<text id="804">Now that the clouds are gone, I can finally enjoy our twin sunshine. You know, I heard there&apos;s an oasis in the desert where there&apos;s this giant turtle. I&apos;d love to go there...</text>
	<text id="805">A School of Magic? Do you think they might need an assistant?</text>
	<text id="806">No, I fell asleep in the sun, I didn&apos;t see any wizard.</text>
	<text id="807">Where do you want to go, Twinsen?</text>
	<text id="808">You know, I wonder if they might have brought her around, actually...What with all the wizards and Esmers hanging around the Hacienda these days...</text>
	<text id="809">I love these visitors from the sky. After the sewers of Citadel Island, I was to repaint the steambath. But, to celebrate their arrival, they bought plenty of drinks!!! Not only for me, but also for the wizards who drop in here.</text>
	<text id="810">Well well! Hello, mister Twinsen!</text>
	<text id="811">Yep!</text>
	<text id="812">For sure. Carousing with a bunch of Esmers...By the way, I wonder where they all went.</text>
	<text id="813">Sorry, but I&apos;ve forbidden roof access since my colleague from Citadel Island had legal issues with a customer who took a bad dive in the cellar of his bar!</text>
	<text id="814">Well, what&apos;ve you learned?</text>
	<text id="815">Hello, sir.</text>
	<text id="816">Out, quick!</text>
	<text id="817">For some time now, I&apos;ve watched &apos;em pass through my establishment. They all hang around the patio or the steambath. Go take a look.</text>
	<text id="818">These Esmers are pretty chummy, buying drinks for everybody. They even buy them for the wizards. I still keep an eye on the women&apos;s steambath, though... The first one who goes in there will have to deal with me!!</text>
	<text id="819">It&apos;s depressing. There&apos;s nobody left, so obviously business is down. Then the Esmers come and shut my Turkish bath down. I don&apos;t get it!</text>
	<text id="820">Unbelievable, the Esmers think they own the place. Their space shuttles come and go through Bald Mountain, it&apos;s like they have an anthill underneath!!</text>
	<text id="821">Ah no, I didn&apos;t even know there was one on this island!</text>
	<text id="822">There is a top secret exchange program, currently reserved for the wizards. Come discover our science and civilization, and show us your Magic in return. You&apos;ll get rich in knowledge and experience. Don&apos;t mention it to your School of Magic yet, it&apos;s too early ... they would not understand.</text>
	<text id="823">Are you ready to come and spend some time on our planet?</text>
	<text id="824">Greetings, Twinsunian. We are your friends. We come in peace to your planet. We only wish to know you and to share our knowledge with you. @ Have trust in our friendship!</text>
	<text id="825">My master often goes to get sand roses for me. I love munching them. They&apos;re so crunchy!</text>
	<text id="826">I don&apos;t know Twinsen, I don&apos;t live here. I was just imported.</text>
	<text id="827">I saw one go by a while ago. I think he was looking for sand roses.</text>
	<text id="828">Howdy.</text>
	<text id="829">Phew, it&apos;s hot but it feels so wonderful!</text>
	<text id="830">A School of Magic? Is that for real? At any rate, it&apos;s not here. I come here everyday, I should know.</text>
	<text id="831">I&apos;ve seen some pass by, quite a few frankly. But they all disappear before I can figure out where they&apos;re going.</text>
	<text id="832">Ah thank you. I don&apos;t need it anymore, but it was kind of you to bring it back.</text>
	<text id="833">You can borrow this vial, I don&apos;t think Master Ker&apos;aooc has much use for it.</text>
	<text id="834">Only the wizards and the initiated know her whereabouts. All I know is that she went into hiding somewhere on the island.</text>
	<text id="835">All I know is that the wizard Ker&apos;aooc has gone on a trip with some of his colleagues. It&apos;s the Esmers who invited him!!</text>
	<text id="836">Hello sir.</text>
	<text id="837">Oh, that&apos;s you! Hi!</text>
	<text id="838">I am a little worried, you know. Since he left, Wizard Ker&apos;aooc has not sent any sign of life. I don&apos;t like what&apos;s going on, this is not his habit.</text>
	<text id="839">I hope that the Wizard Ker&apos;aooc will come back soon. I don&apos;t feel safe with all these Esmers patrolling the streets.</text>
	<text id="840">I&apos;m sorry that the healer Ker&apos;aooc is away. When he&apos;ll be back is anyone&apos;s guess. If it&apos;s an emergency, try the School of Magic.</text>
	<text id="841">Your reputation has hopped from island to island to reach me, Twinsen. You are the hero of this planet and you must know that the Esmers invite the wizards to come and study their planet of origin. Watch out, there&apos;s something fishy.</text>
	<text id="842">It&apos;s in the desert. The entrance is in a cemetery to scare off strangers.</text>
	<text id="843">Whoever wants to know has to go and see! Now, you must fulfill your destiny, my young hero.</text>
	<text id="844">Hello to you, Twinsen !</text>
	<text id="845">For some time now, I&apos;ve been observing inexplicable goings-on here. But it&apos;s too soon to be sure.</text>
	<text id="846">Hi Twinsen. If you want to see Moya the turtle, you may find her at the small oasis or on the other side of the harbor. To call her, just ring the bell.</text>
	<text id="847">Sorry, can&apos;t help you. The only story about magic that I know is the one about a rabbibunny that got turned into a shell!</text>
	<text id="848">The visitors who come from the sky are weird. I heard them invite some wizards to their planet.</text>
	<text id="849">The aliens have finally shown their true faces. Everybody&apos;s terrified of them.</text>
	<text id="850">My friends the moles told me that all the Esmers were gathering underground.</text>
	<text id="851">My dear sir, my goods are only available to fully licensed wizards.</text>
	<text id="852">Ah, you must be Twinsen. Congratulations for passing your examination. If you want a magician&apos;s tunic it&apos;ll only cost you 50 kashes. We&apos;ll throw in a false beard to make you look like an old magician. Interested?</text>
	<text id="853">Now that you are a wizard, I can sell you some orange powder. It costs 10 Kashes, and will recharge you in Magic and Life Points.</text>
	<text id="854">Hey!! You nuts?</text>
	<text id="855">Hello!</text>
	<text id="856">I know where it is, but I don&apos;t have the right to tell you.</text>
	<text id="857">I saw Ker&apos;aooc pass by a while back. Told me the Esmers had invited him...someplace or other. Regardless, he was going to the Hacienda.</text>
	<text id="858">Welcome, Twinsen. I&apos;d be honored to have you study with us. But even though you once saved our world, you&apos;ll still have to pass the same tests as the other students.</text>
	<text id="859">Do you wish to join our school?</text>
	<text id="860">Inscription fee is 120 Kashes. Are you ready to start right away?</text>
	<text id="861">You&apos;ll obtain the power to heal by passing one of the tests of wizardry. But first you have to enroll. Upon graduation, you get an additional level of magic!</text>
	<text id="862">You are now a member of our school.</text>
	<text id="863">To become a wizard, you must first pass 3 tests, in any order you wish.</text>
	<text id="864">You can bring me the result of each test at your leisure, but I will give you your wizard&apos;s diploma and your new level of magic only after you succeed in all 3 tests!!</text>
	<text id="865">Once you pass through this door, you will have to be both fast and accurate. Stand in the middle of the room and, with the help of your ball, reverse all the magic symbols.</text>
	<text id="866">Try again, Twinsen.</text>
	<text id="867">Mmm, I love the smell of Garden Balsam. Anyway, in exchange for the flower, here&apos;s the Horn of the Blue Triton. It&apos;ll make you a Healer.</text>
	<text id="868">You still have two tests to pass.</text>
	<text id="869">You still have one test to pass before you become a wizard.</text>
	<text id="870">Bravo Twinsen, you have earned this blowgun. It provides accurate and rapid shots.</text>
	<text id="871">Bravo Twinsen. You now bear the title of wizard. @ I don&apos;t have any spare wizard&apos;s parade tunics left. But there is a peddler on the island. I&apos;ll contact him and ask him to give you one. Go find him. Also, let your beard grow.</text>
	<text id="872">Listen to me, I must inform you of some very concerning news. Almost all the wizards of Twinsun have disappeared, and no one knows where they are. They must be found, and you are the only one who can accomplish this noble task. The school is counting on you Twinsen!</text>
	<text id="873">You have to find a peddler who lives on this island. I advised him to provide you with a hat and your wizard&apos;s parade tunic.</text>
	<text id="874">Ah, only the wizards are able to read this.</text>
	<text id="875">That&apos;s strange that the school does not know... I don&apos;t like it. Without wizards, Twinsun is not safe. You must go find them, Twinsen!!</text>
	<text id="876">To practice for your Blowgun Test, simply go through this door at the back of this room. You&apos;ll then have a limited time to shoot all the targets.</text>
	<text id="877">For the Test of the Slate, you must first go to the island called the Dome of the Slate, a stone&apos;s throw away from Citadel Island.</text>
	<text id="878">The wizards -- did you find any trace of them? The people talk of nothing but these Esmer visitors, but this mysterious disappearance is most grim. Without them, Twinsun&apos;s balance and safety are threatened!</text>
	<text id="879">For the Test of the Balsam, you&apos;ll have to fetch me a balsam! It&apos;s a rare plant which grows in the desert.</text>
	<text id="880">No. Twinsen, only you can save them. But before you confront the Esmers, you will have to reinforce your powers. And only the Ball of Sendell can accomplish this.</text>
	<text id="881">Shortly after FunFrock&apos;s disappearance, it was hidden on Citadel Island by the Weather Wizard. He placed it in a cage of ice which he then bound with a powerful spell. According to him, only the power of lightning is capable of freeing the ball.</text>
	<text id="882">There is a giant clam which lives in a marine cave in the cliffs, near Port-Ludo. This creature is host to the pearl of incandescence.</text>
	<text id="883">It is a pearl of incandescence. The Weather Wizard makes use of it for his lightning spell. With it, you could free the Ball of Sendell.</text>
	<text id="884">Have you found the Ball of Sendell? Again, all I know is that it lies on Citadel Island and that only the lightning spell can free it.</text>
	<text id="885">You must go your way, Twinsen. The Esmers begin to be less numerous. It looks like they are gathering by the temple of Bù, you should go take a look.</text>
	<text id="886">Go look at the Temple of Bù. They&apos;re discussing an old treasure still buried there.</text>
	<text id="887">Well done Twinsen. By taking care of this place you&apos;ve enabled new plants to grow. That&apos;s smart thinking for all the magicians who come to pick Balsam will benefit.</text>
	<text id="888">Hello.</text>
	<text id="889">This Turkish bath is too hot for me! Sometimes, it&apos;s so hot that I have hallucinations... I see wizards everywhere!!!</text>
	<text id="890">Nah, but if they&apos;ve got something to lower the temperature of this bath, I&apos;m willing to go see them.</text>
	<text id="891">I don&apos;t know where it is, but it can&apos;t be that far. It&apos;s all wizards and Esmers that pass by here.</text>
	<text id="892">Hello</text>
	<text id="893">Actually I saw one earlier. He was carrying suitcases and heading for the Hacienda. These Esmers make my skin break out. I wonder if they really came in peace.</text>
	<text id="894">No, no idea.</text>
	<text id="895">Well, this climate promotes the growth of this coniferous yellow flower. It&apos;s in high demand among the wizards and it only grows in rocky, hard to reach areas.</text>
	<text id="896">Oh, hi Twinsen ! If you want to take a little sea trip, jump on my back!!</text>
	<text id="897">Sorry Twinsen, but I don&apos;t know where it is.</text>
	<text id="898">Earlier, when I was on the other side of the island, I saw one enter the Hacienda.</text>
	<text id="899">You&apos;ll see ...</text>
	<text id="900">Hi!!!</text>
	<text id="901">These...[hic!] These strangers sure are cool...[hic!] They keep buying us drinks. What a great bunch of guys!! [Hic!!] Right, buddy? [Hic!!]</text>
	<text id="902">Me, I... [hic]... er... I have no i... idea. Beuh, buuut you could try [hic!] old Mr. Wiseguy on the terrace... [Burp!] He knows zunbelievable things!!!</text>
	<text id="903">Yup!!</text>
	<text id="904">Greetings, Twinsunian. We are your friends. We come in peace to your planet. We only wish to know you and to share our knowledge with you. @ Have trust in our friendship!</text>
	<text id="905">Greetings, Twinsunian. We are organizing a gathering for the wizards at the hacienda, near Bald Mountain. If you attend, I think you&apos;ll be very interested.</text>
	<text id="906">Hello!! Allow to me introduce the Grand Rector of the School of Magic!</text>
	<text id="907">A pleasant stay in our magnificent school of magic!!</text>
	<text id="908">Oh, these dreadfully dull Esmers are simply everywhere. Except here, fortunately. I believe they haven&apos;t found the school yet.</text>
	<text id="909">Greetings, Twinsunian. We are your friends. We come in peace to your planet. We only wish to know you and to share our knowledge with you. Have trust in our friendship!</text>
	<text id="910">Greetings, Twinsunian. We are organizing a gathering for the wizards at the hacienda, near Bald Mountain. If you attend, I think you&apos;ll be very interested.</text>
	<text id="911">Get out!</text>
	<text id="912">Masher!!!</text>
	<text id="913">Helllppp !!!</text>
	<text id="914">Everybody talks about these guys from outer space, they say they landed on several islands. But that should not interrupt our game.</text>
	<text id="915">You pest!</text>
	<text id="916">I&apos;ve noticed I keep losing since you helped my little friend over there. Nice move Sherlock!</text>
	<text id="917">I don&apos;t know. But it has been a long time since I last saw Ker&apos;aooc the healer.</text>
	<text id="918">I believe it is in the desert, but I never found it!!</text>
	<text id="919">Oh! Hello Mr. Twinsen.</text>
	<text id="920">Cheater!</text>
	<text id="921">I usually play better than that, but my back&apos;s killing me. The healer Ker&apos;aooc went out and forgot to leave me some poultice.</text>
	<text id="922">Aah, thank you kiddo! Feels like I got the back of a young Sphero again.</text>
	<text id="923">Well kiddo, all you had to do was treat my back for me to win all the games, golly gee!</text>
	<text id="924">I often go to see the healing wizard for my back... I have a sore back from time to time.</text>
	<text id="925">I&apos;m no spring chicken anymore, you know. And the back, it&apos;s important when you bowl!!</text>
	<text id="926">Who that?</text>
	<text id="927">Oh sure! There, right at the corner of the plaza...</text>
	<text id="928">What, the school of bowling, er... of magic? Ah yes, when I was young, it was said to be in the cemetery!</text>
	<text id="929">Hello.</text>
	<text id="930">The wizards? Ah yes, I saw some pass by quite a while back. They were talking about the Hacienda, in the desert.</text>
	<text id="931">I found this car in the desert. Some people think they can get away with anything. By the way, if you want it, it&apos;s yours for 50 Kashes.</text>
	<text id="932">Here, I am the best. Nobody can follow me. Try if you want.</text>
	<text id="933">I don&apos;t know where it is, but it would be nice if there was a driving school. At least, that would be useful.</text>
	<text id="934">The wizards? Ah no, I don&apos;t see many. They are not in the habit of coming here, you know!!</text>
	<text id="935">Lost!!</text>
	<text id="936">If you think you can follow me, go to the starting line.</text>
	<text id="937">You succeeded. Maybe I should go see the healing wizard. He told me that, if I poured a little gallic acid in my engine, I could go faster!!</text>
	<text id="938">I am going to tell you a little secret: a wizard told me that he might have hidden a protective spell on the island across from the Hacienda.</text>
	<text id="939">If you want to do a few laps, you should go get a car!!</text>
	<text id="940">Welcome</text>
	<text id="941">No... although ... I go to the desert to gather the plants with which I cook. But I always avoid crossing a terrifying place, a kind of a forlorn garden... It might be there.</text>
	<text id="942">I wouldn&apos;t be surprised if they had disappeared in the ancient Temple of Bù !! My brother-in-law works there and he tells strange tales about disappearances...</text>
	<text id="943">These Esmer visitors are extraordinary. They are supposed to come from the Emerald Moon. Would you believe that??</text>
	<text id="944">Since the Esmers have shown their true faces, people have gone home. Everybody hides and only a few businesses are allowed to open.</text>
	<text id="945">I hope my clientele will come back. It looks like there are less and less Esmers in the streets of Port-Ludo.</text>
	<text id="946">A holomap costs 10 Kashes.</text>
	<text id="947">A flask of gallic costs 50 kashes.</text>
	<text id="948">Stand in front of the article of your choice and do &quot;ACTION&quot;.</text>
	<text id="949">Good day sir, welcome to my shop.</text>
	<text id="950">A Nitro-Meca-Penguin costs 4 Kashes.</text>
	<text id="951">For 15 Kashes, you can get recharged in Life points.</text>
	<text id="952">For 15 Kashes, you can get recharged in Magic points.</text>
	<text id="953">Three darts will cost you 4 Kashes.</text>
	<text id="954">I&apos;m unclear on the details, but a customer told me about an old wiseman who presumably knows all the island secrets. I believe he lives near the Hacienda.</text>
	<text id="955">Do you know that you are my first customer since way back when.</text>
	<text id="956">I don&apos;t know where they are, sir. Me and the tales of magic, you know...</text>
	<text id="957">These strangers are pretty strange. They have this whole collection of carnival costumes that range from cacti to garbage cans. They seem to enjoy it. I keep seeing them in disguise.</text>
	<text id="958">Hello.</text>
	<text id="959">I can&apos;t answer you, sir. I am not from here.</text>
	<text id="960">Bravo!!</text>
	<text id="961">Dumb! I can&apos;t remember what I did with the admission tickets and I&apos;m afraid we might be checked!! ...Et er... do you think we can go farther?</text>
	<text id="962">Oh! Er... hello sir.</text>
	<text id="963">I left our tickets to my brother, he&apos;s the park warden, you know, Mr. Organized... up there... hmm!...that&apos;s it, almost there...</text>
	<text id="964">I don&apos;t know, sir.</text>
	<text id="965">Ah no, I didn&apos;t see any. On the other hand, quite a few Esmers pass by here.</text>
	<text id="966">Sir!</text>
	<text id="967">If you want to go farther out, you&apos;ll have to board a vacant cart. Watch out during the visit, stay on the tracks and don&apos;t get off. It&apos;s dangerous, and you could easily injure yourself.</text>
	<text id="968">Hello sir.</text>
	<text id="969">Never heard of it.</text>
	<text id="970">Didn&apos;t see none. Did see a bunch of Esmers pass by en route to the lowest basement. &quot;To do some repairs,&quot; they said.</text>
	<text id="971">Magnificent!</text>
	<text id="972">My son adores tales of magic... he even believes we got in here with our special powers!! as if by a miracle!!</text>
	<text id="973">This temple is absolutely extraordinary. I wonder what we&apos;ll see afterwards!?</text>
	<text id="974">Hello.</text>
	<text id="975">I didn&apos;t know one existed. If we have time and manage to find it, we&apos;ll pay a visit, yes?</text>
	<text id="976">No. Didn&apos;t see any.</text>
	<text id="977">I don&apos;t know. I always make a detour whenever I take a stroll in the area. Not far from here, there is a dreadful garden on the rocky hillside.</text>
	<text id="978">Ah no, I don&apos;t know where they are. In fact, it has been awhile since I saw any.</text>
	<text id="979">Hi.</text>
	<text id="980">I enjoy wandering in the desert. Once, in the Temple of Bù, I found lots of little treasures.</text>
	<text id="981">The access to the lower floors is temporarily prohibited, we can no longer assure the safety of the visitors. The Esmers have volunteered to do the work in the lowest basement. It&apos;s not I who will complain!!</text>
	<text id="982">Oh! Hello Mr. Twinsen! What an honor to see you here.</text>
	<text id="983">I don&apos;t know, I heard that it is in the desert.</text>
	<text id="984">No idea. Since I&apos;m been here, I have not seen a single one!</text>
	<text id="985">Hey, mister! My daddy, he&apos;s smart. He was able to get us in without tickets!</text>
	<text id="986">Yippee!!!!</text>
	<text id="987">I don&apos;t like school!!</text>
	<text id="988">Wizards? Those fellows with the funny hats? Nope, I didn&apos;t see any!</text>
	<text id="989">A ticket mister? For only 7 Kashes, you can visit all of Temple-Park, including the inside of the Temple of Bù.</text>
	<text id="990">Stop him!</text>
	<text id="991">Now that the temple&apos;s under repair, we don&apos;t have too many customers. Just Esmers mostly, visiting. They offered to help us.</text>
	<text id="992">It exists? I always thought it was just another desert mirage.</text>
	<text id="993">Sorry, I didn&apos;t see any.</text>
	<text id="994">Careful sir, keep off the grass!</text>
	<text id="995">I don&apos;t know, sir. Once, a customer told me about it, but he didn&apos;t know where it was. That, or I forgot.</text>
	<text id="996">No, sir, can&apos;t help you. It&apos;s not often we see wizards around here..</text>
	<text id="997">Phew!! With all these gate-crashers, I don&apos;t know which way to turn.</text>
	<text id="998">Would you like 3 darts and try some duck shooting? The price is 4 kashes.</text>
	<text id="999">Bravo sir, you won these magnificent balloons!!!</text>
	<text id="1000">For 12 Kashes, where do you want to go?</text>
	<text id="1001">Welcome to the Inter-islands Ferry, sir.</text>
	<text id="1002">Our ferries don&apos;t service this island, sir.</text>
	<text id="1003">I don&apos;t know where it is.</text>
	<text id="1004">No, I haven&apos;t seen any in quite a while.</text>
	<text id="1005">Help!!</text>
	<text id="1006">Oof! Thanks Twinsen, that shell was getting on my nerves!!</text>
	<text id="1007">Hey Twinsen! It&apos;s me, Joe!! I don&apos;t feel too good. Couldn&apos;t you do something for me?</text>
	<text id="1008">It has been two months since I enrolled in this blasted school, and I have not been able to pass a single test!!!</text>
	<text id="1009">Ah no!! If I had seen any, I&apos;d have asked them to help me pass at least one test!!!</text>
	<text id="1010">I can&apos;t, I just can&apos;t!!! I heard some alien dudes landed on Twinsun, and I didn&apos;t even see them! I tried for days to do that blowgun test!</text>
	<text id="1011">I&apos;ve had it with these studies. I should do something else... I think I am going to try studying extra-zeelichian populations!!!</text>
	<text id="1012">How can I get in?</text>
	<text id="1013">Quickly! We must save Twinsun!!!</text>
	<text id="1014">What&apos;s he saying??</text>
	<text id="1015">Code Operation GREEN MOON</text>
	<text id="1016">Code Operation Dark Monk</text>
	<text id="1017">Operation Moon.</text>
	<text id="1018">Code 36AX 95.</text>
	<text id="1019">Shuttle 64 87, mission Twinsun.</text>
	<text id="1020">Hello</text>
	<text id="1021">Twinsen!! You are here at last! It&apos;s horrible!! The Esmers have built some reactors on Emerald Moon in order to propel it toward Twinsun and explode our planet!! They obey their God who was miraculously reincarnated, and they want to fulfill an ancient prophecy which is supposed to return their planet to its ancient heavenly look.</text>
	<text id="1022">Hey, Twinsen, take this translator, and you will conveniently understand the language of Zeelich!!</text>
	<text id="1023">Follow me!</text>
	<text id="1024">Twinsen! I left my vessel near the outside of the crater. We&apos;ll be able to escape through the yard!</text>
	<text id="1025">The door&apos;s jammed. We have to find some way to open it.</text>
	<text id="1026">Zeef erkierio orguoerg erguergu ug- ^hrt.</text>
	<text id="1027">Moon base to shuttle. Moon base to shuttle. Please give your password for identification. I repeat, give your password for identification.</text>
	<text id="1028">Right code.</text>
	<text id="1029">Wrong code.</text>
	<text id="1030">ZAZ zeujazeT er ERItier ertiye YI!</text>
	<text id="1031">Go to the welcoming building, get a pass. Then, go to the main entrance of the base. It&apos;s the door with the green light. That means that it is open.</text>
	<text id="1032">zeio p^r.</text>
	<text id="1033">Hello.</text>
	<text id="1034">ZEOe eiarERAtiERTTERt AYO oertrtYRTIY tp !</text>
	<text id="1035">Only the welcoming building controls the opening of the doors. If you want to enter here, you must ask them to open!</text>
	<text id="1036">zeio p^r.</text>
	<text id="1037">Hello.</text>
	<text id="1038">It&apos;s true! We have been deceived by Dark Monk, our God who reappeared. This must be stopped! But the reactors are indestructible!! They are remote controlled from Zeelich! The center which controls them has been built on island CX. Our only hope of avoiding the disaster is to destroy it!!!</text>
	<text id="1039">I will take you to the dissidents. Only they can help us!! They always haunt the bars and the slightly shady places! Meanwhile, we must leave! We can&apos;t stay here!!</text>
	<text id="1040">Dfkiod fdssfm qQf f-pqG dfggfdg qgdfgk!!</text>
	<text id="1041">We, inhabitants of Zeelich, have been deceived by Dark Monk, our God who reappeared. This must be stopped! But the reactors are indestructible!! They are remote controlled from Zeelich! The center which controls them has been built on island CX. Our only hope of avoiding the disaster is to destroy it!!!</text>
	<text id="1042">Go... to CX...island CX...</text>
	<text id="1043">We&apos;ve to get out of here!!</text>
	<text id="1044">Tfhuirt!</text>
	<text id="1045">Halt!!</text>
	<text id="1046">Zeorfevg r!!</text>
	<text id="1047">Stop!!</text>
	<text id="1048">ZX81!!</text>
	<text id="1049">HAL!!</text>
	<text id="1050">Ereolju p-er omom qeo omkldf zekujze mzkmjha!!</text>
	<text id="1051">Don&apos;t forget to go to the welcoming building and have your passage registered.</text>
	<text id="1052">Hello.</text>
	<text id="1053">Thanks, Joe! But what are you doing here?</text>
	<text id="1054">What do the wizards say??</text>
	<text id="1055">It&apos;s OK.</text>
	<text id="1056">I&apos;m not interested.</text>
	<text id="1057">I&apos;d like to get to island CX. Can you take me there?</text>
	<text id="1058">I&apos;d like to buy some gazogem.</text>
	<text id="1059">I&apos;m trying to get to island CX.</text>
	<text id="1060">Are you winning?</text>
	<text id="1061">What should I do?</text>
	<text id="1062">It&apos;s OK!</text>
	<text id="1063">But Jerome, I&apos;ve got to find island CX and destroy the machines that control the lunar reactors!</text>
	<text id="1064">I don&apos;t care about that.</text>
	<text id="1065">The island of the Francos.</text>
	<text id="1066">Celebration Island.</text>
	<text id="1067">I&apos;d like to see Rick, the boss.</text>
	<text id="1068">You know Rick, I&apos;d like to see him.</text>
	<text id="1069">The emperor had some secret base built on island CX. From there, he&apos;ll trigger the firing of these reactors built on the moon in utmost secrecy which&apos;ll destroy my whole planet. I&apos;ve got to go to this island to prevent this from happening. Could you help me get there?</text>
	<text id="1070">I&apos;m looking for a Mr. Johnny Rocket.</text>
	<text id="1071">Are you Mr. Rocket?</text>
	<text id="1072">I&apos;m here on behalf of Rick to look for the dissidents, and I desperately need to get to island CX!</text>
	<text id="1073">Not yet.</text>
	<text id="1074">That&apos;s me. I have to get to island CX and somehow destroy the control center of the lunar reactors before they&apos;re fired and the moon starts falling toward Twinsun.</text>
	<text id="1075">Where should I go?</text>
	<text id="1076">I&apos;m staying here.</text>
	<text id="1077">I don&apos;t have enough Kashes.</text>
	<text id="1078">I don&apos;t have enough Zlitos.</text>
	<text id="1079">&quot;You are at the harbor of Otringal.&quot;</text>
	<text id="1080">&quot;You are in downtown Otringal.&quot;</text>
	<text id="1081">&quot;You are at the astroport of Otringal.&quot;</text>
	<text id="1082">&quot;THE ZEELICH GAZETTE: ...Johnny Rocket at the Imperial! Zeelich&apos;s brightest star, the first explorer to set foot on Twinsun, now lives on Otringal...&quot;</text>
	<text id="1083">&quot;THE INQUIRER : ...group of dissidents who defaced our beautiful city with subversive posters.... some will be arrested... the police are looking for runaways...&quot;</text>
	<text id="1084">&quot;OTRINGAL NEWS : The twinsunian wizards on a visit of Otringal...&quot;</text>
	<text id="1085">&quot;THE OFFICIAL RUMOR: The Emperor asserts: Dark Monk will fulfill the prophecy, whether or not the mosquibees are willing to bring their fragment!!!&quot;</text>
	<text id="1086">&quot;THE DESPATCH OF ZEELICH: shortage of gazogem, the tankers stopped supplying Otringal!&quot;</text>
	<text id="1087">&quot;THE INQUIRER: Looking for witnesses! 10,000 Zlitos reward!!! If you see a Twinsunian in a blue tunic, call the police immediately...armed and dangerous...&quot;</text>
	<text id="1088">&quot;OTRINGAL NEWS: Twinsunian Anarchist Disrupts Dark Monk&apos;s Ceremony...</text>
	<text id="1089">&quot;THE OFFICIAL RUMOR: Emperor Reveals: Dark Monk Warned Me! He predicted a Twinsunian dressed in blue would try to prevent our ceremony...&quot;</text>
	<text id="1090">&quot;2:55 p.m., shuttle 65 38, destination planet Zirla for fly safari... 3:20 p.m., shuttle 007, destination red planet...&quot;</text>
	<text id="1091">Rtergp- er ojf -j -jo- jljg &quot;j ljvb ql-mj l-bj jbljbsjr -rj.</text>
	<text id="1092">&quot;DARK MONK HAS REINCARNATED!!! Come Join The Revelry! Be part of the celebration as he cancels the curse of Zeelich and restores its heavenly look!&quot;</text>
	<text id="1093">&quot;WANTED: The so-called &quot;Twinsen.&quot; Master criminal - Trying to oppose Dark Monk and prevent the great celebration - Wears blue tunic - If you see him, call the police - Anyone helping bring this miscreant into custody will be rewarded the amount of 10,000 Zlitos.&quot;</text>
	<text id="1094">I hold a wizard&apos;s diploma.</text>
	<text id="1095">One ferry ticket.</text>
	<text id="1096">I have an umbrella.</text>
	<text id="1097">I&apos;ve got some Twinsunian money.</text>
	<text id="1098">I already have a crystal, so now I&apos;ll be able to use this laser pistol.</text>
	<text id="1099">But... who do you mean?</text>
	<text id="1100">&quot;Out of order, no gazogem&quot;</text>
	<text id="1101">I don&apos;t have anything to sell.</text>
	<text id="1102">This painting is strange, signed by some guy...Gramitte.</text>
	<text id="1103">&quot;You are in the lower city of Otringal.&quot;</text>
	<text id="1104">&quot;IMPERIAL HOTEL - Luxury establishment, members only&quot;</text>
	<text id="1105">&quot;You are in the upper city of Otringal.&quot;</text>
	<text id="1106">Whoah, these paintings are bogus!</text>
	<text id="1107">This control panel&apos;s been modified. Apparently, I can&apos;t put the itinerary tokens in here anymore.</text>
	<text id="1108">There&apos;s a piece missing, something disc-shaped. I guess I need it for the shuttle to take off.</text>
	<text id="1109">Depiction of Zeelich, the Planet of a Thousand Wonders!!</text>
	<text id="1110">Fdodik pfdjf df-l fj -r -g lgjjg ldfjg- rjljvg -dfj-j jj!!</text>
	<text id="1111">Darn! This here shuttle, t&apos;will soon be ready fer takeoff. Me myself, ah would of fixed them stabilizing jets!! Barrin&apos; that, best use an itinerary token! Might not take off without it.</text>
	<text id="1112">epdu.e fe djkhs-dyty opizef m&apos;zefjklf!!</text>
	<text id="1113">Cool down, Mr. Wizard sir! Please, walk this way...</text>
	<text id="1114">Welcome to Zeelich, Master. Follow me, I will take you to your twinsunian colleagues.</text>
	<text id="1115">Follow us!!</text>
	<text id="1116">Calm down!</text>
	<text id="1117">Please come in, Master.</text>
	<text id="1118">Watch the hair!!</text>
	<text id="1119">Here we are, Master, on our way to Zeelich! Relax, the trip will not be very long.</text>
	<text id="1120">You are welcome, Master. Make yourself comfortable.</text>
	<text id="1121">But... it&apos;s... Twinsen! Yo, Twinsen! It&apos;s me, Joe the Elf! Your old friend! Good to see you again!!!</text>
	<text id="1122">Hey, Twinsen, great bumping into you! Say, you don&apos;t seem all that buddy-buddy with the locals! Soon as they heard your name, they jumped you, knocked you out, and stole your wizard&apos;s costume. And now, we&apos;re in jail.</text>
	<text id="1123">Actually I was with the wizards when the Esmers invited them to this planet. Now, they&apos;re being held captive by the emperor and claim the Esmers want to kidnap the children of Twinsun. I got scared, so I left, and found you there.</text>
	<text id="1124">They say the Esmers left for our planet to kidnap Twinsun&apos;s children! They say nothing can be done, but I still have hope. I&apos;m sure you will succeed in reaching the astroport to steal a shuttle and go save those children!!!</text>
	<text id="1125">Ah, not so nice, that one. I&apos;d rather not be left alone with him!!</text>
	<text id="1126">That&apos;s him! That&apos;s the Twinsunian we&apos;re looking for! Arrest him!</text>
	<text id="1127">Fdoejd hjduiy hjdysuyuyszdf!!&quot;</text>
	<text id="1128">You have no business here, sir!!</text>
	<text id="1129">Ererklerg- m mgmoeroz!!</text>
	<text id="1130">No!! Don&apos;t touch that!!</text>
	<text id="1131">Zpgjdfuetc jkdu dhjsdgzt dhy s zeyyhsh ??</text>
	<text id="1132">This is where we calculate the flight plans for the shuttles. You have no business being in here!!</text>
	<text id="1133">KHJopfgi ou dfiyu Heiosdn!!!!</text>
	<text id="1134">You must vacate the premises, sir. You are disturbing the work of our technicians.</text>
	<text id="1135">HJGri ??</text>
	<text id="1136">Free me!!</text>
	<text id="1137">fiodu qd ogjq vqdfjovjoqdf ovodjvj kdfjvdf jdv jdf io fbdfj dfovbbofg!!</text>
	<text id="1138">Thank you for having freed me. I am a dissident of the government. The emperor and Dark Monk, our reincarnated God, manipulate the people of Zeelich. They lie continually. @ But let&apos;s not waste any time. If you want to get out of here, don&apos;t take the main entrance, it is being watched by soldiers.</text>
	<text id="1139">Gfgkis p-rtojz fg m-fg p jkg-k p !!</text>
	<text id="1140">I am innocent, let me free!!!</text>
	<text id="1141">Rdjkhd fFu osdfiuIOI.</text>
	<text id="1142">I&apos;m sorry sir you may not enter here. It is restricted to the astroport personnel.</text>
	<text id="1143">Erergioeroerpzer erpfger!!!</text>
	<text id="1144">I can&apos;t believe it! There are two of them in this cell! Open the doors, I am going to put the funny one in his own cell!!</text>
	<text id="1145">GER ,ioyu zeyz RET zeafizef U zepz?ze.</text>
	<text id="1146">Hello Master. Settle down comfortably and don&apos;t hestitate to consult our tourist information terminal.</text>
	<text id="1147">OPIhki df fqddqsomf!!</text>
	<text id="1148">No!! That device is not the tourist information terminal. Don&apos;t touch anything, please!!</text>
	<text id="1149">Efek gfjiodf jkmfr kn jklm jklm.</text>
	<text id="1150">You came to pick up your itinerary token as well?</text>
	<text id="1151">reloeroui ergjumgumeugioeu gyu gio ugt fqh .</text>
	<text id="1152">Starting the automatic guidance system from the control tower.</text>
	<text id="1153">@ Welcome to Zeelich, the planet of a thousand wonders!! @ @ Its beauty will dazzle your eyes. The kindness of its inhabitants will warm your heart! @ @ We are the craftsmen of your happiness. @ @ Have trust in our friendship!!</text>
	<text id="1154">@ @ In our laboratories, our scientists are developing a technology of the future, capable of crossing space to come meet you personally. @ @ Come! Come share our science.</text>
	<text id="1155">@ If you don&apos;t meet with him, you might at least get a glance of our most high Emperor. @ @ With an unequaled kindness, he oversees our planet with skill and leniency.</text>
	<text id="1156">@ @ At the palace doors, you will get a look at his personal guard. @ @ They are imperial warriors, who perform a majestic parade every day.</text>
	<text id="1157">@ After that, you will try your luck in one of our extraordinary casinos, where you might win the &quot;Total Jackpot&quot;!!</text>
	<text id="1158">@ And don&apos;t forget to get a taste of our culinary specialties. @ @ Feel free to help yourself to a second slice of our unique firefly tart!!</text>
	<text id="1159">@ And, to crown your evening, you can learn our local dances in one of our prestigious clubs!!</text>
	<text id="1160">@ By no means! @ @ You shouldn&apos;t leave Zeelich without witnessing the unique, the incomparable, the one and only ceremony of Dark Monk, our all powerful God!!! @ @ Emerging from the crater of the volcano, amid a shimmer of lava explosions, his statue will inscribe the Redemption of our people in letters of fire!</text>
	<text id="1161">@ Only then will you leave Zeelich, your head filled with images and your heart ablaze with zest for life. @ @ Meanwhile, and awaiting your visit here, we thank you for your kind attention to our modest presentation.</text>
	<text id="1162">Insert 10 Zlitos if you want 10 Magic points</text>
	<text id="1163">Insert 10 Zlitos if you want 10 Life points.</text>
	<text id="1164">Zeoeipefi jfil-jgl-bm mjgjgk lgjlgfjljlg jlkjfghklm jfgljljs mj lmfgj!!</text>
	<text id="1165">Ah, but you&apos;re a Twinsunian. Bravo! And thanks to your wizards! The entire population of Zeelich is impatiently awaiting the ceremony!</text>
	<text id="1166">If you need some information, the destinations and departure times for the shuttles are indicated on the main panel.</text>
	<text id="1167">Hey, you! Stop! Police! I&apos;ve got him, he&apos;s right here! Let&apos;s see that reward!!!!</text>
	<text id="1168">Dezp iopjero-em -ljg- mflk j lf- klfg l-l-jk fjkb l-lf jgh-ilsfgj.</text>
	<text id="1169">Don&apos;t hesitate to call me if you need anything at all.</text>
	<text id="1170">E zeoirerj s ldjdfgldjg rgjo-jgo djgdlmgj!</text>
	<text id="1171">This is a well organized planet: soldiers everywhere, law and order, discipline, clean streets.</text>
	<text id="1172">I hope my shuttle will be here soon, I can&apos;t wait to get back home.</text>
	<text id="1173">Ereroerirejo kefkkh jkevv hiovkhkv kh kjhjk k vh fjkvh f fj k!!</text>
	<text id="1174">I&apos;ve had it with these Zeelichians!! They&apos;re totally nuts. Cops combing the streets, Cops everywhere, soon as we do a little something the wrong way, they jump all over us! I&apos;m getting fed up with this conditional freedom!</text>
	<text id="1175">I&apos;m leaving for Zirla. Heard they organize fantastic safaris, but I don&apos;t see the actual organizers anywhere. Hope I didn&apos;t pick the wrong day.</text>
	<text id="1176">Twinsen, I damaged the vessel during landing. I need some time for repairs. The Zeelichian fuel is called gazogem, it&apos;s very powerful. You should go get some.</text>
	<text id="1177">Of course, but I will need this gazogem sooner or later. Besides, it will allow me to transform your protopack and increase its performance.</text>
	<text id="1178">You must go get me some gazogem, so that I can finish to repair our vessel and make your protopack more powerful!!</text>
	<text id="1179">Thanks, Twinsen. Now I can finish up on the ship. I&apos;ll buzz you on the radio as soon as I do the protopack.</text>
	<text id="1180">Hey there, don&apos;t forget my gazogem. I really need it to repair the vessel. And I think you&apos;ll really appreciate what it does to your protopack.</text>
	<text id="1181">Thank you, Twinsen. Now I can make us a ship that can race the comets! Anyway, here&apos;s something to turn your protopack into a superjetpack. and from now on, you can fly higher!</text>
	<text id="1182">It&apos;s going to take me quite a while longer to finish up on the vessel here.</text>
	<text id="1183">Come in! Twinsen? It&apos;s me, Baldino! I&apos;ve improved your protopack, you can come pick it up now!</text>
	<text id="1184">On island CX? No way Jack! That&apos;s rough turf over there!!</text>
	<text id="1185">For 5 Zlitos, I can take you somewheres. Where do you wanna go?</text>
	<text id="1186">Oh most certainly not, sir. For some time now, nobody is returning from there. They say a monster is lurking in the area. No one in their right mind will take you there!</text>
	<text id="1187">For 5 Zlitos, I can be taking you somewhere. Where do you want to go sir?</text>
	<text id="1188">Hmmm... Maybe yes, maybe no, maybe both... Might be able to tell you something about it... expensive, though... maybe 100 Zlitos... and maybe &apos;cause it&apos;s you...</text>
	<text id="1189">I do know a dude who came back. These days, he sells souvenirs on Celebration Island. Might be able to take you to him.... Oh well, for you, it&apos;s a freebie! Welcome aboard Leontine, my cab!!</text>
	<text id="1190">If you want, mate, you can climb aboard my Leontine and I&apos;ll take you someplace for 10 Zlitos. OK then? Where to?</text>
	<text id="1191">Hello sir. I might be able to help you.</text>
	<text id="1192">Listen, mac. Do what you want, but don&apos;t give us trouble! Otherwise Riri and Momo&apos;ll twist you into a pretzel and dip you in hot cider! That&apos;s how we handle your type around here. You dig?</text>
	<text id="1193">The boss don&apos;t see nobody.</text>
	<text id="1194">Why not just enjoy the show instead of fretting like that.</text>
	<text id="1195">Hello sir.</text>
	<text id="1196">Hey, buddy, you lost something? What is it? You looking for your glasses? Here, we&apos;ll help you out!</text>
	<text id="1197">the Boss no touch!</text>
	<text id="1198">No touch the Boss!</text>
	<text id="1199">Hello sir.</text>
	<text id="1200">Hey get lost man!!</text>
	<text id="1201">You&apos;re on!</text>
	<text id="1202">Lousy audience. They used to be so cool! And they came by the thousands!!!</text>
	<text id="1203">Island CX? You got to be kidding? Lots of guys tried to get there, but not one ever came back. I&apos;d be surprised if you get someone to ferry you over.</text>
	<text id="1204">Yeah, I see who it is. A bit of free advice: don&apos;t try to reach him. Not only is he highly respected and inaccessible, but this is his home turf. Just drop it!</text>
	<text id="1205">Hmmm, aren&apos;t you the one the police are after? I heard you want to stop Dark Monk from celebrating the last ceremony, the one that&apos;ll rid us of the curse. Please don&apos;t screw it up, we&apos;ve been waiting for a millennia.</text>
	<text id="1206">Hmmm... Nobody wants to go there these days, it&apos;s way too risky. They say monsters have come out of the gas over there. Try the Captain, he&apos;s the old nut at the very end of the pier. He&apos;s the only one who&apos;d take you!</text>
	<text id="1207">Hmmm, you look a lot like the one all the cops are after. You&apos;ll be fine here but watch your back if you wander away from this little area.</text>
	<text id="1208">I ain&apos;t takin&apos; you noplace. Go try the casino Gloum. If you win the Jackpot, you&apos;ll have a nice surprise.</text>
	<text id="1209">Go try your luck at the casino Gloum. I&apos;ve been there, there is always a surprise waiting for you!</text>
	<text id="1210">So, you are the notorious Twinsunian who&apos;s dying to see me. You&apos;re on the run, my friend, the police are all after you. Impressive. So spit it out, what do you want?</text>
	<text id="1211">I&apos;ll level with you. Unfortunately, I have no one who can accommodate your needs. But there&apos;s a group of dissidents who are very hostile to the government. Go see Johnny Rocket. Tell him Rick sent you, and he&apos;ll take you to them. He lives at the Imperial hotel, in the upper city.</text>
	<text id="1212">He&apos;s our greatest hero. The first one to set foot on mysterious Twinsun! Thanks to him we&apos;ll get much-needed help from the Twinsunian wizards! He&apos;s over there, in the armchair, with his manicurist.</text>
	<text id="1213">I adore this hotel. Kind of a private club. Only the finest elements of society are allowed entry.</text>
	<text id="1214">I&apos;ve had it with this lousy joint! I&apos;m moving on! The Imperial hotel, that&apos;s where I should have been all this time! Nothing but classy people there, not a bunch of unwashed hoodlums or sailors.</text>
	<text id="1215">Get lost!</text>
	<text id="1216">I can&apos;t wait for my shift to be over, I got to go buy some gazogem at the service station of Otringal.</text>
	<text id="1217">Hello, sir, and welcome to Gambling Paradise!</text>
	<text id="1218">You can try your luck at the gaming tables or the slots. It&apos;s your choice.</text>
	<text id="1219">If you want sir, I can have you taken back up to the exit of the casino.</text>
	<text id="1220">Ah, my dear sir, the Lady Luck is a fickle female! I have been losing since the curse of Dark Monk condemned us to live forever on this miserable planet. But the day will come when I will win!</text>
	<text id="1221">To play, stand in front of a marker or a machine, and insert some Zlitos. If you play the slots, you could win the super Jackpot of the evening. It will grant you admission to our special room!</text>
	<text id="1222">Wait a minute, I smell a rat! I am sure that this filthy critter has been trained.</text>
	<text id="1223">You cheater!!</text>
	<text id="1224">Come on Baby...</text>
	<text id="1225">Yippee!!!!</text>
	<text id="1226">Stand in front of one of the four markers, and place your bets.</text>
	<text id="1227">Welcome, my dear sir! Welcome, welcome to our wheel of fortune! So you&apos;re the one fate has chosen today to try for our Super Jackpot! Excellent, excellent. Now, just stand behind the wheel on the small podium, give it a whirl, and maybe, maybe I say, you will hit it big!!!</text>
	<text id="1228">It&apos;s very simple, my friend. Stand on the small podium, and give the wheel a good hard spin!</text>
	<text id="1229">Banzai!</text>
	<text id="1230">Stand in front of the article of your choice and do &quot;ACTION&quot; if you want to buy it.</text>
	<text id="1231">I couldn&apos;t help but notice you&apos;re from Twinsun. Would you be interested in selling me anything from your planet? Something little-bitty, even?</text>
	<text id="1232">Downstairs you&apos;ll find the rest of the dissidents waiting for you. Johnny has told us you are coming.</text>
	<text id="1233">Go, they&apos;re downstairs.</text>
	<text id="1234">20 Life points cost 20 Zlitos.</text>
	<text id="1235">20 Magic points cost 20 Zlitos.</text>
	<text id="1236">One meca-penguin costs 15 Zlitos.</text>
	<text id="1237">I&apos;ll buy it from you for 25 Zlitos.</text>
	<text id="1238">I&apos;ll take it back for 15 Zlitos, and I think I&apos;m being generous.</text>
	<text id="1239">Ummm...I&apos;ll buy it back for...shall we say 20 Zlitos?</text>
	<text id="1240">A wizard&apos;s diploma costs 40 Zlitos.</text>
	<text id="1241">A ferry ticket costs 30 Zlitos.</text>
	<text id="1242">An umbrella costs 35 Zlitos.</text>
	<text id="1243">A memory viewer costs 30 Zlitos</text>
	<text id="1244">Hmm.... I&apos;ll take your junk for 20 Zlitos.</text>
	<text id="1245">The price of admission to the casino is 5 Zlitos. Would you like to enter?</text>
	<text id="1246">Sorry, bud, I don&apos;t have none left. I&apos;m waiting for some tanker due in from the island of the Francos. Their refinery produces the gazogem from the gems collected in the under-gas.</text>
	<text id="1247">The time is near. During the next ceremony, Dark Monk, our reincarnated God, will reunite the four keys of the four Zeelichian races. And the ground will open.. And the gas and its monsters will flee screaming into the sky. And the curse will lift. We will live and die as before, on our Zeelich restored anew.</text>
	<text id="1248">That&apos;s me, what do you want?</text>
	<text id="1249">Shut up! Are you nuts? Never mention the rebels in public! Meet me in my room, we can talk without danger.</text>
	<text id="1250">You are lucky to come on behalf of Rick. The government is looking for the dissidents, and you are very rash. What do you want?</text>
	<text id="1251">I know you. You&apos;re Twinsen, the hero of your planet. The Emperor and Dark Monk fear you -- that&apos;s why you&apos;re a wanted man. The dissidents will help you. Here, take this ring, go to the Twinsunian souvenir shop, and show it to the salesman. He&apos;ll take you to them.</text>
	<text id="1252">So, have you seen the dissidents?</text>
	<text id="1253">Warning, warning!! Public notice!! Wanted: a Twinsunian named Twinsen, wearing a blue tunic. If you see him, you must immediately inform the police!</text>
	<text id="1254">Police!!</text>
	<text id="1255">So! Are you the Twinsunian Johnny told us about?</text>
	<text id="1256">Listen, Twinsunian. Go to the Mosquibee village in the under-gas. Most of our dissident comrades are already hiding out there. To get in, you have to take the elevator on the platform of the Francos.</text>
	<text id="1257">Go get a rock-crystal from the Island of Celebration. It&apos;ll allow you to operate the laser pistol of Zarnon.</text>
	<text id="1258">I don&apos;t know what to do. The island CX is totally inaccessible. It is impossible to get near it.</text>
	<text id="1259">You&apos;re going to make it twinsunian, I&apos;m sure of that.</text>
	<text id="1260">Now I understand everything! Dark Monk will explode your planet on the day of his big ceremony. It&apos;s the fire from the skies he&apos;s always been preaching about. But how can we stop it? Island CX has become a forbidden zone!</text>
	<text id="1261">Here&apos;s the deal. You have to go to the Francos&apos; platform and take the elevator down to the under-gas. Once there, you&apos;ll have to find the Mosquibee village.</text>
	<text id="1262">We have to find a way to go to this island. But how?</text>
	<text id="1263">Nobody knows for sure. Some guy found that drifting in space. Supposed to come from a very distant garbage can planet...</text>
	<text id="1264">I&apos;ve got it! There&apos;s a passage between the under-gas and island CX. The entrance is in the Mosquibee village, that&apos;s what lets them keep the government soldiers out.</text>
	<text id="1265">To reach the elevator, you need a powerful weapon. Here, this is a pistolaser of Zarnon. But you will have to find a crystal to make it work. There are some on the side of the volcano of the celebration.</text>
	<text id="1266">The passage that leaves the Mosquibee village will allow you to reach island CX directly.</text>
	<text id="1267">From what we know, the passage is blocked by a door. The key belongs to the queen of the mosquibees. It&apos;s up to you to convince them of your good faith. But don&apos;t forget that our comrades are over there!</text>
	<text id="1268">No taxi will go there. A guy I knew once tried to get close on a bet. But nobody&apos;s seen him since.</text>
	<text id="1269">I&apos;ve heard some Zeelichians live under the gas layer. I wonder how you&apos;d get there...</text>
	<text id="1270">I shouldn&apos;t never have watched that commercial for Zeelich, it&apos;s so fake. The changing of the guard was lousy, we never even got to see the emperor, and that casino, it&apos;s a tourist clip-joint... &quot;Have trust in our friendship...&quot; Hah! Who are they kidding!</text>
	<text id="1271">Yessir! News steaming hot off the presses!! Latest edition!! Right here, right here!! Plenty for everybody!!</text>
	<text id="1272">Hey, wait, you&apos;re the criminal Twinsunian!! Police!! Police!!</text>
	<text id="1273">Hello sir!!</text>
	<text id="1274">Step on in and try your luck. You&apos;ll find the best games of chance ever devised. And if you&apos;re in luck, you can even try for our Super Jackpot!!! Don&apos;t you feel like you&apos;re due?? Step right in!!</text>
	<text id="1275">I come from the under-gas. I took the elevator which goes up to the Francos&apos; platform to come here and witness Dark Monk&apos;s ceremony.</text>
	<text id="1276">You can&apos;t climb to the upper city, sir. The elevators are temporarily out of order.</text>
	<text id="1277">Criminal!!! Help!!!!</text>
	<text id="1278">No, thanks, go see somebody else! The place is deadly. And today nobody wants to talk about it.</text>
	<text id="1279">Saw nothing, heard nothing. Now, beat it.</text>
	<text id="1280">Can&apos;t you see I am busy ?</text>
	<text id="1281">The shows here are truly awful, but they have that certain touch of sleazy slickness, don&apos;t you think?</text>
	<text id="1282">Give us our money back!!!</text>
	<text id="1283">Brrravo!!!</text>
	<text id="1284">You can&apos;t get in here, it&apos;s closed. Members only. Quit loitering now, and get moving.</text>
	<text id="1285">What are you doing here? You don&apos;t belong! now Get out!!</text>
	<text id="1286">Are you stupid or what? He&apos;s right there in front of you!</text>
	<text id="1287">He&apos;s in his room.</text>
	<text id="1288">Hheeeeee!!!</text>
	<text id="1289">Get going, mister. You can&apos;t stand in the middle -- that&apos;d bother the other pedestrians.</text>
	<text id="1290">Halt!!!</text>
	<text id="1291">Hello sir.</text>
	<text id="1292">Stop!</text>
	<text id="1293">Welcome to Otringal, sir. Have a pleasant stay.</text>
	<text id="1294">Stop!!</text>
	<text id="1295">Halt!!</text>
	<text id="1296">Careful, sir, you shouldn&apos;t run like that. Someone might think you&apos;re you know who.</text>
	<text id="1297">Stop!!</text>
	<text id="1298">But a thief, of course.</text>
	<text id="1299">Hello sir.</text>
	<text id="1300">Stop!!</text>
	<text id="1301">Hello sir have a pleasant stay among us.</text>
	<text id="1302">Halt!!</text>
	<text id="1303">You who are a tourist, you should go to the casino of the gloums. On my behalf.</text>
	<text id="1304">Murderer!!</text>
	<text id="1305">Sorry sir, this article is not for sale.</text>
	<text id="1306">Hello sir. Wouldn&apos;t you have an object or something to show me?</text>
	<text id="1307">Oh, thank you, sir... Police!! Police!!! We got him!!! He&apos;s right here!!!</text>
	<text id="1308">So you got rid of the Emperor. You&apos;re a tough guy. Maybe you could soon take his place. You&apos;re quite attractive you know.</text>
	<text id="1309">Hhiiiiiiiii !!!!</text>
	<text id="1310">Are you the one who went to island CX and made it back alive?</text>
	<text id="1311">What did you see over there?</text>
	<text id="1312">How can I get there?</text>
	<text id="1313">Otringal</text>
	<text id="1314">The island of the Francos</text>
	<text id="1315">Nowhere, I&apos;m staying right here.</text>
	<text id="1316">Nope, not yet. It&apos;d be great to get to his office. Any ideas?</text>
	<text id="1317">Hello.</text>
	<text id="1318">Oh man, I don&apos;t have enough Zlitos.</text>
	<text id="1319">Oof!! This crystal is way too heavy. I need some kind of tool to break off a piece.</text>
	<text id="1320">In the beginning, the 2 mother planets, Zeer (the sun) and Lich (the cold) met one another during the Oogh: the great cataclysm. From this Zeelich was born. Life appeared and the brotherhood of the Gods sent there the youngest son of the light, who was called Kard N&apos;kom. Alas, some deleterious fumes emanating from the Great Sulfur Mine disfigured him. His horribly mutilated face escaped the Gods, and it was decided that Kard N&apos;kom would have to forever hide his face and never again appear in front of the noble assembly. Condemned to roam the cosmos forever, Kard N&apos;kom saw his Name erased from the divine law. He who wanders without a face became then known as Dark Monk... Zeelich was populated with 4 different races, condemned by the Gods to fight each other forever. But, life being stronger, the divine brotherhood hurled Zeelich into the first sun of the Novae system. This shock created the planet such as we know it: a blanket of clouds isolating the rocky summits from the melting ground.</text>
	<text id="1321">Then Dark Monk came back and announced the latest verdict from the Gods. The races were to fraternize and share the task of returning Zeelich to its former beauty. He unveiled a great wonder: from the deadly cloud, hideous monsters were born and threatened to invade the planet. But, thanks to his Key, Dark Monk also gave rise to a volcano which erupted and sculpted in basalt a gigantic statue in his image, holding the Stone Book of the 10,000 Names. At each ceremony, lightning would henceforth inscribe once more the Name of God, Dark Monk. Before disappearing, Dark Monk broke his Key into 4 pieces and thus revealed the Great Prophecy. On the day when the 10,000th Name of God is engraved the reunion of the 4 fragments of the Key will make the monsters and the gas disappear, and will give back to Zeelich the heavenly appearance of its origin. Life will then be reborn as it was in the time of Eden.</text>
	<text id="1322">And what did you do with the children and the wizards?, you creep!</text>
	<text id="1323">FunFrock, you suck big time, and I&apos;m going to take you out, and I don&apos;t mean for a pizza!</text>
	<text id="1324">I know. But where is he? And where are the children?</text>
	<text id="1325">I&apos;m off to save the children and face FunFrock. Get out of here and get Baldino on Otringal!! We&apos;re going to need his ship to get out of this mess.</text>
	<text id="1326">&quot;... and when the stranger appears, alone capable of reuniting the four keys, Dark Monk will oppose... ...in the ultimate celebration the monsters and the gas will disappear... in forgetfulness Dark Monk will go... ... and life will Zeelich regain...&quot;</text>
	<text id="1327">This way is no good. I need the four fragments.</text>
	<text id="1328">Mosquibee representative. The race of the Mosquibees lives in the under-gas. Their village is a magnificent cocoon anchored on the rocky tor which supports the island CX.</text>
	<text id="1329">Wannie representative. The race of the Wannies lives in the under-gas. They are the workers of the gem mine, from which gazogem is made. The mine is being run by the Building Company, under imperial supervision.</text>
	<text id="1330">Franco representative. The Francos live on the island of the Francos, (what a surprise!), which is enshrouded by the gas swarming with monsters. The Francos refine the gems extracted in the under-gas, and turn them into gazogem, usable by all the vehicles of Zeelich.</text>
	<text id="1331">Sup representative. The Sups live in the upper city of Otringal. They are the planet&apos;s intellectual elite and always hold the highest positions.</text>
	<text id="1332">I know him. He is from my planet. He is evil... But don&apos;t worry, I&apos;ll make sure he knows what&apos;s right.</text>
	<text id="1333">For 5 Zlitos, I can take you somewheres. Where do you wanna go?</text>
	<text id="1334">The fare I am charging is 5 Zlitos. Where would you like to go, sir?</text>
	<text id="1335">That&apos;s it, my man, it&apos;s here. You&apos;ll find him easily, he sells souvenirs.</text>
	<text id="1336">But that&apos;s the Twinsunian who escaped!! After him!! Murderer!!!</text>
	<text id="1337">Halt!!</text>
	<text id="1338">No, no, it&apos;s not me, it&apos;s not me!! Help, police!!! Murderer!!!!</text>
	<text id="1339">I know you...you&apos;re the murderer everybody&apos;s looking for! Police, help!!!!</text>
	<text id="1340">Yeah, it&apos;s me, or what&apos;s left of me. What do you want?</text>
	<text id="1341">Ha ha, what I saw there... a secret fortress, guvv&apos;ner. A fortress built by the parliament, where some army shuttles shoot at everything that gets close. I don&apos;t know what they hide there, and I don&apos;t want to know.</text>
	<text id="1342">Are you kidding me? Nobody can get close. The only ones crazy enough to make a go at it, are Rick&apos;s gang. Rick, he&apos;s the owner of that bar, by the harbor. But he&apos;s much more than that, he&apos;s in charge of the Otringal underworld. Go see him, maybe he&apos;ll help ya.</text>
	<text id="1343">So tell me, have you found Rick ?</text>
	<text id="1344">No... maybe not the lodges. I heard rumors about something, but I just don&apos;t remember.</text>
	<text id="1345">A little statue of Dark Monk, mister? The real one comes out of the volcano only during the cult ceremonies. It&apos;s quite an impressive sight, you should see it some time!</text>
	<text id="1346">It&apos;s... it&apos;s not impossible... Then... Dark Monk is not Dark Monk... Only an impostor...</text>
	<text id="1347">This prophecy is so exciting... I can&apos;t stop reading it over and over. It makes me cry every single time!!</text>
	<text id="1348">This... this character has taken the place of Dark Monk. He has deceived us all. And we, poor dummies, we believed him!! But who is he, who is this FunFrock???</text>
	<text id="1349">It is said the trail used to circle the crater and that folks came to gather crystals. Now, the road&apos;s blocked - and only a fool or a hero would dare venture there.</text>
	<text id="1350">This temple is dedicated to Dark Monk. He is the God of the Zeelichians and lives again! His Majesty promised to cancel the Zeelichian curse during the cult&apos;s next ceremony.</text>
	<text id="1351">Me, I declare this fellow... [hic!] I didn&apos;t trust him so much, [hic!!] I knew darn well we were all digging for nothing, hic!! If I&apos;d known, I&apos;d&apos;ve spent a little more time at Franckie&apos;s instead of digging [hic!]!</text>
	<text id="1352">At last we meet again, Twinsen! But this time, you are too late!! With the emperor&apos;s help, I succeeded in deceiving the Esmers. Ironic, isn&apos;t it? They mistook me for the reincarnation of Dark Monk and granted me divine powers that even I didn&apos;t possess. Thanks to those Esmers, these powers will be mine as soon as the moon collides with Twinsun!!</text>
	<text id="1353">I needed the wizards to operate the machine I built in the statue. It&apos;ll attract the Sendells&apos; energy from Twinsun&apos;s core, and release it in the explosion! The children were only a ploy to coerce the wizards&apos; obedience!!</text>
	<text id="1354">Even you a part of my plan, fool of a Quetch!! The statue is in fact an antenna! And I needed the four fragments to place it in its ceremonial position! Now, you will witness the destruction of your planet and my consecration as well! As soon as I activate the machine and the cosmic shock takes place, I will seize the Sendells&apos; energy. It will make me a God in flesh as well as in name!!!</text>
	<text id="1355">So you followed me, you miserable maggot!!! You didn&apos;t get the picture, did you? Now it&apos;s too late. In a few minutes, your planet will be destroyed, and its energy will make me the equivalent of a God!!! @ For annoying me with the sight of you yet again, I&apos;m going to sacrifice these children you love so dearly right in front of your eyes!!!</text>
	<text id="1356">Adieu!!!</text>
	<text id="1357">Thank you for saving us, Twinsen. It is FunFrock who has chained us to this machine. He is alive! He has come back!! He is impersonating Dark Monk and he wants to destroy Twinsun!!</text>
	<text id="1358">He is holding them prisoner in a cage like beasts. They&apos;re up there now, in the statue&apos;s head. The access gate&apos;s closed, but we&apos;ll help! All the magic at our disposal is going to be channeled into breaking that thing down!!! @ Let&apos;s do it!</text>
	<text id="1359">Bravo!!!</text>
	<text id="1360">Ready?</text>
	<text id="1361">Go!!!</text>
	<text id="1362">So, our Queen was right. The emperor lied to us all. He manipulated us all! All this to protect this impostor!!!</text>
	<text id="1363">Terrific!!! Thank you, Sendell. Without your help, I would have never succeeded!</text>
	<text id="1364">What do you mean?</text>
	<text id="1365">These people are great. They are generous and honest. It&apos;s about time the people of Zeelich and Twinsun finally met.</text>
	<text id="1366">Twinsen, the emerald moon just resumed its normal trajectory, Twinsun has been saved!!!!</text>
	<text id="1367">It is I who must thank you, you saved us!! Don&apos;t forget that we, the Sendells, are an integral part of Twinsun!!! I think that we should also thank the Esmers...</text>
	<text id="1368">Well, the reactor was much too powerful, even for us. If they had not come to destroy it, I am afraid we would not have succeeded!! You have unmasked FunFrock in front of their eyes, when they thought he was Dark Monk, their savior. Thanks to your intervention, they&apos;ve understood. That&apos;s why they came to our rescue!!!</text>
	<text id="1369">Did you say fireflies? Ugh...[sigh]</text>
	<text id="1370">The island of the Mosquibees</text>
	<text id="1371">The island of the volcano</text>
	<text id="1372">Do you know where the Mosquibee village is at?</text>
	<text id="1373">Do you know where I could find the Mosquibees?</text>
	<text id="1374">I asked Mr. Monk how to get to the Mosquibees, and he told me to ask you about the ferryman.</text>
	<text id="1375">I&apos;m trying to find the Mosquibees. Can you help me out?</text>
	<text id="1376">But, I am only trying to go to the Mosquibees...</text>
	<text id="1377">No thank you, honest!</text>
	<text id="1378">Hey! how can I find the Queen of the Mosquibees?</text>
	<text id="1379">I went shopping. Be back soon. Signed: your housemaid.</text>
	<text id="1380">What a weird painting, looks like a monster from the gas.</text>
	<text id="1381">Ugh, taste in home decor is rather lame.</text>
	<text id="1382">Dark Monk&apos;s chapel.</text>
	<text id="1383">I don&apos;t have enough gems.</text>
	<text id="1384">Hello</text>
	<text id="1385">Hi</text>
	<text id="1386">Hello</text>
	<text id="1387">Your Majesty, I&apos;ve come to free you, and ask you to open the door to the passage which leads to island CX. My planet&apos;s being threatened and I have to save it.</text>
	<text id="1388">&quot;You are entering the domain of the Wannies.&quot;</text>
	<text id="1389">Ferryman if you please, @ take me across the raging seas, @ for a few gems, I take your boat, @ I cannot swim, I cannot float!!</text>
	<text id="1390">You&apos;re at the Building Company, in front of the gem mine.</text>
	<text id="1391">You&apos;re at the ferryman&apos;s lane.</text>
	<text id="1392">You&apos;re in the village of the Wannies.</text>
	<text id="1393">Hello. Won&apos;t you come in and share our meal?</text>
	<text id="1394">So? How do you like my firefly tart?</text>
	<text id="1395">Dinner is served!</text>
	<text id="1396">Feeling better? Well, it&apos;s the first time I find somebody who does not like my tart!!</text>
	<text id="1397">Would you like another slice of tart?</text>
	<text id="1398">I hope the military are not going to come back and wreak havoc here. Since their passage, I haved a tough time finding fireflies for my tarts.</text>
	<text id="1399">He bothering me!!</text>
	<text id="1400">Whoever wants to cross the ocean of fire must pay the price. Four gems is the fare. @ Where do you want to go?</text>
	<text id="1401">Help me...</text>
	<text id="1402">Ah, thank you, thank you! I&apos;d fallen and couldn&apos;t get up. What can I do to thank you?</text>
	<text id="1403">She&apos;s locked up in the premises of the Building Company, the entrance of which is heavily guarded. But from the mine, you can access the nearest hangar. And from there, if you take the roof, you can reach the building where she&apos;s being held.</text>
	<text id="1404">Be careful Twinsen, all the soldiers are looking for you.</text>
	<text id="1405">Here, as a token of my gratitude, I&apos;m giving you this glove. It protects us from fire and lets us get the gems out of the molten lava without burning up.</text>
	<text id="1406">Here, to thank you, take this gem.</text>
	<text id="1407">Hey, pal! Say, if you bring me back a slice of tart, I&apos;ll tell you a pretty wacky secret.</text>
	<text id="1408">Oh, thanks a bunch, pal! Listen, this kid, he give me the key to the chapel. Here, take it. I&apos;ve had enough fun with it.</text>
	<text id="1409">That was one hummer of a tart! My boy, &apos;e sez that I shouldn&apos;t eat none &apos;cause it could make me sick. But that&apos;s all a bunch of hogwash. Phooey, I sez.</text>
	<text id="1410">Hi, pal! Hey, is that you who brought on all this military? They don&apos;t look all that strong, if you ask me. In my day, it was different. They fed us firefly tarts, that really built us up!!!</text>
	<text id="1411">Say, I&apos;ve heard that them Mosquibees got ambushed. Pretty sure they took shelter in the cave near the waterfall at the foot of the volcano.</text>
	<text id="1412">Very well. But first, being that you&apos;re a stranger, I must warn you.</text>
	<text id="1413">Once, long ago, our god, Dark Monk, condemned us, the people of Zeelich, to live forever on our planet which he then turned into hell so as to make it seem more of a real condemnation. Each of the four races received a fragment of a key. These must be reunited during a great ceremony. And when our people have atoned for their sins, Dark Monk will rid us of the curse and give Zeelich back its original appearance. Today, he&apos;s returned and we all await the next and last ceremony. Twinsen, do not dare interfere with the religious practice of our people.</text>
	<text id="1414">For that, you&apos;ll have to call on the ferryman&apos;s services. He provides the only communication between the islands and the under-gas. Go see my housemaid. She shall tell you how to proceed.</text>
	<text id="1415">But it&apos;s you who took our fragment. You don&apos;t realize what you have done. Listen carefully.</text>
	<text id="1416">The time of the ceremony is near. Dark Monk in person will chase away the monsters of the gas cloud when we reunite the four fragments for the last time.</text>
	<text id="1417">The time of the ceremony is near. Now that you have taken our fragment, Dark Monk will not chase the monsters of the gas or the cloud which blankets Zeelich!</text>
	<text id="1418">Oh, my, that&apos;s pretty far, no. You see, none of us have ever left our island or our beloved old mine.</text>
	<text id="1419">My mommy, she&apos;s helping Mr. Monk make Dark Monk come back. And then, when he&apos;s here, heads are gonna roll! It&apos;ll be so awesome!! My mommy&apos;s strong!!</text>
	<text id="1420">Waah!!!</text>
	<text id="1421">Of course, it&apos;s fairly simple. You have to pay him in gems if you want him to take you. But first you have to call him. To do that, you have to stand at the end of the ferryman&apos;s pier and call him with this song. Listen to me and don&apos;t forget.</text>
	<text id="1422">Ferryman if you please, take me across the raging seas, for a few gems, I take your boat, I cannot swim, I cannot float!!</text>
	<text id="1423">The Monk impatiently awaits the ceremony of the celebration. It&apos;s a major event for our entire population. It represents the end of the curse which lies heavily upon Zeelich. We shall at last resume the course of our lives on a hospitable planet, not in this forlorn place.</text>
	<text id="1424">Ah, yes, right. Only thing is, they don&apos;t live on this island, sir. You have to go to the wharf and call the ferryman. I&apos;ve never actually seen him, but this rumor has an air of truth. Ask the Monk, he&apos;ll be able to answer you.</text>
	<text id="1425">I&apos;m in a bind, I&apos;ve lost my glove in the mine. With it, I can catch the pieces of lava and the balls of fire, I can even pitch them back. Everybody has one, to extract gems.</text>
	<text id="1426">The Monk, he threw me out of his choir. It&apos;s not fair, I didn&apos;t do anything. So I stole the key to the chapel! So I boxed it in and gave it to the old man!</text>
	<text id="1427">I fish fireflies used to bake tarts. It&apos;s awfully good you know, a firefly tart.</text>
	<text id="1428">I can always look for gems around here, there are none. Nothing doing, they can only be found in the mine. And yet, I was told that they were easy to find on the other islands.</text>
	<text id="1429">I knew the Mosquibees live away from the rest, but they must&apos;ve done something pretty drastic for the emperor to send his army. It&apos;s being whispered they&apos;re looking for a criminal hostile to Dark Monk!!</text>
	<text id="1430">Hmmf! Lost my glove somewhere in the mine. Now I can&apos;t reach into the lava to grab up the gems.</text>
	<text id="1431">No time.</text>
	<text id="1432">Hi.</text>
	<text id="1433">Leave me alone.</text>
	<text id="1434">Hello.</text>
	<text id="1435">Twinsen!!</text>
	<text id="1436">You&apos;re very brave, but I&apos;ve got face the emperor. Soon I&apos;ll be transferred to his palace, and he&apos;ll come to interrogate me. So I suppose I&apos;ll just stay here. Here! Take the key to the passage! Go and save your people!!</text>
	<text id="1437">Hurry, Twinsen!! You have to penetrate to island CX. The entrance is behind our village! Use it! Quickly!</text>
	<text id="1438">Only you can stop the emperor and Dark Monk.</text>
	<text id="1439">Don&apos;t stay here! Escape while you still can!</text>
	<text id="1440">The Monk punished our buddy Johnny &apos;cause he lost the key to the chapel. Wasn&apos;t even true.</text>
	<text id="1441">Let&apos;s get this over with, so we can go and see the soldiers.</text>
	<text id="1442">As for me, I&apos;m real glad the Monk punished this Johnny. He had it coming he was always making fun of me.</text>
	<text id="1443">I sure hope the army wasted this Johnny. Or, better yet, maybe they fed him to the ferryman!!</text>
	<text id="1444">Look, this job is too much drudgery for us to want to talk about it!</text>
	<text id="1445">Here, there is no hope. All we do is dig. That&apos;s all.</text>
	<text id="1446">Watch out!!</text>
	<text id="1447">You don&apos;t have business here, get lost!!!</text>
	<text id="1448">Welcome to the Building Company, sir. If you&apos;re here to make a cash deposit, we can take care of it right away.</text>
	<text id="1449">Er... good day... sir... I&apos;m the manager of this institution. You were let in without an appointment? I take it then you&apos;re here to deposit an obscenely large sum of money?</text>
	<text id="1450">No, have mercy!!</text>
	<text id="1451">Easy, Twinsen, be careful. It&apos;s not the time to break this precious fragment!!</text>
	<text id="1452">Please leave now and close the door! Here, as we say, &quot;Idle hands make the Devil&apos;s workshop!!!&quot;</text>
	<text id="1453">Ferryman if you please, @ take me across the raging seas, @ for a few gems, I take your boat, @ I cannot swim, I cannot float!!</text>
	<text id="1454">The island of the volcano</text>
	<text id="1455">The island of the Wannies.</text>
	<text id="1456">I need your help. Dark Monk and the Emperor have built a reactor on Emerald moon. This reactor is going to hurl the moon toward my planet destroying life as we know it!! We don&apos;t have much time, Dark Monk promised to make this happen at the next ceremony.</text>
	<text id="1457">The control center is on island CX. The only way in is the passage which starts from the under-gas. Fortunately, the rebels from above told me the local rebels would help me.</text>
	<text id="1458">I don&apos;t have enough gems.</text>
	<text id="1459">Hello</text>
	<text id="1460">Hello</text>
	<text id="1461">I&apos;m staying here.</text>
	<text id="1462">Tourism is really big around here!</text>
	<text id="1463">I&apos;ve got to speak to your Queen!</text>
	<text id="1464">Hey, Leave me alone!</text>
	<text id="1465">You are at the village of the Mosquibees.</text>
	<text id="1466">Whoever wants to cross the ocean of fire must pay the price. Four gems is the fare. @ Where do you want to go?</text>
	<text id="1467">It&apos;s our secret identification sign. He just might be speaking the truth your Majesty.</text>
	<text id="1468">Don&apos;t you have any proof of your good faith? An identification sign, an object?</text>
	<text id="1469">My dissident friend confirmed that you are in fact a Twinsunian. While on a mission to your planet he saw the actions of the Emperor&apos;s soldiers. We know that Dark Monk and the Emperor have lied to us, as well as kidnapping your wizards and children. But you, what are you doing here?</text>
	<text id="1470">And what can we do?</text>
	<text id="1471">Do you have proof?</text>
	<text id="1472">You mustn&apos;t try to prove your allegations like that. I am waiting for you to find a more intelligent way of going about it!</text>
	<text id="1473">But he is not a Mosquibee. You will have to prove your courage and pass the test of truth before you can become one of us... Only then will we help you.</text>
	<text id="1474">Listen to me Twinsunian! You must seize a weapon hidden behind one of the doors! Do what you can, there are no other rules!</text>
	<text id="1475">Excellent Twinsen! You just grabbed the blowtron! This weapon makes you our equal. You are now welcome in the village of the Mosquibees and we will help you reach the island CX. I not only own the key to the passage which leads there, I will also open the doors for you as soon as we arrive!!</text>
	<text id="1476">Well, Twinsunian, I am waiting...</text>
	<text id="1477">On guard! The Emperor&apos;s soldiers!! They&apos;re attacking!! There all over us!! Your Majesty, we can&apos;t hold them, they&apos;re already in the village, we must retreat!! You must leave now or be captured.</text>
	<text id="1478">What are you doing here?</text>
	<text id="1479">OK, Hang on!!</text>
	<text id="1480">Ah, Twinsen!! With the arrival of these paratroopers, I am afraid to see our fragment might fall into the hands of the emperor. By the way, If you know how to throw back the balls of fire with your hands, try to grab some.</text>
	<text id="1481">The Queen has been captured, but some of our people managed to escape. They took shelter in the cave of the volcano.</text>
	<text id="1482">Otringal</text>
	<text id="1483">The island of the celebration</text>
	<text id="1484">Nowhere, I&apos;m staying here.</text>
	<text id="1485">Hello.</text>
	<text id="1486">Oh Batbarf, I don&apos;t have enough Zlitos.</text>
	<text id="1487">OK!</text>
	<text id="1488">&quot;Mr. Kurtz - Retired Colonel - Specializing in non-scientific sciences&quot;</text>
	<text id="1489">And, today, nobody knows where the heck the fragment is. That&apos;s why everyone is digging all over the place!! But why didn&apos;t he leave any notes?</text>
	<text id="1490">&quot;Roger de la Fontaine - Franco Burgermaster&quot;</text>
	<text id="1491">I am not interested.</text>
	<text id="1492">It&apos;s locked.</text>
	<text id="1493">You are at the village of the Francos.</text>
	<text id="1494">You are at the gazogem refinery.</text>
	<text id="1495">You are at the harbor of the Francos.</text>
	<text id="1496">But, I found it, you know, your fragment!!!</text>
	<text id="1497">For 5 Zlitos, I can take you somewheres. Where would you like to go bud?</text>
	<text id="1498">The fare I am charging is 5 Zlitos. Where would you like to be going sir?</text>
	<text id="1499">Wackos! A bunch of wackos live in this village. Even the birds are stupid. Especially this owl who came to roost here. It quietly took possession of this niche, and now it&apos;s his home.</text>
	<text id="1500">Biddy, Biddy!!</text>
	<text id="1501">Taking the size of the island, its geological structure and wind direction into account. I have concocted a potion which should allow me to precisely determine the location of the fragment! Unfortunately...I uh, lost the vial.</text>
	<text id="1502">Roger de la Fontaine, he was my brother. He was the local burgermaster you know, who was responsible of our fragment. Roger, he kept hiding the fragment somewhere without telling anyone, until the accident... Pity, he was eaten by a monster from the gas.</text>
	<text id="1503">I don&apos;t think so. Anyhow, the closet that he had ornamented with little stuffed monsters from the gas, well, it is locked... Besides, I lost the key. Then...</text>
	<text id="1504">Holy Santa Maria!, somebody really ought to find this fragment.</text>
	<text id="1505">Yeah, sure whatever, your the twelfth person to lay this on me... I didn&apos;t believe the first eleven so why should I believe you?</text>
	<text id="1506">I&apos;m sure it&apos;s not even true...</text>
	<text id="1507">Since everyone started looking for our fragment, I&apos;ve turned the bazaar into a treasure hunter&apos;s shop.</text>
	<text id="1508">If you want to buy something from me, you just have to stand in front of it and do &quot;ACTION&quot;.</text>
	<text id="1509">A pick-ax costs 20 Zlitos.</text>
	<text id="1510">10 Life points cost 20 Zlitos.</text>
	<text id="1511">10 Magic points cost 20 Zlitos.</text>
	<text id="1512">This frying pan is not for sale, it&apos;s only for the decor.</text>
	<text id="1513">You have to be crazy to believe all these stories of fragment hunting. Me, I think Roger lost it at home before getting eaten by the monster. What are you gonna do?, at least its good for business.</text>
	<text id="1514">Yeah it&apos;s pretty serious, this here story!! It better be found this er...fragment. &apos;Cause no fragment, no ceremony, and no paradise!! Bah, I don&apos;t give a hoot, I&apos;ve got myself a vineyard... Come on, mister, just a snort?</text>
	<text id="1515">I&apos;m certain our fragment&apos;s buried here. Obviously, must be hidden under the grass. I mean the burgermaster couldn&apos;t have buried it under the rock, am I right?</text>
	<text id="1516">I, well, er, well I dig here because it&apos;s just as good as somewhere else. Everybody here digs, why not me? Heh? And why not here?</text>
	<text id="1517">This Roger de la Fontaine, he used to go pretty close to the gas. Could well be where he hid it, our fragment!!</text>
	<text id="1518">Because of this lost fragment nonsense, everyone is looking for it. So they leave their little rug rats with me all day long. They just don&apos;t stop bawling...I&apos;m going to look for another job soon.</text>
	<text id="1519">I won&apos;t talk!! My parents put me here to punish me &apos;cause I lost the key to our house. It&apos;s wasn&apos;t my fault, that thief of an owl that took it from me. That filthy mechanical owl!! And it&apos;s not a loser like you who is going to help me!!</text>
	<text id="1520">Waah!!</text>
	<text id="1521">Waah!!</text>
	<text id="1522">Waah!!</text>
	<text id="1523">Waah!!</text>
	<text id="1524">No way! I&apos;m going to stop you!!</text>
	<text id="1525">Hello.</text>
	<text id="1526">Twinsen...Oh Twinsen, it&apos;s me, Sendell!!! Twinsen, a cosmic cataclysm is on its way!!! The moon has started to move! Soon, it is going to hurl itself against Twinsun, destroying our planet!!! You must stop Dark Monk and prevent him from using that infernal machine he built inside the statue. With it, he could attract and steal the energy that we could use to stop the moon!!! You must get the four key fragments, which are used in the ceremony and are protected by the Esmer races. With these fragments the statue of Dark Monk will emerge from the crater!! Once you stop Dark Monk, you will have to come back to Twinsun and, in the Well of the Sendells, I will help you stop the moon!!</text>
	<text id="1527">Here you are at last! I was waiting for you Twinsunian, Dark Monk told me a lot about you!!</text>
	<text id="1528">It&apos;s over Twinsen, you lost. To make your defeat even more bitter, I am going to tell you the truth. @ With all these beliefs, I was not master of my own planet, people had only ears for Dark Monk&apos;s priests!! One day, a stranger landed on Zeelich and offered to pass himself off as Dark Monk. Together, we spread the belief that he was to fulfill the great prophecy. Of course, this is far from the truth. @ I don&apos;t know why, but Dark Monk wants to appropriate the magical energy contained in your planet. And, since I want to become the master of Zeelich, we made a deal!!!</text>
	<text id="1529">Twinsunian, Dark Monk is unbeatable. In his statue, he has built a machine capable of storing the magical energy that he intends to steal from your planet!!! @ My agents went to Twinsun to kidnap your wizards since we needed them to attract the energy from your planet to Zeelich. But we were forced to kidnap the children because the wizards refused to cooperate!! @ You were our only obstacle. But now, we have won. The destruction of Twinsun and the use of the machine will intervene during the next ceremony. And you cannot prevent me from triggering the lunar reactors!!!</text>
	<text id="1530">Who are you? This is the emperor&apos;s personal shuttle! You have no business here!!!</text>
	<text id="1531">Heeeeeee!!!</text>
	<text id="1532">But... who are you?</text>
	<text id="1533">How did you know I would be coming here?</text>
	<text id="1534">Ah, here you are at last! I was beginning to wonder if I would see you today.</text>
	<text id="1535">I, my lad, am an assassin that Dark Monk&apos;s paid to eliminate you. But, looking at you, it seems I must have the wrong fellow. The lad I hunt is a warrior so fierce, that Dark Monk himself fears him!</text>
	<text id="1536">Laddie, you are as savvy as a monster from the gas. When you established contact with Johnny Rocket, my spies were there. We have followed you since. I knew that you wanted to go down to the under-gas. Thus I waited here to strike. But enough said. Now, lad, prepare yourself to die!!</text>
	<text id="1537">Ferryman if you please, @ take me across the raging seas, @ for a few gems, I take your boat, @ I cannot swim, I cannot float!!</text>
	<text id="1538">No thank you.</text>
	<text id="1539">The island of the Mosquibees.</text>
	<text id="1540">The island of the Wannies.</text>
	<text id="1541">You are on the island below the Volcano of the Celebration.</text>
	<text id="1542">Yes, but I have no clue where the others are.</text>
	<text id="1543">I gotta find the Queen. Her Highness has the key of passage to island CX!!</text>
	<text id="1544">I don&apos;t have enough gems.</text>
	<text id="1545">Hello</text>
	<text id="1546">Hi</text>
	<text id="1547">Whoever wants to cross the ocean of fire must pay the price. Four gems is the fare. @ Where do you want to go?</text>
	<text id="1548">Twinsen, you managed to escape?</text>
	<text id="1549">The Queen has been captured, as well as a few of our dissident friends. By now, they must be locked up in the jails of the Building Company. The cells are in the administrative building, next to the warehouse.</text>
	<text id="1550">As for us, we stay here until things cool down.</text>
	<text id="1551">Our village is now half destroyed. I don&apos;t know what&apos;s going to happen to us.</text>
	<text id="1552">Lucky we knew where this hideout was. Without it, we would have been jailed, like the others.</text>
</texts>
