<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<texts>
	<text id="2">Ferryman if you please, @ take me across the raging seas, @ for a few gems, I take your boat, @ I cannot swim, I cannot float!!</text>
	<text id="8">The island of the volcano</text>
	<text id="9">The island of the Wannies.</text>
	<text id="10">You are at the village of the Mosquibees.</text>
	<text id="15">What are you doing here?</text>
	<text id="16">OK, Hang on!!</text>
	<text id="20">I need your help. Dark Monk and the Emperor have built a reactor on Emerald moon. This reactor is going to hurl the moon toward my planet destroying life as we know it!! We don&apos;t have much time, Dark Monk promised to make this happen at the next ceremony.</text>
	<text id="21">The control center is on island CX. The only way in is the passage which starts from the under-gas. Fortunately, the rebels from above told me the local rebels would help me.</text>
	<text id="25">Tourism is really big around here!</text>
	<text id="26">I&apos;ve got to speak to your Queen!</text>
	<text id="27">Hey, Leave me alone!</text>
	<text id="29">Otringal</text>
	<text id="30">The island of the celebration</text>
	<text id="31">Nowhere, I&apos;m staying here.</text>
	<text id="32">Hello.</text>
	<text id="33">Oh Batbarf, I don&apos;t have enough Zlitos.</text>
	<text id="34">OK!</text>
	<text id="35">Mr. Kurtz - Retired Colonel - Specializing in non-scientific sciences&quot;</text>
	<text id="39">And, today, nobody knows where the heck the fragment is. That&apos;s why everyone is digging all over the place!! But why didn&apos;t he leave any notes?</text>
	<text id="40">Roger de la Fontaine - Franco Burgermaster&quot;</text>
	<text id="41">I am not interested.</text>
	<text id="42">It&apos;s locked.</text>
	<text id="43">You are at the village of the Francos.</text>
	<text id="44">You are at the gazogem refinery.</text>
	<text id="45">You are at the harbor of the Francos.</text>
	<text id="46">But, I found it, you know, your fragment!!!</text>
	<text id="48">Biddy, Biddy!!</text>
	<text id="53">Wackos! A bunch of wackos live in this village. Even the birds are stupid. Especially this owl who came to roost here. It quietly took possession of this niche, and now it&apos;s his home.</text>
	<text id="63">Waah!!</text>
	<text id="68">Waah!!</text>
	<text id="70">No way! I&apos;m going to stop you!!</text>
	<text id="73">Hello.</text>
	<text id="74">But... who are you?</text>
	<text id="75">How did you know I would be coming here?</text>
	<text id="78">Ferryman if you please, @ take me across the raging seas, @ for a few gems, I take your boat, @ I cannot swim, I cannot float!!</text>
	<text id="82">No thank you.</text>
	<text id="83">The island of the Mosquibees.</text>
	<text id="85">The island of the Wannies.</text>
	<text id="86">You are on the island below the Volcano of the Celebration.</text>
	<text id="87">Twinsen, rush to the downtown pharmacy and find a cure for the Dino-Fly ! He has just crashed in the garden and looks injured.</text>
	<text id="88">You&apos;ll need a baggage check to claim anything stored here.</text>
	<text id="89">Ah, Mr. Twinsen. Your friend Baldino left me a crate for you. It&apos;s in the basement, a brown crate with a big label on top. Just follow the arrows, bring it back here, and I&apos;ll open it. If you need help, ask my colleagues downstairs.</text>
	<text id="90">You again Mr. Twinsen? But I don&apos;t have anything left to give you!</text>
	<text id="91">Zoé&apos;s diary @ @ Dear diary: Today, I tell you the story of the Adventure that I had with Twinsen under the dictatorship of Dr. FunFrock: @ It was long, long ago. This Dr. FunFrock, a quetch, was oppressing the populace with terrible violence thanks to the techniques of cloning and mutation, but mostly through his mastery of teleportation. His power dominated everyone! He even had the northern hemisphere evacuated in order to execute his plan. This plan consisted of a gigantic drilling operation aimed at reaching the heart of Twinsun and grabbing the magic energy of the Sendells. Without the providential intervention of Twinsen who eliminated FunFrock, this demented project would have resulted in the implosion of the planet and the destruction of the Stellar Entity living in its center. @ Twinsen had hardly practiced Magic since this &quot;Day of Triumph&quot;, when Sendell exceptionally entrusted him with his immense Power ...&quot; @</text>
	<text id="92">He left work? Hmm! I&apos;ll bet he went to play his guitar by the cliffs again!</text>
	<text id="93">Hi, Twinsen. Far as I&apos;m concerned, I like it when it rains. The grass gets nicely thick. Makes it taste better.</text>
	<text id="94">Excuse him, he is a nice Grobo. You know, he only gives himself airs.</text>
	<text id="95">You showed up at the right time. The door at the top of the stairs is jammed. We need to find a way to go upstairs to release it and free the bell which protects your tunic.</text>
	<text id="96">What? The lighthouse keeper? Ah, no! No, no I didn&apos;t see him!</text>
	<text id="97">Yeah, actually I saw him pass by a while back. He was holding his guitar, heading for the cliffs.</text>
	<text id="98">Here, sir, we have a collection devoted to the great Twinsen and to the development of Magic on the planet. Don&apos;t hesitate to educate yourself!</text>
	<text id="99">Since the good weather&apos;s back, my bird friends are much less on edge. Oh, and be careful, there&apos;s a weirdo hiding behind the trees.</text>
	<text id="100">Mr. Twinsen! Free me, quick!! I am Raph! You know, the lighthouse keeper!! I&apos;ve been caught by the Tralü, he wants to turn me into a rabbibunny-melba.</text>
	<text id="102">Waaah!!!</text>
	<text id="103">OK, I&apos;ll buy it!</text>
	<text id="104">No, I am not interested.</text>
	<text id="105">But I have a customer who works for a healing wizard named Ker&apos;aooc. He lives on Desert Island. According to my friend, he treats everybody for everything.</text>
	<text id="106">I don&apos;t know this character!</text>
	<text id="107">Thank you for releasing the door, Twinsen. Use your tunic with wisdom.</text>
	<text id="108">Hey!... you know, you look like the guy in the picture!</text>
	<text id="109">I am not from here, you see... I don&apos;t know him.</text>
	<text id="110">Geez, the counter-clerk is as smart as ever, he never recognizes me. What&apos;s more, he always charges me admission.</text>
	<text id="111">I want to get back my Tunic and my Sendell&apos;s Medallion.</text>
	<text id="112">Thank you, Mr. Twinsen! I was rehearsing a new tune when this filthy Tralü chewed up my guitar. Besides, it looks like he got others before me!! Well, back to the lighthouse, otherwise I&apos;ll get in hot water.</text>
	<text id="113">This storm...I wanted to get rid of it but the lighthouse was closed and I can&apos;t find the keeper anywhere. Only he could help me reach the top of the building where I have the view I need to utter a conjuration. It&apos;s the only way to stop this storm that neutralizes the island. But I need the lighthouse keeper.</text>
	<text id="114">Please, don&apos;t touch the container on the stove. OK? It contains a terrible creature!</text>
	<text id="115">Hmm...er... don&apos;t mention it please, it&apos;s only... well just a kind of a small personal experiment.</text>
	<text id="116">To my future descendants: I have lent to Miss Bloop&apos;s private museum, the Medallion and the Ancestral Tunic which rightfully belong to you. Signed: Twinsen.&quot;</text>
	<text id="117">Hello?</text>
	<text id="118">Hello! Twinsen? Baldino here! How are you? Looks like this transmitter works! If you swing by, I have a portable radio to give you. Also, I will have the proto-pack finished soon. It will allow you to fly in complete safety. Over.</text>
	<text id="119">The car&apos;s not working. Zoé said there&apos;s still a part she needs. She asked Baldino to make it for her.</text>
	<text id="120">This is the text of the ancient prophecy. It is intended for my family, in case my descendants are also called by Sendell. Hopefully, I&apos;ll never need it again. @ And that&apos;s all I&apos;ve got left from the house that FunFrock razed.</text>
	<text id="121">Know, sir, that I alone have the right to press this button!! You must pay to enter!</text>
	<text id="122">Personnel only.&quot;</text>
	<text id="123">I&apos;ve got enough problems without you touching stuff...so get lost!</text>
	<text id="125">Hey mister! If you want, I can carry your crate up to the exit for 102 little Kashes!</text>
	<text id="127">Go back upstairs. You&apos;ll get your crate, I&apos;m sending it directly to the reception!</text>
	<text id="128">Ouch!</text>
	<text id="129">Hi, Twinsen. With this storm, I&apos;ve got lots of customers and I don&apos;t have one minute to myself.</text>
	<text id="130">I don&apos;t have the time, Twinsen. Ask Luc, the boss!</text>
	<text id="131">Insert 5 Kashes if you want 10 Magic points.</text>
	<text id="132">Insert 5 Kashes if you want 10 Life points.</text>
	<text id="133">If you want Life or Magic points, you can get some from one of the vending machines on the bar.</text>
	<text id="134">Better ask his buddies Pat or Fab. They&apos;re upstairs. Haven&apos;t moved since it started raining.</text>
	<text id="135">Howdy kiddo! How goes it?</text>
	<text id="136">He said he wanted to practice a new piece on his guitar. He usually hides out on the cliffs for peace and quiet. But not this long usually.</text>
	<text id="137">Thanks for having freed my buddy Raph, kiddo. Without you, his goose was cooked for sure.</text>
	<text id="138">Raph? With him and Fab, we put together a killer combo to play some funky rock&apos;n rave! But since he didn&apos;t show at the last rehearsal, no way I can tell you where he is now!</text>
	<text id="139">Cool!! That music rocks! Don&apos;t you think?</text>
	<text id="140">If you go to the cellar, be [hic!]... be careful! I been there my own self... just to get in a couple snorts on the sly: well there&apos;s a [hic!] there&apos;s a hole smack in the middle. Yessir, smack in the middle! Oh, that falllll, yowza!</text>
	<text id="142">Insert 5 Kashes if you want to listen to a title:</text>
	<text id="143">Honey Bee&quot;</text>
	<text id="144">LBA&apos;s Theme&quot;</text>
	<text id="145">The Empire&quot;</text>
	<text id="146">What a story, those guys showing up from the Emerald Moon, what a story!</text>
	<text id="147">Darn, I had seen some pink grobos before, but green chaps from outer space, that&apos;s a first!</text>
	<text id="148">These &quot;Esmers&quot; look quite nice, they ask lots of questions though. Everything interests them.</text>
	<text id="149">Thief!</text>
	<text id="150">I sure dig those &quot;extra-twinsunians&quot;. Their civilization is more advanced than ours, but they are still way cool.</text>
	<text id="152">Not being from here, I find your island rather strange. I don&apos;t understand why your Weather Wizard does nothing about this storm. By the way, do you know that it&apos;s possible to search the garbage cans, the vases and the closets by standing in front of them and doing &quot;ACTION&quot;?</text>
	<text id="153">Sorry, I am not from here.</text>
	<text id="155">But I have an idea how you can help your friend!</text>
	<text id="156">Thank you!</text>
	<text id="157">Waiter!</text>
	<text id="158">Waiter!</text>
	<text id="159">Twinsen, you have no business being here!</text>
	<text id="161">The foul weather prevents the boats from leaving the harbor. There&apos;s nothing to do, all maritime activity is paralyzed. Let me tell you, Mr. Twinsen, only the Weather Wizard could set things straight!!</text>
	<text id="162">What?? Very funny!! Now this good-for-nothing abandons the lighthouse right in the middle of the storm! What a shame!!</text>
	<text id="164">Don&apos;t touch that! I &apos;m trying to create an enchanted ring and this pot must not boil. Once I get myself an pearl of incandescence, I &apos;ll be able to call the lightning!</text>
	<text id="166">I freed him!</text>
	<text id="167">I just bumped into the keeper who was going back to the lighthouse. He told me that a true hero had just saved him from a voracious monster.</text>
	<text id="168">Ah yes! It is on Desert Island. You&apos;ll find it easely, the entry is inside the cemetery !</text>
	<text id="169">Bravo! And now, if you appreciate Great Art, let&apos;s meet at the lighthouse. You&apos;ll see what you&apos;ll see!</text>
	<text id="170">I am updating the works of my defunct son. Certain plans here date back from the time when he rebuilt the island&apos;s network of sewers.</text>
	<text id="172">Hey, this looks like a map. But I can&apos;t read it!</text>
	<text id="173">Here we have a very instructive map of the sewers. Before you can consult it, you must wait until I restore it. For that, I need a vial of gallic acid. Unfortunately, there&apos;s none left on the island.</text>
	<text id="174">Yes, that&apos;s exactly what I needed. I am going to use it on the map of the sewers.</text>
	<text id="175">Hello Twinsen!</text>
	<text id="176">Please, Mr. Twinsen, go get your fetching little costume and your magic ball. Be our hero again! Come back to save me from the Tralü. I&apos;m scared he&apos;s gonna eat me!!</text>
	<text id="178">Help!</text>
	<text id="179">You can board as soon as the storm is over.</text>
	<text id="180">Last time I saw him, he was hanging around in town.</text>
	<text id="181">Welcome to the Inter-islands Ferry, Mr. Twinsen!</text>
	<text id="184">This rain, will it ever end! Between my kids who were supposed to go on a field trip and my oldest son who keeps forgetting his umbrella...I hope that they&apos;re not outside in this weather.</text>
	<text id="185">Personally, I don&apos;t know where he is, but go look at the pharmacy. His sister might be able to help you.</text>
	<text id="187">Hello.</text>
	<text id="188">Hi.</text>
	<text id="190">By graduating from magic school, I&apos;ve earned this horn that I can use to treat Dino-Fly.</text>
	<text id="192">If you are lost, go back and get your holomap.</text>
	<text id="193">Hey!, we need some music here!</text>
	<text id="194">I am looking for the lighthouse keeper.</text>
	<text id="197">It&apos;s locked.</text>
	<text id="198">Good day, Master</text>
	<text id="200">Aha! a sign from Sendell. They are venerated by all the wizards.</text>
	<text id="201">I&apos;m staying here.</text>
	<text id="202">I don&apos;t have enough Kashes.</text>
	<text id="204">Could you help me find the school of magic?</text>
	<text id="267">Strange, this looks like a keyhole.</text>
	<text id="288">If you&apos;d care to purchase something, you just have to stand in front of it and do &quot;ACTION&quot;.</text>
	<text id="289">Go ahead, Mr. Twinsen. It&apos;s your property, isn&apos;t it?</text>
	<text id="290">A Nitro-Meca-Penguin costs 4 Kashes.</text>
	<text id="291">I heard he likes to &quot;seek inspiration&quot; by &quot;The Cliffs of the Woodbridge&quot;. That place is dangerous, if half of what I&apos;ve heard about the Tralü&apos;s for real. Don&apos;t go if you are unarmed.</text>
	<text id="292">10 Life points! Cool!</text>
	<text id="293">10 Magic points! All right!</text>
	<text id="294">Three darts cost 4 Kashes.</text>
	<text id="295">Don&apos;t do that, you fool, it&apos;s going to blow up!</text>
	<text id="296">Nobody touches the cash register!</text>
	<text id="297">Waiter!</text>
	<text id="299">I am going to see the Dino-Fly, it just landed behind the house. Don&apos;t forget that you can change the perspective by pressing &quot;ENTER&quot;.</text>
	<text id="301">Get out of the way!!</text>
	<text id="303">Oh what a fall, I&apos;m hurt badly. Under normal conditions, I could have taken you for a spin in the air. But this time, you will have to treat me first.</text>
	<text id="305">Oh! I don&apos;t know where he is. But if he&apos;d done his job, I&apos;d have seen his light and wouldn&apos;t have crashed.</text>
	<text id="312">Hey, a portrait of Sendell! They must have used my descriptions to make it.</text>
	<text id="313">Cross-section of Twinsun. @ @ 1: Sendell @ @ 2: Well of Sendell @ @ 3: Temple of Bù @ @</text>
	<text id="315">Vial which once contained the Clear Water. &quot;</text>
	<text id="317">Rock from the Temple of Bù.&quot;</text>
	<text id="318">Aha !, Sendell&apos;s Medallion and my Ancestral Tunic.</text>
	<text id="323">What a pain these sewers! What a stink and I still have oodles of manhole covers to update. Phew!! I have had it up to here!!</text>
	<text id="324">Well, I am certain he is not in the sewers, I would have seen him.</text>
	<text id="327">Safeguard Street&quot;</text>
	<text id="328">Green Corulla Street&quot;</text>
	<text id="330">Book of Bù. It allows me to speak with the animals of Twinsun.&quot;</text>
	<text id="331">Horn of Gawley.&quot;</text>
	<text id="333">Sorry, but I don&apos;t have anything for a Dino-Fly.</text>
	<text id="334">Hello.</text>
	<text id="335">Infortunately, he&apos;s disappeared, Mr. Twinsen! I hope he hasn&apos;t gone on another of his strolls on the cliffs! One of these days it might be nasty, with all these rumors about the Tralü...</text>
	<text id="336">I don&apos;t understand why the lighthouse is closed and turned off. What could my fiancé Raph, be doing? By the way, Mr. Twinsen, did you know you can jump over the rocks if you are trapped ?</text>
	<text id="338">If you are interested in an item, stand in front of it and do &quot;ACTION&quot;.</text>
	<text id="339">I&apos;m looking for something to cure my injured Dino-fly.</text>
	<text id="340">Personally, I have nothing for your Dino-Fly, but the client said she could help you.</text>
	<text id="341">Here&apos;s the deal. I will tell you how to treat your Dino-Fly, if you would bring back my umbrella. Use your smarts but remember that, in life, haste makes waste...</text>
	<text id="343">Ah you are so kind. Go see Ker&apos;aooc the healer on my behalf on Desert Island. I work for him and, believe me, he knows tricks that would cure anything, even a Dino-Fly...</text>
	<text id="345">You know, even though he is my brother, I don&apos;t give a hoot about his whereabouts, this lazy bum thinks about nothing but playing his guitar on the cliffs.</text>
	<text id="346">I don&apos;t know. I live on Desert Island.</text>
	<text id="349">Don&apos;t touch my cash register!</text>
	<text id="351">Mr. Twinsen! Could you tell me why you&apos;re following me?!</text>
	<text id="352">The umbrella please.</text>
	<text id="353">Give me my tunic back!</text>
	<text id="354">Errr, ... nothing. See ya.</text>
	<text id="355">To knock you out!</text>
	<text id="356">But that&apos;s my umb... Oh !!! Excuse me... I thought it was mine. Boohooo, I&apos;m so embarrassed... I keep making mistakes...</text>
	<text id="357">But, Mr. Twinsen, I assure you that I don&apos;t have your tunic. Maybe you should look at home.</text>
	<text id="358">Help!!</text>
	<text id="360">Raph ? Ah yeah, he has set up a super combo with his buddies Pat and Fab. But I don&apos;t know where he is.</text>
	<text id="362">Not again. What do you want from me now, Mr. Twinsen?</text>
	<text id="363">Thief!</text>
	<text id="364">The price of admission is 15 Kashes! Interested?</text>
	<text id="367">Unbelievable, this whole extratwinsunians scare. The storm I chased off has let them land here among us. The second I have less work on my hands, I&apos;ll have to go see what they&apos;re up to.</text>
	<text id="369">Diploma of Elementary-Weather Magic. The Wizard Bersimon has proven his talents as a master of the elements. He has reached the rank of Grand Master of sea winds and tornadoes. &quot;</text>
	<text id="370">To the glory of Dr. FunFrock.&quot;. This bust makes an excellent target.</text>
	<text id="371">I really like this image of my trusty Dino-Fly.&quot;</text>
	<text id="372">Twinsen, your performance was exemplary; here&apos;s your reward, this slate. It allows you to memorize images that you see, such as maps.</text>
	<text id="373">Bravo!!</text>
	<text id="374">Aahhh, thank you! I think I can fly now and take you where you want.</text>
	<text id="376">Where do you want to go, Twinsen?</text>
	<text id="377">Hi Mr. Twinsen!</text>
	<text id="378">No school for me today. I&apos;d love to find the Tralü and do it in. &apos;Cause if I make the Tralü disappear, I&apos;ll become a hero and they will erect me a whole museum!!</text>
	<text id="379">I don&apos;t know where he is, but his buddies are at the pub &quot;Chez Luc&quot;.</text>
	<text id="382">Dome of the Slate.&quot;</text>
	<text id="383">Ruins of the old citadel.&quot;</text>
	<text id="386">Say Twinsen, did you ever see that Tralü? They say it&apos;s a monster that lives in the cliffs above Lupin-Bourg. If you take a walk up there, don&apos;t forget to carry a weapon. I mean your magic ball!</text>
	<text id="387">I don&apos;t know him very well, but try asking around at &quot;Chez Luc,&quot; that&apos;s his big hangout.</text>
	<text id="388">Hey, did you really destroy the Tralü? This monster really existed? Hail to you, may you be prosperous and may the Sendells protect your descendants!</text>
	<text id="390">I&apos;m still looking for a cure. Don&apos;t worry, I&apos;ll find one.</text>
	<text id="393">But I saw the keeper! He&apos;s being held prisoner inside a cave under the cliff! I&apos;ve got to get him free!</text>
	<text id="394">Hello Mr. Twinsen.</text>
	<text id="395">Master, how do you explain a storm in this season?</text>
	<text id="396">Could you help me treat my injured Dino-Fly ?</text>
	<text id="397">Why don&apos;t you read the posters. And if you are interested in a destination, you tell me.</text>
	<text id="398">Just looking.</text>
	<text id="401">What can I do for you?</text>
	<text id="402">For 10 Kashes, wher...where do you want to go?</text>
	<text id="403">The weather&apos;s improving. Now the kids can go on their class outing.</text>
	<text id="404">Hi!</text>
	<text id="405">A portrait of me, back when I was charged with the power of Sendell...</text>
	<text id="406">Twinsen, what are you doing? I am counting on you to take care of the Dino-Fly, and milord is seeking adventures in the underground instead. It&apos;s beyond your control, you have to play the hero!</text>
	<text id="407">All right Zoé, I&apos;ll take you back.</text>
	<text id="408">Not through there.</text>
	<text id="409">When on Desert Island, visit the Temple of Bù, an eventful episode in the history of Twinsen.&quot;</text>
	<text id="412">Welcome, Mr. Twinsen!</text>
	<text id="413">Hello miss.</text>
	<text id="415">Pfew, I&apos;m totally exhausted moving all these crates.</text>
	<text id="417">Hello !</text>
	<text id="420">How&apos;re you doing, Dino buddy?</text>
	<text id="421">So, for 8 Kashes, where do I drop you?</text>
	<text id="422">Let&apos;s go to the lighthouse!</text>
	<text id="423">To Woodbridge island.</text>
	<text id="424">Hang on!</text>
	<text id="425">Beach headland.&quot;</text>
	<text id="426">Lupin-Bourg.&quot;</text>
	<text id="427">Ridge of the Flowers Circle.&quot;</text>
	<text id="428">Cliffs of the Woodbridge.&quot;</text>
	<text id="429">Lighthouse at the end of the island.&quot;</text>
	<text id="430">The Esmers should come here. It feels so good to look for mushrooms. By the way, I wouldn&apos;t try to go swimming, it gets deep very rapidly.</text>
	<text id="432">By the way, don&apos;t forget that the trajectory of your magic ball changes with your behavior!</text>
	<text id="434">OK by me!</text>
	<text id="435">I&apos;m not interested.</text>
	<text id="436">Sorry, but I&apos;ve forbidden roof access since my colleague from Citadel Island had legal issues with a customer who took a bad dive in the cellar of his bar!</text>
	<text id="437">Howdy.</text>
	<text id="438">Your reputation has hopped from island to island to reach me, Twinsen. You are the hero of this planet and you must know that the Esmers invite the wizards to come and study their planet of origin. Watch out, there&apos;s something fishy.</text>
	<text id="439">Well, what&apos;ve you learned?</text>
	<text id="440">Hello, sir.</text>
	<text id="441">I&apos;m sorry that the healer Ker&apos;aooc is away. When he&apos;ll be back is anyone&apos;s guess. If it&apos;s an emergency, try the School of Magic.</text>
	<text id="443">There is a top secret exchange program, currently reserved for the wizards. Come discover our science and civilization, and show us your Magic in return. You&apos;ll get rich in knowledge and experience. Don&apos;t mention it to your School of Magic yet, it&apos;s too early ... they would not understand.</text>
	<text id="445">Welcome, Twinsen. I&apos;d be honored to have you study with us. But even though you once saved our world, you&apos;ll still have to pass the same tests as the other students.</text>
	<text id="446">Do you wish to join our school?</text>
	<text id="447">Inscription fee is 120 Kashes. Are you ready to start right away?</text>
	<text id="449">Hello</text>
	<text id="450">I would like to treat my Dino-fly first!</text>
	<text id="451">Now that the clouds are gone, I can finally enjoy our twin sunshine. You know, I heard there&apos;s an oasis in the desert where there&apos;s this giant turtle. I&apos;d love to go there...</text>
	<text id="452">You&apos;ll obtain the power to heal by passing one of the tests of wizardry. But first you have to enroll. Upon graduation, you get an additional level of magic!</text>
	<text id="453">Hi Twinsen. If you want to see Moya the turtle, you may find her at the small oasis or on the other side of the harbor. To call her, just ring the bell.</text>
	<text id="454">You are now a member of our school.</text>
	<text id="455">To become a wizard, you must first pass 3 tests, in any order you wish.</text>
	<text id="456">You can bring me the result of each test at your leisure, but I will give you your wizard&apos;s diploma and your new level of magic only after you succeed in all 3 tests!!</text>
	<text id="457">Once you pass through this door, you will have to be both fast and accurate. Stand in the middle of the room and, with the help of your ball, reverse all the magic symbols.</text>
	<text id="458">Try again, Twinsen.</text>
	<text id="459">Mmm, I love the smell of Garden Balsam. Anyway, in exchange for the flower, here&apos;s the Horn of the Blue Triton. It&apos;ll make you a Healer.</text>
	<text id="460">I don&apos;t know what Jerome&apos;s cooking up, but there&apos;s a demonic machine under there.</text>
	<text id="461">You still have two tests to pass.</text>
	<text id="462">You still have one test to pass before you become a wizard.</text>
	<text id="463">You know, I wonder if they might have brought her around, actually...What with all the wizards and Esmers hanging around the Hacienda these days...</text>
	<text id="465">It seems Baldino is working on the proto-pack, maybe he&apos;s trying to improve it?</text>
	<text id="466">Hello.</text>
	<text id="467">You are at Temple Park, the ancient site of the Temple of Bù.</text>
	<text id="469">Phew, it&apos;s hot but it feels so wonderful!</text>
	<text id="472">Oh, hi Twinsen ! If you want to take a little sea trip, jump on my back!!</text>
	<text id="473">Are you ready to come and spend some time on our planet?</text>
	<text id="474">Looking for a costume or Magic accessories? Well, Chedil Amiradoo has a deal that&apos;ll make your head spin. Low, low prices and after-sales service. Currently doing the rounds on your island.</text>
	<text id="475">Get out!</text>
	<text id="477">Hi!!!</text>
	<text id="478">These...[hic!] These strangers sure are cool...[hic!] They keep buying us drinks. What a great bunch of guys!! [Hic!!] Right, buddy? [Hic!!]</text>
	<text id="479">This Turkish bath is too hot for me! Sometimes, it&apos;s so hot that I have hallucinations... I see wizards everywhere!!!</text>
	<text id="480">Masher!!!</text>
	<text id="481">Qwelt ik M?lg&apos;b - ~oc  ~&apos;c # %-) ~Big TsS-steel-jenr, (dulkug) hanfin tuwouah koa xdocd &quot; ö&quot;</text>
	<text id="482">Now that the temple&apos;s under repair, we don&apos;t have too many customers. Just Esmers mostly, visiting. They offered to help us.</text>
	<text id="485">Out, quick!</text>
	<text id="487">Bravo Twinsen, you have earned this blowgun. It provides accurate and rapid shots.</text>
	<text id="488">Bravo Twinsen. You now bear the title of wizard. @ I don&apos;t have any spare wizard&apos;s parade tunics left. But there is a peddler on the island. I&apos;ll contact him and ask him to give you one. Go find him. Also, let your beard grow.</text>
	<text id="490">Sorry, can&apos;t help you. The only story about magic that I know is the one about a rabbibunny that got turned into a shell!</text>
	<text id="491">Nah, but if they&apos;ve got something to lower the temperature of this bath, I&apos;m willing to go see them.</text>
	<text id="492">No, no idea.</text>
	<text id="494">Learning also means completing old problems with new methods.&quot;</text>
	<text id="495">You have to find a peddler who lives on this island. I advised him to provide you with a hat and your wizard&apos;s parade tunic.</text>
	<text id="496">I don&apos;t know where it is, but it can&apos;t be that far. It&apos;s all wizards and Esmers that pass by here.</text>
	<text id="497">Ah, only the wizards are able to read this.</text>
	<text id="498">I can&apos;t answer you, sir. I am not from here.</text>
	<text id="499">Honor roll of most recent wizard graduates: Aril van Koow, Hougo Dolphar, Carnogeel.&quot;</text>
	<text id="500">Honor roll of most recent wizard graduates: Aril van Koow, Hougo Dolphar, Carnogeel, Twinsen.&quot;</text>
	<text id="502">Hello!! Allow to me introduce the Grand Rector of the School of Magic!</text>
	<text id="503">A pleasant stay in our magnificent school of magic!!</text>
	<text id="504">My dear sir, my goods are only available to fully licensed wizards.</text>
	<text id="505">Ah, you must be Twinsen. Congratulations for passing your examination. If you want a magician&apos;s tunic it&apos;ll only cost you 50 kashes. We&apos;ll throw in a false beard to make you look like an old magician. Interested?</text>
	<text id="506">Now that you are a wizard, I can sell you some orange powder. It costs 10 Kashes, and will recharge you in Magic and Life Points.</text>
	<text id="507">Hey!! You nuts?</text>
	<text id="508">Sorry Twinsen, but I don&apos;t know where it is.</text>
	<text id="509">Disappeared?? Master, this is grave news. I&apos;ll do all in my power to find them. Trust me!!</text>
	<text id="510">You are at the Hacienda del Monte-Pelado.&quot;</text>
	<text id="512">I know where it is, but I don&apos;t have the right to tell you.</text>
	<text id="514">I saw Ker&apos;aooc pass by a while back. Told me the Esmers had invited him...someplace or other. Regardless, he was going to the Hacienda.</text>
	<text id="516">Hello!</text>
	<text id="517">What should I do, Master?</text>
	<text id="521">Helllppp !!!</text>
	<text id="522">Do you want to use the telescope for 2 Kashes?&quot;</text>
	<text id="527">It exists? I always thought it was just another desert mirage.</text>
	<text id="529">No... although ... I go to the desert to gather the plants with which I cook. But I always avoid crossing a terrifying place, a kind of a forlorn garden... It might be there.</text>
	<text id="532">Welcome</text>
	<text id="533">Hello.</text>
	<text id="534">Hi.</text>
	<text id="536">The oasis in the desert.</text>
	<text id="537">There&apos;s a piece missing here, something disc-shaped. I guess it allows the shuttle to take off.</text>
	<text id="538">A School of Magic? Do you think they might need an assistant?</text>
	<text id="540">For sure. Carousing with a bunch of Esmers...By the way, I wonder where they all went.</text>
	<text id="541">The visitors who come from the sky are weird. I heard them invite some wizards to their planet.</text>
	<text id="542">The wizards? Ah yes, I saw some pass by quite a while back. They were talking about the Hacienda, in the desert.</text>
	<text id="543">It&apos;s locked.</text>
	<text id="544">Good day, Master</text>
	<text id="546">Aha! a sign from Sendell. They are venerated by all the wizards.</text>
	<text id="548">I don&apos;t have enough Kashes.</text>
	<text id="549">ER ioergouerg - erioufmqer o-u tu zejkhze jkhqdsqdsl iklds klqdfjn !!</text>
	<text id="550">OFFICIAL NOTICE ... all shuttles going to the moon base... new password... without which the soldiers will intervene... operation GREEN MOON !!</text>
	<text id="551">Go look at the Temple of Bù. They&apos;re discussing an old treasure still buried there.</text>
	<text id="558">My master often goes to get sand roses for me. I love munching them. They&apos;re so crunchy!</text>
	<text id="559">I don&apos;t know Twinsen, I don&apos;t live here. I was just imported.</text>
	<text id="560">I saw one go by a while ago. I think he was looking for sand roses.</text>
	<text id="636">Hey, Jerome.</text>
	<text id="637">Here! Here&apos;s the part that Zoé needs for your car.</text>
	<text id="639">Hello, Twinsen.</text>
	<text id="640">Ah no, I didn&apos;t even know there was one on this island!</text>
	<text id="641">I could&apos;ve called it an &quot;integrated super dynamo circuitry mechanism&quot; but I decided to go with &quot;portable radio&quot;. A little catchier, huh? Incidentally, I&apos;ll let you know when the Proto-Pack is ready, it&apos;ll let you fly around in complete safety.</text>
	<text id="642">Everybody talks about these guys from outer space, they say they landed on several islands. But that should not interrupt our game.</text>
	<text id="644">You pest!</text>
	<text id="645">Cheater!</text>
	<text id="646">I usually play better than that, but my back&apos;s killing me. The healer Ker&apos;aooc went out and forgot to leave me some poultice.</text>
	<text id="649">In spite of my powerful telescope, I saw only a couple of flying saucers pass behind the Moon. The Esmers must live on the hidden side.</text>
	<text id="652">Visit Temple-Park. Just one step from Bald Mountain, relive a pivotal episode in Twinsun&apos;s glorious history by exploring the Temple of Bù.&quot;</text>
	<text id="655">Jerome Baldino. @ Miscellaneous Gadgets  Inventions.&quot;</text>
	<text id="656">Hello?</text>
	<text id="658">Good day, Master, but... is that you Twinsen? You look terrific as a wizard, congratulations.</text>
	<text id="661">Von Kournil tour. @ (Island of the White Leaf Desert) &quot;</text>
	<text id="675">I don&apos;t know. I always make a detour whenever I take a stroll in the area. Not far from here, there is a dreadful garden on the rocky hillside.</text>
	<text id="676">Port-Ludo @ (Island of the White Leaf Desert). &quot;</text>
	<text id="680">The access to the lower floors is temporarily prohibited, we can no longer assure the safety of the visitors. The Esmers have volunteered to do the work in the lowest basement. It&apos;s not I who will complain!!</text>
	<text id="681">Bravo!!</text>
	<text id="682">Magnificent!</text>
	<text id="683">Sir!</text>
	<text id="684">If you want to go farther out, you&apos;ll have to board a vacant cart. Watch out during the visit, stay on the tracks and don&apos;t get off. It&apos;s dangerous, and you could easily injure yourself.</text>
	<text id="685">Hello sir.</text>
	<text id="686">Hey, mister! My daddy, he&apos;s smart. He was able to get us in without tickets!</text>
	<text id="687">Dumb! I can&apos;t remember what I did with the admission tickets and I&apos;m afraid we might be checked!! ...Et er... do you think we can go farther?</text>
	<text id="689">My son adores tales of magic... he even believes we got in here with our special powers!! as if by a miracle!!</text>
	<text id="694">Aah, thank you kiddo! Feels like I got the back of a young Sphero again.</text>
	<text id="703">Well kiddo, all you had to do was treat my back for me to win all the games, golly gee!</text>
	<text id="707">I&apos;ve noticed I keep losing since you helped my little friend over there. Nice move Sherlock!</text>
	<text id="709">I don&apos;t know. But it has been a long time since I last saw Ker&apos;aooc the healer.</text>
	<text id="710">Stand in front of the article of your choice and do &quot;ACTION&quot;.</text>
	<text id="713">You are at the harbor @ (Island of the White Leaf Desert). &quot;</text>
	<text id="714">To the harbor.&quot;</text>
	<text id="715">To the Temple of Bù.&quot;</text>
	<text id="718">To the Hacienda del Monte-Pelado.&quot;</text>
	<text id="719">Ah thank you. I don&apos;t need it anymore, but it was kind of you to bring it back.</text>
	<text id="720">You can borrow this vial, I don&apos;t think Master Ker&apos;aooc has much use for it.</text>
	<text id="721">A ticket mister? For only 7 Kashes, you can visit all of Temple-Park, including the inside of the Temple of Bù.</text>
	<text id="723">Where do you want to go, Twinsen?</text>
	<text id="724">How can I get in?</text>
	<text id="725">Quickly! We must save Twinsun!!!</text>
	<text id="726">What&apos;s he saying??</text>
	<text id="728">Code Operation GREEN MOON</text>
	<text id="729">Code Operation Dark Monk</text>
	<text id="730">Operation Moon.</text>
	<text id="731">Code 36AX 95.</text>
	<text id="732">Shuttle 64 87, mission Twinsun.</text>
	<text id="733">Hello.</text>
	<text id="734">Thanks, Joe! But what are you doing here?</text>
	<text id="735">What do the wizards say??</text>
	<text id="736">It&apos;s OK.</text>
	<text id="737">I&apos;m not interested.</text>
	<text id="738">I&apos;d like to get to island CX. Can you take me there?</text>
	<text id="739">I&apos;d like to buy some gazogem.</text>
	<text id="740">I&apos;m trying to get to island CX.</text>
	<text id="741">Are you winning?</text>
	<text id="743">What should I do?</text>
	<text id="744">It&apos;s OK!</text>
	<text id="745">But Jerome, I&apos;ve got to find island CX and destroy the machines that control the lunar reactors!</text>
	<text id="746">I don&apos;t care about that.</text>
	<text id="747">The island of the Francos.</text>
	<text id="748">Celebration Island.</text>
	<text id="749">I&apos;d like to see Rick, the boss.</text>
	<text id="750">You know Rick, I&apos;d like to see him.</text>
	<text id="751">The emperor had some secret base built on island CX. From there, he&apos;ll trigger the firing of these reactors built on the moon in utmost secrecy which&apos;ll destroy my whole planet. I&apos;ve got to go to this island to prevent this from happening. Could you help me get there?</text>
	<text id="752">I&apos;m looking for a Mr. Johnny Rocket.</text>
	<text id="753">Are you Mr. Rocket?</text>
	<text id="754">I&apos;m here on behalf of Rick to look for the dissidents, and I desperately need to get to island CX!</text>
	<text id="755">Not yet.</text>
	<text id="756">That&apos;s me. I have to get to island CX and somehow destroy the control center of the lunar reactors before they&apos;re fired and the moon starts falling toward Twinsun.</text>
	<text id="757">Where should I go?</text>
	<text id="758">I hold a wizard&apos;s diploma.</text>
	<text id="759">One ferry ticket.</text>
	<text id="760">I have an umbrella.</text>
	<text id="761">I already have a crystal, so now I&apos;ll be able to use this laser pistol.</text>
	<text id="762">But... who do you mean?</text>
	<text id="763">You are at the harbor of Otringal.&quot;</text>
	<text id="764">You are in downtown Otringal.&quot;</text>
	<text id="765">You are at the astroport of Otringal.&quot;</text>
	<text id="766">Out of order, no gazogem&quot;</text>
	<text id="767">I don&apos;t have anything to sell.</text>
	<text id="770">DARK MONK HAS REINCARNATED!!! Come Join The Revelry! Be part of the celebration as he cancels the curse of Zeelich and restores its heavenly look!&quot;</text>
	<text id="771">WANTED: The so-called &quot;Twinsen.&quot; Master criminal - Trying to oppose Dark Monk and prevent the great celebration - Wears blue tunic - If you see him, call the police - Anyone helping bring this miscreant into custody will be rewarded the amount of 10,000 Zlitos.&quot;</text>
	<text id="773">This painting is strange, signed by some guy...Gramitte.</text>
	<text id="774">You are in the lower city of Otringal.&quot;</text>
	<text id="775">IMPERIAL HOTEL - Luxury establishment, members only&quot;</text>
	<text id="776">You are in the upper city of Otringal.&quot;</text>
	<text id="777">Whoah, these paintings are bogus!</text>
	<text id="778">This control panel&apos;s been modified. Apparently, I can&apos;t put the itinerary tokens in here anymore.</text>
	<text id="779">There&apos;s a piece missing, something disc-shaped. I guess I need it for the shuttle to take off.</text>
	<text id="783">Depiction of Zeelich, the Planet of a Thousand Wonders!!</text>
	<text id="793">I&apos;ve got some Twinsunian money.</text>
	<text id="847">I&apos;m staying here.</text>
	<text id="848">I don&apos;t have enough Kashes.</text>
	<text id="849">I don&apos;t have enough Zlitos.</text>
	<text id="853">THE ZEELICH GAZETTE: ...Johnny Rocket at the Imperial! Zeelich&apos;s brightest star, the first explorer to set foot on Twinsun, now lives on Otringal...&quot;</text>
	<text id="854">THE INQUIRER : ...group of dissidents who defaced our beautiful city with subversive posters.... some will be arrested... the police are looking for runaways...&quot;</text>
	<text id="855">OTRINGAL NEWS : The twinsunian wizards on a visit of Otringal...&quot;</text>
	<text id="856">THE OFFICIAL RUMOR: The Emperor asserts: Dark Monk will fulfill the prophecy, whether or not the mosquibees are willing to bring their fragment!!!&quot;</text>
	<text id="857">THE DESPATCH OF ZEELICH: shortage of gazogem, the tankers stopped supplying Otringal!&quot;</text>
	<text id="858">THE INQUIRER: Looking for witnesses! 10,000 Zlitos reward!!! If you see a Twinsunian in a blue tunic, call the police immediately...armed and dangerous...&quot;</text>
	<text id="859">OTRINGAL NEWS: Twinsunian Anarchist Disrupts Dark Monk&apos;s Ceremony...</text>
	<text id="860">THE OFFICIAL RUMOR: Emperor Reveals: Dark Monk Warned Me! He predicted a Twinsunian dressed in blue would try to prevent our ceremony...&quot;</text>
	<text id="861">2:55 p.m., shuttle 65 38, destination planet Zirla for fly safari... 3:20 p.m., shuttle 007, destination red planet...&quot;</text>
	<text id="923">Twinsen, I damaged the vessel during landing. I need some time for repairs. The Zeelichian fuel is called gazogem, it&apos;s very powerful. You should go get some.</text>
	<text id="924">Of course, but I will need this gazogem sooner or later. Besides, it will allow me to transform your protopack and increase its performance.</text>
	<text id="925">You must go get me some gazogem, so that I can finish to repair our vessel and make your protopack more powerful!!</text>
	<text id="926">Thanks, Twinsen. Now I can finish up on the ship. I&apos;ll buzz you on the radio as soon as I do the protopack.</text>
	<text id="927">Hey there, don&apos;t forget my gazogem. I really need it to repair the vessel. And I think you&apos;ll really appreciate what it does to your protopack.</text>
	<text id="928">Thank you, Twinsen. Now I can make us a ship that can race the comets! Anyway, here&apos;s something to turn your protopack into a superjetpack. and from now on, you can fly higher!</text>
	<text id="929">It&apos;s going to take me quite a while longer to finish up on the vessel here.</text>
	<text id="930">Come in! Twinsen? It&apos;s me, Baldino! I&apos;ve improved your protopack, you can come pick it up now!</text>
	<text id="933">epdu.e fe djkhs-dyty opizef m&apos;zefjklf!!</text>
	<text id="934">Cool down, Mr. Wizard sir! Please, walk this way...</text>
	<text id="938">Welcome to Zeelich, Master. Follow me, I will take you to your twinsunian colleagues.</text>
	<text id="939">Follow us!!</text>
	<text id="940">Calm down!</text>
	<text id="941">Please come in, Master.</text>
	<text id="942">Watch the hair!!</text>
	<text id="943">But... it&apos;s... Twinsen! Yo, Twinsen! It&apos;s me, Joe the Elf! Your old friend! Good to see you again!!!</text>
	<text id="944">Hey, Twinsen, great bumping into you! Say, you don&apos;t seem all that buddy-buddy with the locals! Soon as they heard your name, they jumped you, knocked you out, and stole your wizard&apos;s costume. And now, we&apos;re in jail.</text>
	<text id="945">Actually I was with the wizards when the Esmers invited them to this planet. Now, they&apos;re being held captive by the emperor and claim the Esmers want to kidnap the children of Twinsun. I got scared, so I left, and found you there.</text>
	<text id="946">They say the Esmers left for our planet to kidnap Twinsun&apos;s children! They say nothing can be done, but I still have hope. I&apos;m sure you will succeed in reaching the astroport to steal a shuttle and go save those children!!!</text>
	<text id="947">Ah, not so nice, that one. I&apos;d rather not be left alone with him!!</text>
	<text id="953">That&apos;s him! That&apos;s the Twinsunian we&apos;re looking for! Arrest him!</text>
	<text id="958">Here we are, Master, on our way to Zeelich! Relax, the trip will not be very long.</text>
	<text id="959">You are welcome, Master. Make yourself comfortable.</text>
	<text id="963">Fdoejd hjduiy hjdysuyuyszdf!!&quot;</text>
	<text id="964">You have no business here, sir!!</text>
	<text id="965">Ererklerg- m mgmoeroz!!</text>
	<text id="966">No!! Don&apos;t touch that!!</text>
	<text id="973">Zpgjdfuetc jkdu dhjsdgzt dhy s zeyyhsh ??</text>
	<text id="974">This is where we calculate the flight plans for the shuttles. You have no business being in here!!</text>
	<text id="978">Sorry, bud, I don&apos;t have none left. I&apos;m waiting for some tanker due in from the island of the Francos. Their refinery produces the gazogem from the gems collected in the under-gas.</text>
	<text id="983">KHJopfgi ou dfiyu Heiosdn!!!!</text>
	<text id="984">You must vacate the premises, sir. You are disturbing the work of our technicians.</text>
	<text id="988">On island CX? No way Jack! That&apos;s rough turf over there!!</text>
	<text id="989">For 5 Zlitos, I can take you somewheres. Where do you wanna go?</text>
	<text id="991">And what did you do with the children and the wizards?, you creep!</text>
	<text id="992">FunFrock, you suck big time, and I&apos;m going to take you out, and I don&apos;t mean for a pizza!</text>
	<text id="995">Are you the one who went to island CX and made it back alive?</text>
	<text id="996">What did you see over there?</text>
	<text id="997">How can I get there?</text>
	<text id="998">Otringal</text>
	<text id="999">The island of the Francos</text>
	<text id="1000">Nowhere, I&apos;m staying right here.</text>
	<text id="1003">Nope, not yet. It&apos;d be great to get to his office. Any ideas?</text>
	<text id="1004">Hello.</text>
	<text id="1005">Oh man, I don&apos;t have enough Zlitos.</text>
	<text id="1007">I know. But where is he? And where are the children?</text>
	<text id="1008">I&apos;m off to save the children and face FunFrock. Get out of here and get Baldino on Otringal!! We&apos;re going to need his ship to get out of this mess.</text>
	<text id="1009">... and when the stranger appears, alone capable of reuniting the four keys, Dark Monk will oppose... ...in the ultimate celebration the monsters and the gas will disappear... in forgetfulness Dark Monk will go... ... and life will Zeelich regain...&quot;</text>
	<text id="1010">Oof!! This crystal is way too heavy. I need some kind of tool to break off a piece.</text>
	<text id="1011">This way is no good. I need the four fragments.</text>
	<text id="1025">In the beginning, the 2 mother planets, Zeer (the sun) and Lich (the cold) met one another during the Oogh: the great cataclysm. From this Zeelich was born. Life appeared and the brotherhood of the Gods sent there the youngest son of the light, who was called Kard N&apos;kom. Alas, some deleterious fumes emanating from the Great Sulfur Mine disfigured him. His horribly mutilated face escaped the Gods, and it was decided that Kard N&apos;kom would have to forever hide his face and never again appear in front of the noble assembly. Condemned to roam the cosmos forever, Kard N&apos;kom saw his Name erased from the divine law. He who wanders without a face became then known as Dark Monk... Zeelich was populated with 4 different races, condemned by the Gods to fight each other forever. But, life being stronger, the divine brotherhood hurled Zeelich into the first sun of the Novae system. This shock created the planet such as we know it: a blanket of clouds isolating the rocky summits from the melting ground.</text>
	<text id="1026">Then Dark Monk came back and announced the latest verdict from the Gods. The races were to fraternize and share the task of returning Zeelich to its former beauty. He unveiled a great wonder: from the deadly cloud, hideous monsters were born and threatened to invade the planet. But, thanks to his Key, Dark Monk also gave rise to a volcano which erupted and sculpted in basalt a gigantic statue in his image, holding the Stone Book of the 10,000 Names. At each ceremony, lightning would henceforth inscribe once more the Name of God, Dark Monk. Before disappearing, Dark Monk broke his Key into 4 pieces and thus revealed the Great Prophecy. On the day when the 10,000th Name of God is engraved the reunion of the 4 fragments of the Key will make the monsters and the gas disappear, and will give back to Zeelich the heavenly appearance of its origin. Life will then be reborn as it was in the time of Eden.</text>
	<text id="1027">Did you say fireflies? Ugh...[sigh]</text>
	<text id="1034">The island of the Mosquibees</text>
	<text id="1035">The island of the volcano</text>
	<text id="1037">Do you know where the Mosquibee village is at?</text>
	<text id="1038">Do you know where I could find the Mosquibees?</text>
	<text id="1039">I asked Mr. Monk how to get to the Mosquibees, and he told me to ask you about the ferryman.</text>
	<text id="1040">I&apos;m trying to find the Mosquibees. Can you help me out?</text>
	<text id="1041">But, I am only trying to go to the Mosquibees...</text>
	<text id="1043">No thank you, honest!</text>
	<text id="1044">Hey! how can I find the Queen of the Mosquibees?</text>
	<text id="1045">You are entering the domain of the Wannies.&quot;</text>
	<text id="1048">You&apos;re at the Building Company, in front of the gem mine.</text>
	<text id="1049">You&apos;re at the ferryman&apos;s lane.</text>
	<text id="1050">You&apos;re in the village of the Wannies.</text>
	<text id="1052">Ferryman if you please, @ take me across the raging seas, @ for a few gems, I take your boat, @ I cannot swim, I cannot float!!</text>
	<text id="1057">I went shopping. Be back soon. Signed: your housemaid.</text>
	<text id="1058">What a weird painting, looks like a monster from the gas.</text>
	<text id="1059">Ugh, taste in home decor is rather lame.</text>
	<text id="1060">Dark Monk&apos;s chapel.</text>
	<text id="1062">Your Majesty, I&apos;ve come to free you, and ask you to open the door to the passage which leads to island CX. My planet&apos;s being threatened and I have to save it.</text>
	<text id="1077">I don&apos;t have enough gems.</text>
</texts>
