<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1" ?>

<lbatexts>
  <game>2</game>
  <quotes>
    <quote id="1" type="1">How can I get in?</quote>
    <quote id="2" type="1">Quickly! We must save Twinsun!!!</quote>
    <quote id="3" type="1">What's he saying??</quote>
    <quote id="4" type="1">Code Operation GREEN MOON</quote>
    <quote id="5" type="1">Code Operation Dark Monk</quote>
    <quote id="6" type="1">Operation Moon.</quote>
    <quote id="7" type="1">Code 36AX 95.</quote>
    <quote id="8" type="1">Shuttle 64 87, mission Twinsun.</quote>
    <quote id="9" type="1">Hello</quote>
    <quote id="10" type="3">Twinsen!! You are here at last! It's horrible!! The Esmers have built some reactors on Emerald Moon in order to propel it toward Twinsun and explode our planet!! They obey their God who was miraculously reincarnated, and they want to fulfill an ancient prophecy which is supposed to return their planet to its ancient heavenly look.</quote>
    <quote id="11" type="1">Hey, Twinsen, take this translator, and you will conveniently understand the language of Zeelich!!</quote>
    <quote id="12" type="9">Follow me!</quote>
    <quote id="13" type="1">Twinsen! I left my vessel near the outside of the crater. We'll be able to escape through the yard!</quote>
    <quote id="14" type="1">The door's jammed. We have to find some way to open it.</quote>
    <quote id="15" type="1">Zeef erkierio orguoerg erguergu ug- ^hrt.</quote>
    <quote id="16" type="1">Moon base to shuttle. Moon base to shuttle. Please give your password for identification. I repeat, give your password for identification.</quote>
    <quote id="17" type="1">Right code.</quote>
    <quote id="18" type="1">Wrong code.</quote>
    <quote id="19" type="1">ZAZ zeujazeT er ERItier ertiye YI!</quote>
    <quote id="20" type="1">Go to the welcoming building, get a pass. Then, go to the main entrance of the base. It's the door with the green light. That means that it is open.</quote>
    <quote id="21" type="1">zeio p^r.</quote>
    <quote id="22" type="1">Hello.</quote>
    <quote id="23" type="1">ZEOe eiarERAtiERTTERt AYO oertrtYRTIY tp !</quote>
    <quote id="24" type="1">Only the welcoming building controls the opening of the doors. If you want to enter here, you must ask them to open!</quote>
    <quote id="25" type="1">zeio p^r.</quote>
    <quote id="26" type="1">Hello.</quote>
    <quote id="27" type="1">It's true! We have been deceived by Dark Monk, our God who reappeared. This must be stopped! But the reactors are indestructible!! They are remote controlled from Zeelich! The center which controls them has been built on island CX. Our only hope of avoiding the disaster is to destroy it!!!</quote>
    <quote id="28" type="1">I will take you to the dissidents. Only they can help us!! They always haunt the bars and the slightly shady places! Meanwhile, we must leave! We can't stay here!!</quote>
    <quote id="29" type="1">Dfkiod fdssfm qQf f-pqG dfggfdg qgdfgk!!</quote>
    <quote id="30" type="1">We, inhabitants of Zeelich, have been deceived by Dark Monk, our God who reappeared. This must be stopped! But the reactors are indestructible!! They are remote controlled from Zeelich! The center which controls them has been built on island CX. Our only hope of avoiding the disaster is to destroy it!!!</quote>
    <quote id="31" type="1">Go... to CX...island CX...</quote>
    <quote id="32" type="1">We've to get out of here!!</quote>
    <quote id="33" type="9">Tfhuirt!</quote>
    <quote id="34" type="9">Halt!!</quote>
    <quote id="35" type="9">Zeorfevg r!!</quote>
    <quote id="36" type="9">Stop!!</quote>
    <quote id="37" type="9">ZX81!!</quote>
    <quote id="38" type="9">HAL!!</quote>
    <quote id="39" type="1">Ereolju p-er omom qeo omkldf zekujze mzkmjha!!</quote>
    <quote id="40" type="1">Don't forget to go to the welcoming building and have your passage registered.</quote>
  </quotes>
</lbatexts>
