<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1" ?>

<lbatexts>
  <game>2</game>
  <quotes>
    <quote id="1" type="1">No way! I'm going to stop you!!</quote>
    <quote id="2" type="1">Hello.</quote>
    <quote id="3" type="5">Twinsen...Oh Twinsen, it's me, Sendell!!! Twinsen, a cosmic cataclysm is on its way!!! The moon has started to move! Soon, it is going to hurl itself against Twinsun, destroying our planet!!! You must stop Dark Monk and prevent him from using that infernal machine he built inside the statue. With it, he could attract and steal the energy that we could use to stop the moon!!! You must get the four key fragments, which are used in the ceremony and are protected by the Esmer races. With these fragments the statue of Dark Monk will emerge from the crater!! Once you stop Dark Monk, you will have to come back to Twinsun and, in the Well of the Sendells, I will help you stop the moon!!</quote>
    <quote id="4" type="1">Here you are at last! I was waiting for you Twinsunian, Dark Monk told me a lot about you!!</quote>
    <quote id="5" type="3">It's over Twinsen, you lost. To make your defeat even more bitter, I am going to tell you the truth. @ With all these beliefs, I was not master of my own planet, people had only ears for Dark Monk's priests!! One day, a stranger landed on Zeelich and offered to pass himself off as Dark Monk. Together, we spread the belief that he was to fulfill the great prophecy. Of course, this is far from the truth. @ I don't know why, but Dark Monk wants to appropriate the magical energy contained in your planet. And, since I want to become the master of Zeelich, we made a deal!!!</quote>
    <quote id="6" type="3">Twinsunian, Dark Monk is unbeatable. In his statue, he has built a machine capable of storing the magical energy that he intends to steal from your planet!!! @ My agents went to Twinsun to kidnap your wizards since we needed them to attract the energy from your planet to Zeelich. But we were forced to kidnap the children because the wizards refused to cooperate!! @ You were our only obstacle. But now, we have won. The destruction of Twinsun and the use of the machine will intervene during the next ceremony. And you cannot prevent me from triggering the lunar reactors!!!</quote>
    <quote id="7" type="1">Who are you? This is the emperor's personal shuttle! You have no business here!!!</quote>
    <quote id="8" type="9">Heeeeeee!!!</quote>
  </quotes>
</lbatexts>
