<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1" ?>

<lbatexts>
  <game>2</game>
  <quotes>
    <quote id="1" type="1">Ferryman if you please, @ take me across the raging seas, @ for a few gems, I take your boat, @ I cannot swim, I cannot float!!</quote>
    <quote id="2" type="1">The island of the volcano</quote>
    <quote id="3" type="1">The island of the Wannies.</quote>
    <quote id="4" type="1">I need your help. Dark Monk and the Emperor have built a reactor on Emerald moon. This reactor is going to hurl the moon toward my planet destroying life as we know it!! We don't have much time, Dark Monk promised to make this happen at the next ceremony.</quote>
    <quote id="5" type="1">The control center is on island CX. The only way in is the passage which starts from the under-gas. Fortunately, the rebels from above told me the local rebels would help me.</quote>
    <quote id="6" type="1">I don't have enough gems.</quote>
    <quote id="7" type="1">Hello</quote>
    <quote id="8" type="1">Hello</quote>
    <quote id="9" type="1">I'm staying here.</quote>
    <quote id="10" type="1">Tourism is really big around here!</quote>
    <quote id="11" type="1">I've got to speak to your Queen!</quote>
    <quote id="12" type="1">Hey, Leave me alone!</quote>
    <quote id="13" type="1">You are at the village of the Mosquibees.</quote>
    <quote id="14" type="1">Whoever wants to cross the ocean of fire must pay the price. Four gems is the fare. @ Where do you want to go?</quote>
    <quote id="15" type="1">It's our secret identification sign. He just might be speaking the truth your Majesty.</quote>
    <quote id="16" type="1">Don't you have any proof of your good faith? An identification sign, an object?</quote>
    <quote id="17" type="1">My dissident friend confirmed that you are in fact a Twinsunian. While on a mission to your planet he saw the actions of the Emperor's soldiers. We know that Dark Monk and the Emperor have lied to us, as well as kidnapping your wizards and children. But you, what are you doing here?</quote>
    <quote id="18" type="1">And what can we do?</quote>
    <quote id="19" type="1">Do you have proof?</quote>
    <quote id="20" type="1">You mustn't try to prove your allegations like that. I am waiting for you to find a more intelligent way of going about it!</quote>
    <quote id="21" type="1">But he is not a Mosquibee. You will have to prove your courage and pass the test of truth before you can become one of us... Only then will we help you.</quote>
    <quote id="22" type="1">Listen to me Twinsunian! You must seize a weapon hidden behind one of the doors! Do what you can, there are no other rules!</quote>
    <quote id="23" type="1">Excellent Twinsen! You just grabbed the blowtron! This weapon makes you our equal. You are now welcome in the village of the Mosquibees and we will help you reach the island CX. I not only own the key to the passage which leads there, I will also open the doors for you as soon as we arrive!!</quote>
    <quote id="24" type="1">Well, Twinsunian, I am waiting...</quote>
    <quote id="25" type="1">On guard! The Emperor's soldiers!! They're attacking!! There all over us!! Your Majesty, we can't hold them, they're already in the village, we must retreat!! You must leave now or be captured.</quote>
    <quote id="26" type="1">What are you doing here?</quote>
    <quote id="27" type="9">OK, Hang on!!</quote>
    <quote id="28" type="1">Ah, Twinsen!! With the arrival of these paratroopers, I am afraid to see our fragment might fall into the hands of the emperor. By the way, If you know how to throw back the balls of fire with your hands, try to grab some.</quote>
    <quote id="29" type="1">The Queen has been captured, but some of our people managed to escape. They took shelter in the cave of the volcano.</quote>
  </quotes>
</lbatexts>
