<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1" ?>

<lbatexts>
  <game>2</game>
  <quotes>
    <quote id="1" type="1">Otringal</quote>
    <quote id="2" type="1">The island of the celebration</quote>
    <quote id="3" type="1">Nowhere, I'm staying here.</quote>
    <quote id="4" type="1">Hello.</quote>
    <quote id="5" type="1">Oh Batbarf, I don't have enough Zlitos.</quote>
    <quote id="6" type="1">OK!</quote>
    <quote id="7" type="1">"Mr. Kurtz - Retired Colonel - Specializing in non-scientific sciences"</quote>
    <quote id="8" type="1">And, today, nobody knows where the heck the fragment is. That's why everyone is digging all over the place!! But why didn't he leave any notes?</quote>
    <quote id="9" type="1">"Roger de la Fontaine - Franco Burgermaster"</quote>
    <quote id="10" type="1">I am not interested.</quote>
    <quote id="11" type="1">It's locked.</quote>
    <quote id="12" type="1">You are at the village of the Francos.</quote>
    <quote id="13" type="1">You are at the gazogem refinery.</quote>
    <quote id="14" type="1">You are at the harbor of the Francos.</quote>
    <quote id="15" type="1">But, I found it, you know, your fragment!!!</quote>
    <quote id="16" type="1">For 5 Zlitos, I can take you somewheres. Where would you like to go bud?</quote>
    <quote id="17" type="1">The fare I am charging is 5 Zlitos. Where would you like to be going sir?</quote>
    <quote id="18" type="1">Wackos! A bunch of wackos live in this village. Even the birds are stupid. Especially this owl who came to roost here. It quietly took possession of this niche, and now it's his home.</quote>
    <quote id="19" type="9">Biddy, Biddy!!</quote>
    <quote id="20" type="1">Taking the size of the island, its geological structure and wind direction into account. I have concocted a potion which should allow me to precisely determine the location of the fragment! Unfortunately...I uh, lost the vial.</quote>
    <quote id="21" type="1">Roger de la Fontaine, he was my brother. He was the local burgermaster you know, who was responsible of our fragment. Roger, he kept hiding the fragment somewhere without telling anyone, until the accident... Pity, he was eaten by a monster from the gas.</quote>
    <quote id="22" type="1">I don't think so. Anyhow, the closet that he had ornamented with little stuffed monsters from the gas, well, it is locked... Besides, I lost the key. Then...</quote>
    <quote id="23" type="1">Holy Santa Maria!, somebody really ought to find this fragment.</quote>
    <quote id="24" type="1">Yeah, sure whatever, your the twelfth person to lay this on me... I didn't believe the first eleven so why should I believe you?</quote>
    <quote id="25" type="1">I'm sure it's not even true...</quote>
    <quote id="26" type="1">Since everyone started looking for our fragment, I've turned the bazaar into a treasure hunter's shop.</quote>
    <quote id="27" type="1">If you want to buy something from me, you just have to stand in front of it and do "ACTION".</quote>
    <quote id="28" type="1">A pick-ax costs 20 Zlitos.</quote>
    <quote id="29" type="1">10 Life points cost 20 Zlitos.</quote>
    <quote id="30" type="1">10 Magic points cost 20 Zlitos.</quote>
    <quote id="31" type="1">This frying pan is not for sale, it's only for the decor.</quote>
    <quote id="32" type="1">You have to be crazy to believe all these stories of fragment hunting. Me, I think Roger lost it at home before getting eaten by the monster. What are you gonna do?, at least its good for business.</quote>
    <quote id="33" type="1">Yeah it's pretty serious, this here story!! It better be found this er...fragment. 'Cause no fragment, no ceremony, and no paradise!! Bah, I don't give a hoot, I've got myself a vineyard... Come on, mister, just a snort?</quote>
    <quote id="34" type="1">I'm certain our fragment's buried here. Obviously, must be hidden under the grass. I mean the burgermaster couldn't have buried it under the rock, am I right?</quote>
    <quote id="35" type="1">I, well, er, well I dig here because it's just as good as somewhere else. Everybody here digs, why not me? Heh? And why not here?</quote>
    <quote id="36" type="1">This Roger de la Fontaine, he used to go pretty close to the gas. Could well be where he hid it, our fragment!!</quote>
    <quote id="37" type="1">Because of this lost fragment nonsense, everyone is looking for it. So they leave their little rug rats with me all day long. They just don't stop bawling...I'm going to look for another job soon.</quote>
    <quote id="38" type="1">I won't talk!! My parents put me here to punish me 'cause I lost the key to our house. It's wasn't my fault, that thief of an owl that took it from me. That filthy mechanical owl!! And it's not a loser like you who is going to help me!!</quote>
    <quote id="39" type="9">Waah!!</quote>
    <quote id="40" type="9">Waah!!</quote>
    <quote id="41" type="9">Waah!!</quote>
    <quote id="42" type="9">Waah!!</quote>
  </quotes>
</lbatexts>
