<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1" ?>

<lbatexts>
  <game>2</game>
  <quotes>
    <quote id="1" type="1">Did you say fireflies? Ugh...[sigh]</quote>
    <quote id="2" type="1">The island of the Mosquibees</quote>
    <quote id="3" type="1">The island of the volcano</quote>
    <quote id="4" type="1">Do you know where the Mosquibee village is at?</quote>
    <quote id="5" type="1">Do you know where I could find the Mosquibees?</quote>
    <quote id="6" type="1">I asked Mr. Monk how to get to the Mosquibees, and he told me to ask you about the ferryman.</quote>
    <quote id="7" type="1">I'm trying to find the Mosquibees. Can you help me out?</quote>
    <quote id="8" type="1">But, I am only trying to go to the Mosquibees...</quote>
    <quote id="9" type="1">No thank you, honest!</quote>
    <quote id="10" type="1">Hey! how can I find the Queen of the Mosquibees?</quote>
    <quote id="11" type="1">I went shopping. Be back soon. Signed: your housemaid.</quote>
    <quote id="12" type="1">What a weird painting, looks like a monster from the gas.</quote>
    <quote id="13" type="1">Ugh, taste in home decor is rather lame.</quote>
    <quote id="14" type="1">Dark Monk's chapel.</quote>
    <quote id="15" type="1">I don't have enough gems.</quote>
    <quote id="16" type="1">Hello</quote>
    <quote id="17" type="1">Hi</quote>
    <quote id="18" type="1">Hello</quote>
    <quote id="19" type="1">Your Majesty, I've come to free you, and ask you to open the door to the passage which leads to island CX. My planet's being threatened and I have to save it.</quote>
    <quote id="20" type="1">"You are entering the domain of the Wannies."</quote>
    <quote id="21" type="1">Ferryman if you please, @ take me across the raging seas, @ for a few gems, I take your boat, @ I cannot swim, I cannot float!!</quote>
    <quote id="22" type="1">You're at the Building Company, in front of the gem mine.</quote>
    <quote id="23" type="1">You're at the ferryman's lane.</quote>
    <quote id="24" type="1">You're in the village of the Wannies.</quote>
    <quote id="25" type="1">Hello. Won't you come in and share our meal?</quote>
    <quote id="26" type="1">So? How do you like my firefly tart?</quote>
    <quote id="27" type="9">Dinner is served!</quote>
    <quote id="28" type="1">Feeling better? Well, it's the first time I find somebody who does not like my tart!!</quote>
    <quote id="29" type="1">Would you like another slice of tart?</quote>
    <quote id="30" type="1">I hope the military are not going to come back and wreak havoc here. Since their passage, I haved a tough time finding fireflies for my tarts.</quote>
    <quote id="31" type="9">He bothering me!!</quote>
    <quote id="32" type="1">Whoever wants to cross the ocean of fire must pay the price. Four gems is the fare. @ Where do you want to go?</quote>
    <quote id="33" type="9">Help me...</quote>
    <quote id="34" type="1">Ah, thank you, thank you! I'd fallen and couldn't get up. What can I do to thank you?</quote>
    <quote id="35" type="1">She's locked up in the premises of the Building Company, the entrance of which is heavily guarded. But from the mine, you can access the nearest hangar. And from there, if you take the roof, you can reach the building where she's being held.</quote>
    <quote id="36" type="1">Be careful Twinsen, all the soldiers are looking for you.</quote>
    <quote id="37" type="1">Here, as a token of my gratitude, I'm giving you this glove. It protects us from fire and lets us get the gems out of the molten lava without burning up.</quote>
    <quote id="38" type="1">Here, to thank you, take this gem.</quote>
    <quote id="39" type="1">Hey, pal! Say, if you bring me back a slice of tart, I'll tell you a pretty wacky secret.</quote>
    <quote id="40" type="1">Oh, thanks a bunch, pal! Listen, this kid, he give me the key to the chapel. Here, take it. I've had enough fun with it.</quote>
    <quote id="41" type="1">That was one hummer of a tart! My boy, 'e sez that I shouldn't eat none 'cause it could make me sick. But that's all a bunch of hogwash. Phooey, I sez.</quote>
    <quote id="42" type="1">Hi, pal! Hey, is that you who brought on all this military? They don't look all that strong, if you ask me. In my day, it was different. They fed us firefly tarts, that really built us up!!!</quote>
    <quote id="43" type="1">Say, I've heard that them Mosquibees got ambushed. Pretty sure they took shelter in the cave near the waterfall at the foot of the volcano.</quote>
    <quote id="44" type="1">Very well. But first, being that you're a stranger, I must warn you.</quote>
    <quote id="45" type="3">Once, long ago, our god, Dark Monk, condemned us, the people of Zeelich, to live forever on our planet which he then turned into hell so as to make it seem more of a real condemnation. Each of the four races received a fragment of a key. These must be reunited during a great ceremony. And when our people have atoned for their sins, Dark Monk will rid us of the curse and give Zeelich back its original appearance. Today, he's returned and we all await the next and last ceremony. Twinsen, do not dare interfere with the religious practice of our people.</quote>
    <quote id="46" type="1">For that, you'll have to call on the ferryman's services. He provides the only communication between the islands and the under-gas. Go see my housemaid. She shall tell you how to proceed.</quote>
    <quote id="47" type="1">But it's you who took our fragment. You don't realize what you have done. Listen carefully.</quote>
    <quote id="48" type="1">The time of the ceremony is near. Dark Monk in person will chase away the monsters of the gas cloud when we reunite the four fragments for the last time.</quote>
    <quote id="49" type="1">The time of the ceremony is near. Now that you have taken our fragment, Dark Monk will not chase the monsters of the gas or the cloud which blankets Zeelich!</quote>
    <quote id="50" type="1">Oh, my, that's pretty far, no. You see, none of us have ever left our island or our beloved old mine.</quote>
    <quote id="51" type="1">My mommy, she's helping Mr. Monk make Dark Monk come back. And then, when he's here, heads are gonna roll! It'll be so awesome!! My mommy's strong!!</quote>
    <quote id="52" type="9">Waah!!!</quote>
    <quote id="53" type="1">Of course, it's fairly simple. You have to pay him in gems if you want him to take you. But first you have to call him. To do that, you have to stand at the end of the ferryman's pier and call him with this song. Listen to me and don't forget.</quote>
    <quote id="54" type="1">Ferryman if you please, take me across the raging seas, for a few gems, I take your boat, I cannot swim, I cannot float!!</quote>
    <quote id="55" type="1">The Monk impatiently awaits the ceremony of the celebration. It's a major event for our entire population. It represents the end of the curse which lies heavily upon Zeelich. We shall at last resume the course of our lives on a hospitable planet, not in this forlorn place.</quote>
    <quote id="56" type="1">Ah, yes, right. Only thing is, they don't live on this island, sir. You have to go to the wharf and call the ferryman. I've never actually seen him, but this rumor has an air of truth. Ask the Monk, he'll be able to answer you.</quote>
    <quote id="57" type="1">I'm in a bind, I've lost my glove in the mine. With it, I can catch the pieces of lava and the balls of fire, I can even pitch them back. Everybody has one, to extract gems.</quote>
    <quote id="58" type="1">The Monk, he threw me out of his choir. It's not fair, I didn't do anything. So I stole the key to the chapel! So I boxed it in and gave it to the old man!</quote>
    <quote id="59" type="1">I fish fireflies used to bake tarts. It's awfully good you know, a firefly tart.</quote>
    <quote id="60" type="1">I can always look for gems around here, there are none. Nothing doing, they can only be found in the mine. And yet, I was told that they were easy to find on the other islands.</quote>
    <quote id="61" type="1">I knew the Mosquibees live away from the rest, but they must've done something pretty drastic for the emperor to send his army. It's being whispered they're looking for a criminal hostile to Dark Monk!!</quote>
    <quote id="62" type="1">Hmmf! Lost my glove somewhere in the mine. Now I can't reach into the lava to grab up the gems.</quote>
    <quote id="63" type="1">No time.</quote>
    <quote id="64" type="1">Hi.</quote>
    <quote id="65" type="1">Leave me alone.</quote>
    <quote id="66" type="1">Hello.</quote>
    <quote id="67" type="9">Twinsen!!</quote>
    <quote id="68" type="1">You're very brave, but I've got face the emperor. Soon I'll be transferred to his palace, and he'll come to interrogate me. So I suppose I'll just stay here. Here! Take the key to the passage! Go and save your people!!</quote>
    <quote id="69" type="1">Hurry, Twinsen!! You have to penetrate to island CX. The entrance is behind our village! Use it! Quickly!</quote>
    <quote id="70" type="1">Only you can stop the emperor and Dark Monk.</quote>
    <quote id="71" type="1">Don't stay here! Escape while you still can!</quote>
    <quote id="72" type="1">The Monk punished our buddy Johnny 'cause he lost the key to the chapel. Wasn't even true.</quote>
    <quote id="73" type="1">Let's get this over with, so we can go and see the soldiers.</quote>
    <quote id="74" type="1">As for me, I'm real glad the Monk punished this Johnny. He had it coming he was always making fun of me.</quote>
    <quote id="75" type="1">I sure hope the army wasted this Johnny. Or, better yet, maybe they fed him to the ferryman!!</quote>
    <quote id="76" type="1">Look, this job is too much drudgery for us to want to talk about it!</quote>
    <quote id="77" type="1">Here, there is no hope. All we do is dig. That's all.</quote>
    <quote id="78" type="9">Watch out!!</quote>
    <quote id="79" type="1">You don't have business here, get lost!!!</quote>
    <quote id="80" type="1">Welcome to the Building Company, sir. If you're here to make a cash deposit, we can take care of it right away.</quote>
    <quote id="81" type="1">Er... good day... sir... I'm the manager of this institution. You were let in without an appointment? I take it then you're here to deposit an obscenely large sum of money?</quote>
    <quote id="82" type="9">No, have mercy!!</quote>
    <quote id="83" type="5">Easy, Twinsen, be careful. It's not the time to break this precious fragment!!</quote>
    <quote id="84" type="1">Please leave now and close the door! Here, as we say, "Idle hands make the Devil's workshop!!!"</quote>
  </quotes>
</lbatexts>
