<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1" ?>

<lbatexts>
  <game>2</game>
  <quotes>
    <quote id="1" type="1">Are you the one who went to island CX and made it back alive?</quote>
    <quote id="2" type="1">What did you see over there?</quote>
    <quote id="3" type="1">How can I get there?</quote>
    <quote id="4" type="1">Otringal</quote>
    <quote id="5" type="1">The island of the Francos</quote>
    <quote id="6" type="1">Nowhere, I'm staying right here.</quote>
    <quote id="7" type="1">Nope, not yet. It'd be great to get to his office. Any ideas?</quote>
    <quote id="8" type="1">Hello.</quote>
    <quote id="9" type="1">Oh man, I don't have enough Zlitos.</quote>
    <quote id="10" type="1">Oof!! This crystal is way too heavy. I need some kind of tool to break off a piece.</quote>
    <quote id="11" type="3">In the beginning, the 2 mother planets, Zeer (the sun) and Lich (the cold) met one another during the Oogh: the great cataclysm. From this Zeelich was born. Life appeared and the brotherhood of the Gods sent there the youngest son of the light, who was called Kard N'kom. Alas, some deleterious fumes emanating from the Great Sulfur Mine disfigured him. His horribly mutilated face escaped the Gods, and it was decided that Kard N'kom would have to forever hide his face and never again appear in front of the noble assembly. Condemned to roam the cosmos forever, Kard N'kom saw his Name erased from the divine law. He who wanders without a face became then known as Dark Monk... Zeelich was populated with 4 different races, condemned by the Gods to fight each other forever. But, life being stronger, the divine brotherhood hurled Zeelich into the first sun of the Novae system. This shock created the planet such as we know it: a blanket of clouds isolating the rocky summits from the melting ground.</quote>
    <quote id="12" type="3">Then Dark Monk came back and announced the latest verdict from the Gods. The races were to fraternize and share the task of returning Zeelich to its former beauty. He unveiled a great wonder: from the deadly cloud, hideous monsters were born and threatened to invade the planet. But, thanks to his Key, Dark Monk also gave rise to a volcano which erupted and sculpted in basalt a gigantic statue in his image, holding the Stone Book of the 10,000 Names. At each ceremony, lightning would henceforth inscribe once more the Name of God, Dark Monk. Before disappearing, Dark Monk broke his Key into 4 pieces and thus revealed the Great Prophecy. On the day when the 10,000th Name of God is engraved the reunion of the 4 fragments of the Key will make the monsters and the gas disappear, and will give back to Zeelich the heavenly appearance of its origin. Life will then be reborn as it was in the time of Eden.</quote>
    <quote id="13" type="1">And what did you do with the children and the wizards?, you creep!</quote>
    <quote id="14" type="1">FunFrock, you suck big time, and I'm going to take you out, and I don't mean for a pizza!</quote>
    <quote id="15" type="1">I know. But where is he? And where are the children?</quote>
    <quote id="16" type="1">I'm off to save the children and face FunFrock. Get out of here and get Baldino on Otringal!! We're going to need his ship to get out of this mess.</quote>
    <quote id="17" type="1">"... and when the stranger appears, alone capable of reuniting the four keys, Dark Monk will oppose... ...in the ultimate celebration the monsters and the gas will disappear... in forgetfulness Dark Monk will go... ... and life will Zeelich regain..."</quote>
    <quote id="18" type="1">This way is no good. I need the four fragments.</quote>
    <quote id="19" type="1">Mosquibee representative. The race of the Mosquibees lives in the under-gas. Their village is a magnificent cocoon anchored on the rocky tor which supports the island CX.</quote>
    <quote id="20" type="1">Wannie representative. The race of the Wannies lives in the under-gas. They are the workers of the gem mine, from which gazogem is made. The mine is being run by the Building Company, under imperial supervision.</quote>
    <quote id="21" type="1">Franco representative. The Francos live on the island of the Francos, (what a surprise!), which is enshrouded by the gas swarming with monsters. The Francos refine the gems extracted in the under-gas, and turn them into gazogem, usable by all the vehicles of Zeelich.</quote>
    <quote id="22" type="1">Sup representative. The Sups live in the upper city of Otringal. They are the planet's intellectual elite and always hold the highest positions.</quote>
    <quote id="23" type="1">I know him. He is from my planet. He is evil... But don't worry, I'll make sure he knows what's right.</quote>
    <quote id="24" type="1">For 5 Zlitos, I can take you somewheres. Where do you wanna go?</quote>
    <quote id="25" type="1">The fare I am charging is 5 Zlitos. Where would you like to go, sir?</quote>
    <quote id="26" type="1">That's it, my man, it's here. You'll find him easily, he sells souvenirs.</quote>
    <quote id="27" type="1">But that's the Twinsunian who escaped!! After him!! Murderer!!!</quote>
    <quote id="28" type="9">Halt!!</quote>
    <quote id="29" type="1">No, no, it's not me, it's not me!! Help, police!!! Murderer!!!!</quote>
    <quote id="30" type="1">I know you...you're the murderer everybody's looking for! Police, help!!!!</quote>
    <quote id="31" type="1">Yeah, it's me, or what's left of me. What do you want?</quote>
    <quote id="32" type="1">Ha ha, what I saw there... a secret fortress, guvv'ner. A fortress built by the parliament, where some army shuttles shoot at everything that gets close. I don't know what they hide there, and I don't want to know.</quote>
    <quote id="33" type="1">Are you kidding me? Nobody can get close. The only ones crazy enough to make a go at it, are Rick's gang. Rick, he's the owner of that bar, by the harbor. But he's much more than that, he's in charge of the Otringal underworld. Go see him, maybe he'll help ya.</quote>
    <quote id="34" type="1">So tell me, have you found Rick ?</quote>
    <quote id="35" type="1">No... maybe not the lodges. I heard rumors about something, but I just don't remember.</quote>
    <quote id="36" type="1">A little statue of Dark Monk, mister? The real one comes out of the volcano only during the cult ceremonies. It's quite an impressive sight, you should see it some time!</quote>
    <quote id="37" type="1">It's... it's not impossible... Then... Dark Monk is not Dark Monk... Only an impostor...</quote>
    <quote id="38" type="1">This prophecy is so exciting... I can't stop reading it over and over. It makes me cry every single time!!</quote>
    <quote id="39" type="1">This... this character has taken the place of Dark Monk. He has deceived us all. And we, poor dummies, we believed him!! But who is he, who is this FunFrock???</quote>
    <quote id="40" type="1">It is said the trail used to circle the crater and that folks came to gather crystals. Now, the road's blocked - and only a fool or a hero would dare venture there.</quote>
    <quote id="41" type="1">This temple is dedicated to Dark Monk. He is the God of the Zeelichians and lives again! His Majesty promised to cancel the Zeelichian curse during the cult's next ceremony.</quote>
    <quote id="42" type="1">Me, I declare this fellow... [hic!] I didn't trust him so much, [hic!!] I knew darn well we were all digging for nothing, hic!! If I'd known, I'd've spent a little more time at Franckie's instead of digging [hic!]!</quote>
    <quote id="43" type="1">At last we meet again, Twinsen! But this time, you are too late!! With the emperor's help, I succeeded in deceiving the Esmers. Ironic, isn't it? They mistook me for the reincarnation of Dark Monk and granted me divine powers that even I didn't possess. Thanks to those Esmers, these powers will be mine as soon as the moon collides with Twinsun!!</quote>
    <quote id="44" type="1">I needed the wizards to operate the machine I built in the statue. It'll attract the Sendells' energy from Twinsun's core, and release it in the explosion! The children were only a ploy to coerce the wizards' obedience!!</quote>
    <quote id="45" type="3">Even you a part of my plan, fool of a Quetch!! The statue is in fact an antenna! And I needed the four fragments to place it in its ceremonial position! Now, you will witness the destruction of your planet and my consecration as well! As soon as I activate the machine and the cosmic shock takes place, I will seize the Sendells' energy. It will make me a God in flesh as well as in name!!!</quote>
    <quote id="46" type="3">So you followed me, you miserable maggot!!! You didn't get the picture, did you? Now it's too late. In a few minutes, your planet will be destroyed, and its energy will make me the equivalent of a God!!! @ For annoying me with the sight of you yet again, I'm going to sacrifice these children you love so dearly right in front of your eyes!!!</quote>
    <quote id="47" type="9">Adieu!!!</quote>
    <quote id="48" type="1">Thank you for saving us, Twinsen. It is FunFrock who has chained us to this machine. He is alive! He has come back!! He is impersonating Dark Monk and he wants to destroy Twinsun!!</quote>
    <quote id="49" type="1">He is holding them prisoner in a cage like beasts. They're up there now, in the statue's head. The access gate's closed, but we'll help! All the magic at our disposal is going to be channeled into breaking that thing down!!! @ Let's do it!</quote>
    <quote id="50" type="9">Bravo!!!</quote>
    <quote id="51" type="9">Ready?</quote>
    <quote id="52" type="9">Go!!!</quote>
    <quote id="53" type="1">So, our Queen was right. The emperor lied to us all. He manipulated us all! All this to protect this impostor!!!</quote>
    <quote id="54" type="5">Terrific!!! Thank you, Sendell. Without your help, I would have never succeeded!</quote>
    <quote id="55" type="5">What do you mean?</quote>
    <quote id="56" type="5">These people are great. They are generous and honest. It's about time the people of Zeelich and Twinsun finally met.</quote>
    <quote id="57" type="5">Twinsen, the emerald moon just resumed its normal trajectory, Twinsun has been saved!!!!</quote>
    <quote id="58" type="5">It is I who must thank you, you saved us!! Don't forget that we, the Sendells, are an integral part of Twinsun!!! I think that we should also thank the Esmers...</quote>
    <quote id="59" type="5">Well, the reactor was much too powerful, even for us. If they had not come to destroy it, I am afraid we would not have succeeded!! You have unmasked FunFrock in front of their eyes, when they thought he was Dark Monk, their savior. Thanks to your intervention, they've understood. That's why they came to our rescue!!!</quote>
  </quotes>
</lbatexts>
