<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1" ?>

<lbatexts>
  <game>2</game>
  <quotes>
    <quote id="1" type="1">OK by me!</quote>
    <quote id="2" type="1">I'm not interested.</quote>
    <quote id="3" type="1">I would like to treat my Dino-fly first!</quote>
    <quote id="4" type="1">Looking for a costume or Magic accessories? Well, Chedil Amiradoo has a deal that'll make your head spin. Low, low prices and after-sales service. Currently doing the rounds on your island.</quote>
    <quote id="5" type="1">"Qwelt ik M?lg'b - ~oc & ~'c # %-) ~Big TsS-steel-jenr, (dulkug) hanfin tuwouah koa xdocd " ö"</quote>
    <quote id="6" type="1">Disappeared?? Master, this is grave news. I'll do all in my power to find them. Trust me!!</quote>
    <quote id="7" type="1">"Learning also means completing old problems with new methods."</quote>
    <quote id="8" type="1">"Honor roll of most recent wizard graduates: Aril van Koow, Hougo Dolphar, Carnogeel."</quote>
    <quote id="9" type="1">What should I do, Master?</quote>
    <quote id="10" type="1">Hey, Jerome.</quote>
    <quote id="11" type="1">"Visit Temple-Park. Just one step from Bald Mountain, relive a pivotal episode in Twinsun's glorious history by exploring the Temple of Bù."</quote>
    <quote id="12" type="1">"Jerome Baldino. @ Miscellaneous Gadgets & Inventions."</quote>
    <quote id="13" type="1">"Von Kournil tour. @ (Island of the White Leaf Desert) "</quote>
    <quote id="14" type="1">"Port-Ludo @ (Island of the White Leaf Desert). "</quote>
    <quote id="15" type="1">"You are at the harbor @ (Island of the White Leaf Desert). "</quote>
    <quote id="16" type="1">"To the harbor."</quote>
    <quote id="17" type="1">"To the Temple of Bù."</quote>
    <quote id="18" type="1">"To the Hacienda del Monte-Pelado."</quote>
    <quote id="19" type="1">"You are at Bald Mountain."</quote>
    <quote id="20" type="1">"To the cemetery."</quote>
    <quote id="21" type="1">Hello.</quote>
    <quote id="22" type="1">Hi.</quote>
    <quote id="23" type="1">It's locked.</quote>
    <quote id="24" type="1">Good day, Master</quote>
    <quote id="25" type="1">I don't have enough Kashes.</quote>
    <quote id="26" type="1">I am looking for the healing wizard, I must treat my Dino-Fly.</quote>
    <quote id="27" type="1">Do you happen to know where he lives?</quote>
    <quote id="28" type="1">But... the healing wizard!!</quote>
    <quote id="29" type="1">I'm trying to find the school of magic.</quote>
    <quote id="30" type="1">Do you know where to find the school of magic?</quote>
    <quote id="31" type="1">Did you see a wizard walk this way recently?</quote>
    <quote id="32" type="1">Do you know where the wizards are?</quote>
    <quote id="33" type="1">"Honor roll of most recent wizard graduates: Aril van Koow, Hougo Dolphar, Carnogeel, Twinsen."</quote>
    <quote id="34" type="9">Hello?</quote>
    <quote id="35" type="1">Master, the children of Twinsun have been kidnapped by the Esmers. Can you help? Maybe a spell to help us know where they were taken?</quote>
    <quote id="36" type="1">Where could I find it?</quote>
    <quote id="37" type="1">I read a message from the Weather Wizard. He needs a pearl of incandescence to finish his lightning spell. Where can I get one?</quote>
    <quote id="38" type="1">Master, I found a strange pearl in a cave, not far from Port-Ludo.</quote>
    <quote id="39" type="1">Citadel Island.</quote>
    <quote id="40" type="1">The island of the Dome of the Slate.</quote>
    <quote id="41" type="1">I'm staying here.</quote>
    <quote id="42" type="1">The island across from the Hacienda.</quote>
    <quote id="43" type="1">The oasis in the desert.</quote>
    <quote id="44" type="1">I don't know what Jerome's cooking up, but there's a demonic machine under there.</quote>
    <quote id="45" type="1">It seems Baldino is working on the proto-pack, maybe he's trying to improve it?</quote>
    <quote id="46" type="1">Hmmm,. these must be the plans for the machine that was hidden under that tarp. Baldino must have used it to get to Emerald Moon.</quote>
    <quote id="47" type="1">You are at Temple Park, the ancient site of the Temple of Bù.</quote>
    <quote id="48" type="1">"You are at the Hacienda del Monte-Pelado."</quote>
    <quote id="49" type="1">I happen to be looking for him.</quote>
    <quote id="50" type="1">Do you know where the wizards could be?</quote>
    <quote id="51" type="1">Where are you taking me, Moya?</quote>
    <quote id="52" type="1">I didn't know about this cave.</quote>
    <quote id="53" type="1">Citadel Island.</quote>
    <quote id="54" type="1">The Dome of the Slate.</quote>
    <quote id="55" type="1">I'm staying here.</quote>
    <quote id="56" type="1">Another tourist minibus. Man, that Temple of Bù really packs 'em in!</quote>
    <quote id="57" type="1">Aha! a sign from Sendell. They are venerated by all the wizards.</quote>
    <quote id="58" type="1">No, not yet.</quote>
    <quote id="59" type="1">No, I have to find the school of magic.</quote>
    <quote id="60" type="1">By passing the school's magic tests, I've gotten this horn to help me treat Dino-Fly.</quote>
    <quote id="61" type="1">I've decided to become a wizard so that I can treat Dino-Fly myself.</quote>
    <quote id="62" type="1">He gave it to me already. I'll bring it over to you.</quote>
    <quote id="63" type="1">They claim to be peaceful... but let's be careful, they look sort of aggressive to me.</quote>
    <quote id="64" type="1">Master, I figured out why the wizards disappeared. The Esmers invited them over to their planet for some kind of cultural and scientific exchange. I wonder what that's all about...</quote>
    <quote id="65" type="1">ER ioergouerg - erioufmqer o-u tu zejkhze jkhqdsqdsl iklds klqdfjn !!</quote>
    <quote id="66" type="1">OFFICIAL NOTICE ... all shuttles going to the moon base... new password... without which the soldiers will intervene... operation GREEN MOON !!</quote>
    <quote id="67" type="1">There's a piece missing here, something disc-shaped. I guess it allows the shuttle to take off.</quote>
    <quote id="68" type="33">Hello? Twinsen? That's it, I fixed the car... You should give it a whirl... I'm bringing it to Desert Island...</quote>
    <quote id="69" type="1">Twinsen, if you want to try out the car, just go to the racetrack or the desert. As long as I'm here, I'm going to catch up on a little shopping. I'll meet you back at the house.</quote>
    <quote id="70" type="33">Twinsen, Did you find the healing wizard?</quote>
    <quote id="71" type="33">Well Twinsen , did you find something to treat the Dino-Fly?</quote>
    <quote id="72" type="33">By the way, could you ask Baldino for the car-part he promised me?</quote>
    <quote id="73" type="33">I'm worried sick, Twinsen. These space visitors look pretty spooky, and their niceness seems...I don't know, phony? Did I mention I've seen some of them hiding in garbage cans?</quote>
    <quote id="74" type="1">Here! Here's the part that Zoé needs for your car.</quote>
    <quote id="75" type="1">Here, this is that portable radio I forgot to give you. Sorry about the mixup, but I think you'll agree it was worth waiting for!</quote>
    <quote id="76" type="1">Hello, Twinsen.</quote>
    <quote id="77" type="1">I could've called it an "integrated super dynamo circuitry mechanism" but I decided to go with "portable radio". A little catchier, huh? Incidentally, I'll let you know when the Proto-Pack is ready, it'll let you fly around in complete safety.</quote>
    <quote id="78" type="1">In spite of my powerful telescope, I saw only a couple of flying saucers pass behind the Moon. The Esmers must live on the hidden side.</quote>
    <quote id="79" type="1">Good day, Master, but... is that you Twinsen? You look terrific as a wizard, congratulations.</quote>
    <quote id="80" type="1">I never realized there was an actual School of Magic! I guess I should get out of my shop more often.</quote>
    <quote id="81" type="1">I don't know where they are, Twinsen.</quote>
    <quote id="82" type="1">You need a ticket to board the ferry there, Mr. Twinsen.</quote>
    <quote id="83" type="1">Your ticket's in order, Mr. Twinsen, you may board. Have a nice trip!</quote>
    <quote id="84" type="1">You may board, Master.</quote>
    <quote id="85" type="1">"Do you want to use the telescope for 2 Kashes?"</quote>
    <quote id="86" type="1">Now that the clouds are gone, I can finally enjoy our twin sunshine. You know, I heard there's an oasis in the desert where there's this giant turtle. I'd love to go there...</quote>
    <quote id="87" type="1">A School of Magic? Do you think they might need an assistant?</quote>
    <quote id="88" type="1">No, I fell asleep in the sun, I didn't see any wizard.</quote>
    <quote id="89" type="1">Where do you want to go, Twinsen?</quote>
    <quote id="90" type="1">You know, I wonder if they might have brought her around, actually...What with all the wizards and Esmers hanging around the Hacienda these days...</quote>
    <quote id="91" type="1">I love these visitors from the sky. After the sewers of Citadel Island, I was to repaint the steambath. But, to celebrate their arrival, they bought plenty of drinks!!! Not only for me, but also for the wizards who drop in here.</quote>
    <quote id="92" type="1">Well well! Hello, mister Twinsen!</quote>
    <quote id="93" type="9">Yep!</quote>
    <quote id="94" type="1">For sure. Carousing with a bunch of Esmers...By the way, I wonder where they all went.</quote>
    <quote id="95" type="1">Sorry, but I've forbidden roof access since my colleague from Citadel Island had legal issues with a customer who took a bad dive in the cellar of his bar!</quote>
    <quote id="96" type="1">Well, what've you learned?</quote>
    <quote id="97" type="1">Hello, sir.</quote>
    <quote id="98" type="9">Out, quick!</quote>
    <quote id="99" type="1">For some time now, I've watched 'em pass through my establishment. They all hang around the patio or the steambath. Go take a look.</quote>
    <quote id="100" type="1">These Esmers are pretty chummy, buying drinks for everybody. They even buy them for the wizards. I still keep an eye on the women's steambath, though... The first one who goes in there will have to deal with me!!</quote>
    <quote id="101" type="1">It's depressing. There's nobody left, so obviously business is down. Then the Esmers come and shut my Turkish bath down. I don't get it!</quote>
    <quote id="102" type="1">Unbelievable, the Esmers think they own the place. Their space shuttles come and go through Bald Mountain, it's like they have an anthill underneath!!</quote>
    <quote id="103" type="1">Ah no, I didn't even know there was one on this island!</quote>
    <quote id="104" type="3">There is a top secret exchange program, currently reserved for the wizards. Come discover our science and civilization, and show us your Magic in return. You'll get rich in knowledge and experience. Don't mention it to your School of Magic yet, it's too early ... they would not understand.</quote>
    <quote id="105" type="1">Are you ready to come and spend some time on our planet?</quote>
    <quote id="106" type="1">Greetings, Twinsunian. We are your friends. We come in peace to your planet. We only wish to know you and to share our knowledge with you. @ Have trust in our friendship!</quote>
    <quote id="107" type="1">My master often goes to get sand roses for me. I love munching them. They're so crunchy!</quote>
    <quote id="108" type="1">I don't know Twinsen, I don't live here. I was just imported.</quote>
    <quote id="109" type="1">I saw one go by a while ago. I think he was looking for sand roses.</quote>
    <quote id="110" type="1">Howdy.</quote>
    <quote id="111" type="1">Phew, it's hot but it feels so wonderful!</quote>
    <quote id="112" type="1">A School of Magic? Is that for real? At any rate, it's not here. I come here everyday, I should know.</quote>
    <quote id="113" type="1">I've seen some pass by, quite a few frankly. But they all disappear before I can figure out where they're going.</quote>
    <quote id="114" type="1">Ah thank you. I don't need it anymore, but it was kind of you to bring it back.</quote>
    <quote id="115" type="1">You can borrow this vial, I don't think Master Ker'aooc has much use for it.</quote>
    <quote id="116" type="1">Only the wizards and the initiated know her whereabouts. All I know is that she went into hiding somewhere on the island.</quote>
    <quote id="117" type="1">All I know is that the wizard Ker'aooc has gone on a trip with some of his colleagues. It's the Esmers who invited him!!</quote>
    <quote id="118" type="1">Hello sir.</quote>
    <quote id="119" type="1">Oh, that's you! Hi!</quote>
    <quote id="120" type="1">I am a little worried, you know. Since he left, Wizard Ker'aooc has not sent any sign of life. I don't like what's going on, this is not his habit.</quote>
    <quote id="121" type="1">I hope that the Wizard Ker'aooc will come back soon. I don't feel safe with all these Esmers patrolling the streets.</quote>
    <quote id="122" type="1">I'm sorry that the healer Ker'aooc is away. When he'll be back is anyone's guess. If it's an emergency, try the School of Magic.</quote>
    <quote id="123" type="3">Your reputation has hopped from island to island to reach me, Twinsen. You are the hero of this planet and you must know that the Esmers invite the wizards to come and study their planet of origin. Watch out, there's something fishy.</quote>
    <quote id="124" type="1">It's in the desert. The entrance is in a cemetery to scare off strangers.</quote>
    <quote id="125" type="1">Whoever wants to know has to go and see! Now, you must fulfill your destiny, my young hero.</quote>
    <quote id="126" type="1">Hello to you, Twinsen !</quote>
    <quote id="127" type="1">For some time now, I've been observing inexplicable goings-on here. But it's too soon to be sure.</quote>
    <quote id="128" type="1">Hi Twinsen. If you want to see Moya the turtle, you may find her at the small oasis or on the other side of the harbor. To call her, just ring the bell.</quote>
    <quote id="129" type="1">Sorry, can't help you. The only story about magic that I know is the one about a rabbibunny that got turned into a shell!</quote>
    <quote id="130" type="1">The visitors who come from the sky are weird. I heard them invite some wizards to their planet.</quote>
    <quote id="131" type="1">The aliens have finally shown their true faces. Everybody's terrified of them.</quote>
    <quote id="132" type="1">My friends the moles told me that all the Esmers were gathering underground.</quote>
    <quote id="133" type="1">My dear sir, my goods are only available to fully licensed wizards.</quote>
    <quote id="134" type="1">Ah, you must be Twinsen. Congratulations for passing your examination. If you want a magician's tunic it'll only cost you 50 kashes. We'll throw in a false beard to make you look like an old magician. Interested?</quote>
    <quote id="135" type="1">Now that you are a wizard, I can sell you some orange powder. It costs 10 Kashes, and will recharge you in Magic and Life Points.</quote>
    <quote id="136" type="9">Hey!! You nuts?</quote>
    <quote id="137" type="1">Hello!</quote>
    <quote id="138" type="1">I know where it is, but I don't have the right to tell you.</quote>
    <quote id="139" type="1">I saw Ker'aooc pass by a while back. Told me the Esmers had invited him...someplace or other. Regardless, he was going to the Hacienda.</quote>
    <quote id="140" type="1">Welcome, Twinsen. I'd be honored to have you study with us. But even though you once saved our world, you'll still have to pass the same tests as the other students.</quote>
    <quote id="141" type="1">Do you wish to join our school?</quote>
    <quote id="142" type="1">Inscription fee is 120 Kashes. Are you ready to start right away?</quote>
    <quote id="143" type="1">You'll obtain the power to heal by passing one of the tests of wizardry. But first you have to enroll. Upon graduation, you get an additional level of magic!</quote>
    <quote id="144" type="1">You are now a member of our school.</quote>
    <quote id="145" type="1">To become a wizard, you must first pass 3 tests, in any order you wish.</quote>
    <quote id="146" type="1">You can bring me the result of each test at your leisure, but I will give you your wizard's diploma and your new level of magic only after you succeed in all 3 tests!!</quote>
    <quote id="147" type="1">Once you pass through this door, you will have to be both fast and accurate. Stand in the middle of the room and, with the help of your ball, reverse all the magic symbols.</quote>
    <quote id="148" type="1">Try again, Twinsen.</quote>
    <quote id="149" type="1">Mmm, I love the smell of Garden Balsam. Anyway, in exchange for the flower, here's the Horn of the Blue Triton. It'll make you a Healer.</quote>
    <quote id="150" type="1">You still have two tests to pass.</quote>
    <quote id="151" type="1">You still have one test to pass before you become a wizard.</quote>
    <quote id="152" type="1">Bravo Twinsen, you have earned this blowgun. It provides accurate and rapid shots.</quote>
    <quote id="153" type="3">Bravo Twinsen. You now bear the title of wizard.  @ I don't have any spare wizard's parade tunics left. But there is a peddler on the island. I'll contact him and ask him to give you one. Go find him. Also, let your beard grow.</quote>
    <quote id="154" type="1">Listen to me, I must inform you of some very concerning news. Almost all the wizards of Twinsun have disappeared, and no one knows where they are. They must be found, and you are the only one who can accomplish this noble task. The school is counting on you Twinsen!</quote>
    <quote id="155" type="1">You have to find a peddler who lives on this island. I advised him to provide you with a hat and your wizard's parade tunic.</quote>
    <quote id="156" type="1">Ah, only the wizards are able to read this.</quote>
    <quote id="157" type="1">That's strange that the school does not know... I don't like it. Without wizards, Twinsun is not safe. You must go find them, Twinsen!!</quote>
    <quote id="158" type="1">To practice for your Blowgun Test, simply go through this door at the back of this room. You'll then have a limited time to shoot all the targets.</quote>
    <quote id="159" type="1">For the Test of the Slate, you must first go to the island called the Dome of the Slate, a stone's throw away from Citadel Island.</quote>
    <quote id="160" type="1">The wizards -- did you find any trace of them? The people talk of nothing but these Esmer visitors, but this mysterious disappearance is most grim. Without them, Twinsun's balance and safety are threatened!</quote>
    <quote id="161" type="1">For the Test of the Balsam, you'll have to fetch me a balsam! It's a rare plant which grows in the desert.</quote>
    <quote id="162" type="1">No. Twinsen, only you can save them. But before you confront the Esmers, you will have to reinforce your powers. And only the Ball of Sendell can accomplish this.</quote>
    <quote id="163" type="1">Shortly after FunFrock's disappearance, it was hidden on Citadel Island by the Weather Wizard. He placed it in a cage of ice which he then bound with a powerful spell. According to him, only the power of lightning is capable of freeing the ball.</quote>
    <quote id="164" type="1">There is a giant clam which lives in a marine cave in the cliffs, near Port-Ludo. This creature is host to the pearl of incandescence.</quote>
    <quote id="165" type="1">It is a pearl of incandescence. The Weather Wizard makes use of it for his lightning spell. With it, you could free the Ball of Sendell.</quote>
    <quote id="166" type="1">Have you found the Ball of Sendell? Again, all I know is that it lies on Citadel Island and that only the lightning spell can free it.</quote>
    <quote id="167" type="1">You must go your way, Twinsen. The Esmers begin to be less numerous. It looks like they are gathering by the temple of Bù, you should go take a look.</quote>
    <quote id="168" type="1">Go look at the Temple of Bù. They're discussing an old treasure still buried there.</quote>
    <quote id="169" type="1">Well done Twinsen. By taking care of this place you've enabled new plants to grow. That's smart thinking for all the magicians who come to pick Balsam will benefit.</quote>
    <quote id="170" type="1">Hello.</quote>
    <quote id="171" type="1">This Turkish bath is too hot for me! Sometimes, it's so hot that I have hallucinations... I see wizards everywhere!!!</quote>
    <quote id="172" type="1">Nah, but if they've got something to lower the temperature of this bath, I'm willing to go see them.</quote>
    <quote id="173" type="1">I don't know where it is, but it can't be that far. It's all wizards and Esmers that pass by here.</quote>
    <quote id="174" type="1">Hello</quote>
    <quote id="175" type="1">Actually I saw one earlier. He was carrying suitcases and heading for the Hacienda. These Esmers make my skin break out. I wonder if they really came in peace.</quote>
    <quote id="176" type="1">No, no idea.</quote>
    <quote id="177" type="1">Well, this climate promotes the growth of this coniferous yellow flower. It's in high demand among the wizards and it only grows in rocky, hard to reach areas.</quote>
    <quote id="178" type="1">Oh, hi Twinsen ! If you want to take a little sea trip, jump on my back!!</quote>
    <quote id="179" type="1">Sorry Twinsen, but I don't know where it is.</quote>
    <quote id="180" type="1">Earlier, when I was on the other side of the island, I saw one enter the Hacienda.</quote>
    <quote id="181" type="1">You'll see ...</quote>
    <quote id="182" type="1">Hi!!!</quote>
    <quote id="183" type="1">These...[hic!] These strangers sure are cool...[hic!] They keep buying us drinks. What a great bunch of guys!! [Hic!!] Right, buddy? [Hic!!]</quote>
    <quote id="184" type="1">Me, I... [hic]... er... I have no i... idea. Beuh, buuut you could try [hic!] old Mr. Wiseguy on the terrace... [Burp!] He knows zunbelievable things!!!</quote>
    <quote id="185" type="9">Yup!!</quote>
    <quote id="186" type="1">Greetings, Twinsunian. We are your friends. We come in peace to your planet. We only wish to know you and to share our knowledge with you. @ Have trust in our friendship!</quote>
    <quote id="187" type="1">Greetings, Twinsunian. We are organizing a gathering for the wizards at the hacienda, near Bald Mountain. If you attend, I think you'll be very interested.</quote>
    <quote id="188" type="1">Hello!! Allow to me introduce the Grand Rector of the School of Magic!</quote>
    <quote id="189" type="1">A pleasant stay in our magnificent school of magic!!</quote>
    <quote id="190" type="1">Oh, these dreadfully dull Esmers are simply everywhere. Except here, fortunately. I believe they haven't found the school yet.</quote>
    <quote id="191" type="1">Greetings, Twinsunian. We are your friends. We come in peace to your planet. We only wish to know you and to share our knowledge with you. Have trust in our friendship!</quote>
    <quote id="192" type="1">Greetings, Twinsunian. We are organizing a gathering for the wizards at the hacienda, near Bald Mountain. If you attend, I think you'll be very interested.</quote>
    <quote id="193" type="9">Get out!</quote>
    <quote id="194" type="9">Masher!!!</quote>
    <quote id="195" type="9">Helllppp !!!</quote>
    <quote id="196" type="1">Everybody talks about these guys from outer space, they say they landed on several islands. But that should not interrupt our game.</quote>
    <quote id="197" type="9">You pest!</quote>
    <quote id="198" type="1">I've noticed I keep losing since you helped my little friend over there. Nice move Sherlock!</quote>
    <quote id="199" type="1">I don't know. But it has been a long time since I last saw Ker'aooc the healer.</quote>
    <quote id="200" type="1">I believe it is in the desert, but I never found it!!</quote>
    <quote id="201" type="1">Oh! Hello Mr. Twinsen.</quote>
    <quote id="202" type="9">Cheater!</quote>
    <quote id="203" type="1">I usually play better than that, but my back's killing me. The healer Ker'aooc went out and forgot to leave me some poultice.</quote>
    <quote id="204" type="1">Aah, thank you kiddo! Feels like I got the back of a young Sphero again.</quote>
    <quote id="205" type="1">Well kiddo, all you had to do was treat my back for me to win all the games, golly gee!</quote>
    <quote id="206" type="1">I often go to see the healing wizard for my back... I have a sore back from time to time.</quote>
    <quote id="207" type="1">I'm no spring chicken anymore, you know. And the back, it's important when you bowl!!</quote>
    <quote id="208" type="1">Who that?</quote>
    <quote id="209" type="1">Oh sure! There, right at the corner of the plaza...</quote>
    <quote id="210" type="1">What, the school of bowling, er... of magic? Ah yes, when I was young, it was said to be in the cemetery!</quote>
    <quote id="211" type="1">Hello.</quote>
    <quote id="212" type="1">The wizards? Ah yes, I saw some pass by quite a while back. They were talking about the Hacienda, in the desert.</quote>
    <quote id="213" type="1">I found this car in the desert. Some people think they can get away with anything. By the way, if you want it, it's yours for 50 Kashes.</quote>
    <quote id="214" type="1">Here, I am the best. Nobody can follow me. Try if you want.</quote>
    <quote id="215" type="1">I don't know where it is, but it would be nice if there was a driving school. At least, that would be useful.</quote>
    <quote id="216" type="1">The wizards? Ah no, I don't see many. They are not in the habit of coming here, you know!!</quote>
    <quote id="217" type="9">Lost!!</quote>
    <quote id="218" type="1">If you think you can follow me, go to the starting line.</quote>
    <quote id="219" type="1">You succeeded. Maybe I should go see the healing wizard. He told me that, if I poured a little gallic acid in my engine, I could go faster!!</quote>
    <quote id="220" type="1">I am going to tell you a little secret: a wizard told me that he might have hidden a protective spell on the island across from the Hacienda.</quote>
    <quote id="221" type="1">If you want to do a few laps, you should go get a car!!</quote>
    <quote id="222" type="1">Welcome</quote>
    <quote id="223" type="1">No... although ... I go to the desert to gather the plants with which I cook. But I always avoid crossing a terrifying place, a kind of a forlorn garden... It might be there.</quote>
    <quote id="224" type="1">I wouldn't be surprised if they had disappeared in the ancient Temple of Bù !! My brother-in-law works there and he tells strange tales about disappearances...</quote>
    <quote id="225" type="1">These Esmer visitors are extraordinary. They are supposed to come from the Emerald Moon. Would you believe that??</quote>
    <quote id="226" type="1">Since the Esmers have shown their true faces, people have gone home. Everybody hides and only a few businesses are allowed to open.</quote>
    <quote id="227" type="1">I hope my clientele will come back. It looks like there are less and less Esmers in the streets of Port-Ludo.</quote>
    <quote id="228" type="1">A holomap costs 10 Kashes.</quote>
    <quote id="229" type="1">A flask of gallic costs 50 kashes.</quote>
    <quote id="230" type="1">Stand in front of the article of your choice and do "ACTION".</quote>
    <quote id="231" type="1">Good day sir, welcome to my shop.</quote>
    <quote id="232" type="1">A Nitro-Meca-Penguin costs 4 Kashes.</quote>
    <quote id="233" type="1">For 15 Kashes, you can get recharged in Life points.</quote>
    <quote id="234" type="1">For 15 Kashes, you can get recharged in Magic points.</quote>
    <quote id="235" type="1">Three darts will cost you 4 Kashes.</quote>
    <quote id="236" type="1">I'm unclear on the details, but a customer told me about an old wiseman who presumably knows all the island secrets. I believe he lives near the Hacienda.</quote>
    <quote id="237" type="1">Do you know that you are my first customer since way back when.</quote>
    <quote id="238" type="1">I don't know where they are, sir. Me and the tales of magic, you know...</quote>
    <quote id="239" type="1">These strangers are pretty strange. They have this whole collection of carnival costumes that range from cacti to garbage cans. They seem to enjoy it. I keep seeing them in disguise.</quote>
    <quote id="240" type="1">Hello.</quote>
    <quote id="241" type="1">I can't answer you, sir. I am not from here.</quote>
    <quote id="242" type="9">Bravo!!</quote>
    <quote id="243" type="1">Dumb! I can't remember what I did with the admission tickets and I'm afraid we might be checked!! ...Et er... do you think we can go farther?</quote>
    <quote id="244" type="1">Oh! Er... hello sir.</quote>
    <quote id="245" type="1">I left our tickets to my brother, he's the park warden, you know, Mr. Organized... up there... hmm!...that's it, almost there...</quote>
    <quote id="246" type="1">I don't know, sir.</quote>
    <quote id="247" type="1">Ah no, I didn't see any. On the other hand, quite a few Esmers pass by here.</quote>
    <quote id="248" type="1">Sir!</quote>
    <quote id="249" type="1">If you want to go farther out, you'll have to board a vacant cart. Watch out during the visit, stay on the tracks and don't get off. It's dangerous, and you could easily injure yourself.</quote>
    <quote id="250" type="1">Hello sir.</quote>
    <quote id="251" type="1">Never heard of it.</quote>
    <quote id="252" type="1">Didn't see none. Did see a bunch of Esmers pass by en route to the lowest basement. "To do some repairs," they said.</quote>
    <quote id="253" type="9">Magnificent!</quote>
    <quote id="254" type="1">My son adores tales of magic... he even believes we got in here with our special powers!! as if by a miracle!!</quote>
    <quote id="255" type="1">This temple is absolutely extraordinary. I wonder what we'll see afterwards!?</quote>
    <quote id="256" type="1">Hello.</quote>
    <quote id="257" type="1">I didn't know one existed. If we have time and manage to find it, we'll pay a visit, yes?</quote>
    <quote id="258" type="1">No. Didn't see any.</quote>
    <quote id="259" type="1">I don't know. I always make a detour whenever I take a stroll in the area. Not far from here, there is a dreadful garden on the rocky hillside.</quote>
    <quote id="260" type="1">Ah no, I don't know where they are. In fact, it has been awhile since I saw any.</quote>
    <quote id="261" type="1">Hi.</quote>
    <quote id="262" type="1">I enjoy wandering in the desert. Once, in the Temple of Bù, I found lots of little treasures.</quote>
    <quote id="263" type="3">The access to the lower floors is temporarily prohibited, we can no longer assure the safety of the visitors. The Esmers have volunteered to do the work in the lowest basement. It's not I who will complain!!</quote>
    <quote id="264" type="1">Oh! Hello Mr. Twinsen! What an honor to see you here.</quote>
    <quote id="265" type="1">I don't know, I heard that it is in the desert.</quote>
    <quote id="266" type="1">No idea. Since I'm been here, I have not seen a single one!</quote>
    <quote id="267" type="1">Hey, mister! My daddy, he's smart. He was able to get us in without tickets!</quote>
    <quote id="268" type="9">Yippee!!!!</quote>
    <quote id="269" type="1">I don't like school!!</quote>
    <quote id="270" type="1">Wizards? Those fellows with the funny hats? Nope, I didn't see any!</quote>
    <quote id="271" type="1">A ticket mister? For only 7 Kashes, you can visit all of Temple-Park, including the inside of the Temple of Bù.</quote>
    <quote id="272" type="9">Stop him!</quote>
    <quote id="273" type="1">Now that the temple's under repair, we don't have too many customers. Just Esmers mostly, visiting. They offered to help us.</quote>
    <quote id="274" type="1">It exists? I always thought it was just another desert mirage.</quote>
    <quote id="275" type="1">Sorry, I didn't see any.</quote>
    <quote id="276" type="1">Careful sir, keep off the grass!</quote>
    <quote id="277" type="1">I don't know, sir. Once, a customer told me about it, but he didn't know where it was. That, or I forgot.</quote>
    <quote id="278" type="1">No, sir, can't help you. It's not often we see wizards around here..</quote>
    <quote id="279" type="1">Phew!! With all these gate-crashers, I don't know which way to turn.</quote>
    <quote id="280" type="1">Would you like 3 darts and try some duck shooting? The price is 4 kashes.</quote>
    <quote id="281" type="1">Bravo sir, you won these magnificent balloons!!!</quote>
    <quote id="282" type="1">For 12 Kashes, where do you want to go?</quote>
    <quote id="283" type="1">Welcome to the Inter-islands Ferry, sir.</quote>
    <quote id="284" type="1">Our ferries don't service this island, sir.</quote>
    <quote id="285" type="1">I don't know where it is.</quote>
    <quote id="286" type="1">No, I haven't seen any in quite a while.</quote>
    <quote id="287" type="9">Help!!</quote>
    <quote id="288" type="1">Oof! Thanks Twinsen, that shell was getting on my nerves!!</quote>
    <quote id="289" type="1">Hey Twinsen! It's me, Joe!! I don't feel too good. Couldn't you do something for me?</quote>
    <quote id="290" type="1">It has been two months since I enrolled in this blasted school, and I have not been able to pass a single test!!!</quote>
    <quote id="291" type="1">Ah no!! If I had seen any, I'd have asked them to help me pass at least one test!!!</quote>
    <quote id="292" type="1">I can't, I just can't!!! I heard some alien dudes landed on Twinsun, and I didn't even see them! I tried for days to do that blowgun test!</quote>
    <quote id="293" type="1">I've had it with these studies. I should do something else... I think I am going to try studying extra-zeelichian populations!!!</quote>
  </quotes>
</lbatexts>
