<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1" ?>

<lbatexts>
  <game>1</game>
  <quotes>
    <quote id="1" type="0">Here's your book.</quote>
    <quote id="2" type="0">Good day</quote>
    <quote id="3" type="0">Good day, all this talk about the Legend is strange, don't you think?</quote>
    <quote id="4" type="0">Very strange indeed. I'm just an old fool who would like to grow flowers in the desert, but... I know about this Legend that Dr. FunFrock forbade. I'll tell you what I know if you bring me a sacred book. It is in the Temple of Bù which was buried by a violent sand storm. You can still get in, however, through one of the ventilation shafts still visible just behind me. But be careful: there is danger everywhere!</quote>
    <quote id="5" type="0">" This book is a keeper of knowledge. It allows you to read the rocks and to talk to the animals. "</quote>
    <quote id="6" type="0">To Principal Island.</quote>
    <quote id="7" type="0">I'll leave later on.</quote>
    <quote id="8" type="0">I can get you to where you want to go for only 10 Kashes! Where do you want to go?</quote>
    <quote id="9" type="0">Sorry, Twinsen, you don't have enough Kashes.</quote>
    <quote id="10" type="0">To Citadel Island.</quote>
    <quote id="11" type="0">Thanks for opening the grotto. My name is Joe the Elf. I was locked up here because I wasn't meant to be in the story, there might have been some bugs in the game!</quote>
    <quote id="12" type="0">See you later, and thanks again.</quote>
    <quote id="13" type="0">You're too aggressive! Come back later when you've calmed down.</quote>
    <quote id="14" type="0">Ow, you crazy or what? You don't deserve to be an elf, give me your membership card!</quote>
    <quote id="15" type="0">Where do you want to go?</quote>
    <quote id="16" type="0">Home.</quote>
    <quote id="17" type="0">Proxima island.</quote>
    <quote id="18" type="0">Rebellion island.</quote>
    <quote id="19" type="0">You are the Heir that the prophecy spoke of, Twinsen ! Find your ancestors' legacy, hidden in your home, and pursue your quest. Come back and see me some time.</quote>
    <quote id="20" type="0">Only the Heir could have survived in that Temple! You are the Chosen One that the prophecy spoke of. You are worthy of keeping the Book of Bù, Twinsen. It will allow you to decipher the runes and to speak to the animals. The prophecy that must be accomplished is also revealed in its pages: you must overthrow Dr. FunFrock, the despot who has destroyed the harmony that once existed on this planet. In my dreams, I saw him profaning the Well of Sendell, which caused the immediate destruction of this world. You must go to the Well of Sendell to save us from Dr. FunFrock. I don't know where this well is, but your ancestors must have left instructions for you, somewhere in your home.</quote>
    <quote id="21" type="0">Hello fellow elf.</quote>
    <quote id="22" type="0">Adios! I think I'm going out to discover the world. </quote>
    <quote id="23" type="0">You seem to be nice enough, I dub thee an honorary elf. Here's your card. It entitles you to a present.</quote>
    <quote id="24" type="0">Hello, quetch !</quote>
    <quote id="25" type="0">Good day, horse.</quote>
    <quote id="26" type="0">I know the story of the emerald moon, but that's all.</quote>
    <quote id="27" type="0">Hii, hi ! Bbbrrrff ! Brf !</quote>
    <quote id="28" type="0">I don't know what that could be all about.</quote>
    <quote id="29" type="0">Did you know that there are strange noises coming from that symbol on the rocks?</quote>
    <quote id="30" type="0">You were the one who freed that gnome with the hideous hat? He asked me if there was a princess that needed freeing in the neighborhood, but if you want my opinion, he doesn't have what it takes to be a hero.</quote>
    <quote id="31" type="0">No more gas.</quote>
    <quote id="32" type="0">Then you should go visit the Maritime museum on Proxima island.</quote>
    <quote id="33" type="0">I can't help you, sorry.</quote>
    <quote id="34" type="0">I'm looking for the plans of the Teleportation Center.</quote>
    <quote id="35" type="0">They say that there are treasures hidden in a temple, somewhere in the desert.</quote>
    <quote id="36" type="0">I'm looking for information about LeBorgne the pirate.</quote>
    <quote id="37" type="0">I read some excerpts from the Captain's log, that LeBorgne was ruthless! If you're still interested, the log is for sale at the Old Burg bazaar, on the Principal island.</quote>
    <quote id="38" type="0">I don't know where they are.</quote>
    <quote id="39" type="0">I don't know anything about it, but I think a while ago the library had some books that spoke of it.</quote>
    <quote id="40" type="0">I don't know where they are, but we elves don't need that sort of stuff. We can teleport ourselves magically! Well, I forgot how, but I'm not a good example.</quote>
    <quote id="41" type="0">To the Hamalayi mountains.</quote>
    <quote id="42" type="0">I'll give you my guitar in exchange for the flute that you possess Twinsen, beforehand, though, you will have play it next to the Clear Water Lake in order to obtain the 4th magical symbol.</quote>
    <quote id="43" type="0">You will no longer need the flute, Twinsen. On the other hand, it might allow me to realize an old dream of mine. I'll trade you for this guitar that I found in the middle of a meteor.</quote>
    <quote id="44" type="0">Good day </quote>
  </quotes>
</lbatexts>
