<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1" ?>

<lbatexts>
  <game>1</game>
  <quotes>
    <quote id="1" type="0">" Maritime Museum, rates: @ Children ... 3 Kashes @ Adults ... 5 Kashes. " </quote>
    <quote id="2" type="0">" Welcome to Proxim-City @ (Proxima Island). "</quote>
    <quote id="3" type="0">" Guard post - open 24 hours a day. Do not disturb... "</quote>
    <quote id="4" type="0">" Appropriate attire required! "</quote>
    <quote id="5" type="0">I'm looking for the plans of the Teleportation Center.</quote>
    <quote id="6" type="0">To Principal Island.</quote>
    <quote id="7" type="0">To Citadel Island.</quote>
    <quote id="8" type="0">We'll see about that later.</quote>
    <quote id="9" type="0">For 10 Kashes, where do you want to go, Twinsen ?</quote>
    <quote id="10" type="0">Sorry, you don't have enough Kashes. I've got kids to feed you know!</quote>
    <quote id="11" type="0">Good day, a ticket for the museum costs 5 Kashes. Would you like one?</quote>
    <quote id="12" type="0">Yes, I'll take one.</quote>
    <quote id="13" type="0">No, museums put me to sleep.</quote>
    <quote id="14" type="0">Sorry, but you don't have enough Kashes.</quote>
    <quote id="15" type="0">" Rear starboard propeller of the FunFrock 2. It was lost when the ship was launched from Principal island. The boat ran out of gas three days later, and finally stopped turning around in circles. "</quote>
    <quote id="16" type="0">" Captain LeBorgne's treasure. This chest contains the fruits of a lifetime of dishonesty. It was seized by the IRS, the only predator known to this terrible pirate. "</quote>
    <quote id="17" type="0">" Loan shark. This species of shark belongs to the movie producer family. "</quote>
    <quote id="18" type="0">" Reed Boat or Quffa. Primitive boat made from weaved reeds."</quote>
    <quote id="19" type="0">" Boarding cannon. "</quote>
    <quote id="20" type="0">" Oak barrel. Barrels such as this one were used to serve up the daily rations of rum to the sailors. "</quote>
    <quote id="21" type="0">" Bùian Mermaid. A fine example of the absurdity of ancient superstitions: this statue was found in the middle of a desert. "</quote>
    <quote id="22" type="0">" Lifeboat. Do not pierce, burn, or bring into contact with an incandescent object. "</quote>
    <quote id="23" type="0">" Life candies: would you like 10 hearts for 10 Kashes? "</quote>
    <quote id="24" type="0">Ok, I'll take them.</quote>
    <quote id="25" type="0">No thank you.</quote>
    <quote id="26" type="0">Not enough Kashes !</quote>
    <quote id="27" type="0">Halt. It is forbidden to touch the exhibits.</quote>
    <quote id="28" type="0">Sound the alarm! It's the escapee!</quote>
    <quote id="29" type="0">" Construction work. SLOW DOWN! "</quote>
    <quote id="30" type="0">" I am the Eclipse Stone. The password for the Marked Stone is "BURBS". Which word will free me? "</quote>
    <quote id="31" type="0">" I am the Marked Stone. The password for the Eclipse Stone is "GIZMO". Which word will free me? "</quote>
    <quote id="32" type="0">I don't know.</quote>
    <quote id="33" type="0">" BURBS "</quote>
    <quote id="34" type="0">" GIZMO "</quote>
    <quote id="35" type="0">My brother was arrested and the house is under surveillance: phony red card traffic. Wait a minute, how did you get in here? And who are you?</quote>
    <quote id="36" type="0">My name is Twinsen. I met your brother. He is in jail but is fine for the moment. He told me to mention the word "Amos" to you.</quote>
    <quote id="37" type="0">My name is Twinsen and I am the Heir... @ voila, voila, voila.</quote>
    <quote id="38" type="0">Ah! Ok. Then you might need this.</quote>
    <quote id="39" type="0">I'm really happy for you, Twinsen! But my brother is being held in FunFrock's headquarters. His cell has a window that is right on the street. If you could tell me how he's doing, I will give you a red card in gratitude.</quote>
    <quote id="40" type="0">You've just rediscovered all the objects that are in your inventory!</quote>
    <quote id="41" type="0">" L.B.A. @ Proxim-City sewer service @ Ferry Street "</quote>
    <quote id="42" type="0">I've been trying to sell this hair dryer ever since I was on Principal island! Come on, I know you can use one for 30 Kashes.</quote>
    <quote id="43" type="0">You don't have enough Kashes, see you later.</quote>
    <quote id="44" type="0">I don't have anything else to sell!</quote>
    <quote id="45" type="0">Aah, I see that you too have come to Proxima island. You remember me, I sell hair dryers. Look, I'll sell you one for only 30 Kashes, but only because it's been a slow day.</quote>
    <quote id="46" type="0">Don't know what you're talking about.</quote>
    <quote id="47" type="0">I've been working on a Jet-Pack prototype for days now. It's a small reactor that harnesses onto your back and allows you to fly about. My problem is that my last test flight wreaked a bit of havoc on the garden wall. It is rather difficult to fine tune the motor's power. I need a rheostat like the one you find in a hair dryer. Do you think you can find one of those for me? </quote>
    <quote id="48" type="0">So you found a hair dryer? Great! I'll be with you in a minute, just let me install the rheostat. </quote>
    <quote id="49" type="0">Well it's not a Jet-Pack yet, it's still just a Proto-Pack. I would appreciate it if you could test it out to see how it works. You should be able to fly over the water if you approach it from a gently sloping beach. But don't jump! Will you test it for 10 Kashes?</quote>
    <quote id="50" type="0">How's the Proto-Pack coming along? Keep testing, I have a bunch of calculations to finish up. And be careful when approaching water: you can only fly by coming in from a gently sloping beach.</quote>
    <quote id="51" type="0">" Our heroic clone troops are responding to the rising rebel threat with a series of bombardments. "</quote>
    <quote id="52" type="0">" Skull flag. Pirate emblem belonging to the famous pirate Captain LeBorgne. " </quote>
    <quote id="53" type="0">The museum's alarm system has been activated: we have evacuated the premises for your security. We will open up again later! </quote>
    <quote id="54" type="0">There was a false alarm at the museum. The only way out was through the sewers, but the grate was not moved, so we're reopening the building.</quote>
    <quote id="55" type="0">Good day.</quote>
    <quote id="56" type="0">Sorry, but you don't have enough Kashes.</quote>
    <quote id="57" type="0">Welcome, dear customer, and thank you for honoring my humble establishment with your presence. Move in front of the item that you desire and use the ACTION command.</quote>
    <quote id="58" type="0">Thief! @ @ Leave my money box alone!</quote>
    <quote id="59" type="0">You're too aggressive! Come back when you've calmed down a bit!</quote>
    <quote id="60" type="0">Where do you want to go?</quote>
    <quote id="61" type="0">Citadel Island.</quote>
    <quote id="62" type="0">The White Leaf Desert.</quote>
    <quote id="63" type="0">Rebellion Island. </quote>
    <quote id="64" type="0">Gas for 10 voyages costs 30 Kashes.</quote>
    <quote id="65" type="0">15 hearts of life powder will cost you 30 Kashes.</quote>
    <quote id="66" type="0">10 flasks of magic powder will cost you 30 Kashes.</quote>
    <quote id="67" type="0">One meca-pinguin costs 3 Kashes.</quote>
    <quote id="68" type="0">My brother is in one of the cells that has a window on the street, in FunFrock's headquarters. And you know, if you tell me how he is doing, I'll give you a red card.</quote>
    <quote id="69" type="0">I'm not interested.</quote>
    <quote id="70" type="0">I don't know where they are.</quote>
    <quote id="71" type="0">I don't know what you're talking about.</quote>
    <quote id="72" type="0">Don't touch the alarm button, the grobo is wiring it as we speak. And in any case, it is forbidden to touch it!</quote>
    <quote id="73" type="0">Then go to the museum. And along those lines, don't touch the alarm button on the wall! </quote>
    <quote id="74" type="0">Well you can believe me if you want, but the museum is well protected! I just connected this button to the alarm system: the building is evacuated as soon as it is pressed. @ Only one or two automatic guards will remain. It also sets off a series of sensors under the wooden floor that will sound the alarm as soon as they detect even the slightest weight. You would have to be able to fly to move around in there!</quote>
    <quote id="75" type="0">I think you're going to get hit, if you keep playing with that button!</quote>
    <quote id="76" type="0">I know that they have something about him in the museum. </quote>
    <quote id="77" type="0">That name sounds familiar. Go visit the Maritime museum, I think that they have two objects that belonged to LeBorgne.</quote>
    <quote id="78" type="0">Oh yes, it's great!</quote>
    <quote id="79" type="0">What about my test flights? I'm not paying you to test your shoes!</quote>
    <quote id="80" type="0">I've been working on a Jet-Pack prototype for days now. It's a small reactor that is harnessed on the back and allows its user to fly about. My problem is that my latest flight test wreaked havoc on my Southern wall. So I'd like to borrow the rheostat in your hair dryer to fine tune the power of the motors (from looking at your hairdo, I don't think you really need the dryer, anyway). And if that works, I will have a job offer for you.</quote>
    <quote id="81" type="0">Well, well. It seems that you too have found an authentic secret map of Captain LeBorgne! Do me a favor would you? Give Lanktir, who lives next to the bazaar, back his coffee pot. I'm so ashamed, I should have given it back long ago.</quote>
    <quote id="82" type="0">Go try at the museum.</quote>
    <quote id="83" type="0">Hi!</quote>
    <quote id="84" type="0">I'm looking for information about LeBorgne the pirate.</quote>
    <quote id="85" type="0">No more gas.</quote>
    <quote id="86" type="0">I read some of the Captain's log - that LeBorgne was ruthless! If you're still interested, the log is for sale at the Old Burg bazaar, on Principal Island.</quote>
    <quote id="87" type="0">I don't know where they are.</quote>
    <quote id="88" type="0">I don't know anything about it, but it seems to me that there were some books over at the library that spoke of it.</quote>
    <quote id="89" type="0">" For reasons of security, this sewer grate will open only from inside the Maritime Museum. "</quote>
    <quote id="90" type="0">To the Hamalayi mountains.</quote>
    <quote id="91" type="0">Apparently, there was a burglary. The visits will recommence later!</quote>
    <quote id="92" type="0">Here, this will help you keep your strength up!</quote>
    <quote id="93" type="0">Apparently, there was a burglary. Alas, the thief escaped!</quote>
    <quote id="94" type="0">Never saw a storm like it, @ never!</quote>
    <quote id="95" type="0">Sorry, but I don't know where they are.</quote>
    <quote id="96" type="0">No more fake red cards, too dangerous, I quit. From now on, I am only going to make fake Captain LeBorgne secret maps.</quote>
    <quote id="97" type="0">Ah, it's impossible to open without a red card.</quote>
    <quote id="98" type="0">To the Eclipse Stone.</quote>
    <quote id="99" type="0">To the Marked Stone.</quote>
    <quote id="100" type="0">To Proxim-City.</quote>
    <quote id="101" type="0">So go in front of LeBorgne's chest, which is in the museum, and read the sign!</quote>
    <quote id="102" type="0">Good day</quote>
    <quote id="103" type="0">Sorry, I don't know anything about it.</quote>
    <quote id="104" type="0">Good day. Incredible huh? These objects belonging to LeBorgne that crossed through time; have you read the inscription in front of the chest?</quote>
    <quote id="105" type="0">Good day.</quote>
    <quote id="106" type="0">Don't know.</quote>
    <quote id="107" type="0">Don't know!</quote>
    <quote id="108" type="0">Good day.</quote>
    <quote id="109" type="0">So read the inscriptions, there are objects that belonged to LeBorgne here!</quote>
    <quote id="110" type="0">I cannot help you. </quote>
    <quote id="111" type="0">Someone made a mistake in the address and sent me this object by accident: it's a keypad that opens a door at the "Teleportation Center". This opens a room full of meca-penguins.</quote>
    <quote id="112" type="0">If you give me back my coffee maker, I'll give you a list of certain places where you can find a rare plant and some boxes. And don't ask me where I found this list! </quote>
    <quote id="113" type="0">Good day.</quote>
    <quote id="114" type="0">I can't help you out.</quote>
    <quote id="115" type="0">" Jérôme Baldino. Diverse Gadgets & Inventions. "</quote>
    <quote id="116" type="0">Try at the museum.</quote>
    <quote id="117" type="0">Leave me alone, I have nothing to say to you.</quote>
    <quote id="118" type="0">§</quote>
  </quotes>
</lbatexts>
