<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1" ?>

<lbatexts>
  <game>1</game>
  <quotes>
    <quote id="1" type="0">Twinsen help! I'm not a clone, it's me, the real Zoé.</quote>
    <quote id="2" type="0">You must break the seal so that I can enter the Well of Sendell. None of my machines could drill through this rock, it resists me, just like the Runic Stone. I began digging around the rocky peak, but it will take months for me to reach the center of the planet! You'll see, I will realize the prophecy myself, and I'll take good care of this planet. Break the seal and I'll spare you Twinsen, you and your friend.</quote>
    <quote id="3" type="0">I will at last see Sendell's face. If everything goes as planned, I'll make you my jester when I come back. Ha, ha, ha!</quote>
    <quote id="4" type="0">Before you destroy the cloning factory, I prepared THIS for you!</quote>
    <quote id="5" type="0">At last, you took your time, my love. I'm not escorted by two groboclones, but I promise that it's really me. Go find Sendell and then we'll go home.</quote>
    <quote id="6" type="0">Good day. </quote>
    <quote id="7" type="0">I am Sendell, like all of those you see here, we are all Sendells. We are here to watch over a stellar entity that is in gestation, it will come into existence in a few centuries. As we can only act from the heart of the planet, we implanted a lineage of elected creatures among the species living on the surface. You are the current descendant of this family, and when FunFrock's threat had become too great, it was me that called to you in your dreams. The entity can now finish its gestation because you rid us of FunFrock. It would have died if he had gotten to it, and this world would have imploded, thanks to you it will continue to flourish. Return now to the surface, you can now erase the final traces that he left there.</quote>
    <quote id="8" type="0">Twinsen, NO! We are finished, don't let him reach us!</quote>
    <quote id="9" type="0">Uh ... you might be surprised when you discover the house.</quote>
    <quote id="10" type="0">What are you doing there? The route that connects the 2 islands is classified top secret.</quote>
    <quote id="11" type="0">Can't start this machine without an ignition key!</quote>
    <quote id="12" type="0">Here, little guy, take the ignition key and bring the bulldozer back for me - I'll appreciate it. I don't have time to do it myself.</quote>
    <quote id="13" type="0">This work is not moving along fast!</quote>
  </quotes>
</lbatexts>
