<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1" ?>

<lbatexts>
  <game>1</game>
  <quotes>
    <quote id="1" type="0">Good day.</quote>
    <quote id="2" type="0">You have no business here, this factory is top secret!</quote>
    <quote id="3" type="0">Don't touch those buttons!</quote>
    <quote id="4" type="0">Hey, you, don't touch our kitchen!</quote>
    <quote id="5" type="0">Noble stranger, we will open the Door of the Sacred Carrot for you if you sabotage the mutant factory, from where the monsters that infest this hemisphere emerge. This door leads to the shore, and from there you can access all of this part of the planet.</quote>
    <quote id="6" type="0">The passage that I'm opening for you leads to a port, where the old subway that crossed the Hamalayi used to leave from. </quote>
    <quote id="7" type="0">Hey, you! Don't touch our k... oh, it's you! @ Good work, you have disabled the mutant factory! No more new monsters are being produced. By the way, what is your name, brave stranger?</quote>
    <quote id="8" type="0">No more gas.</quote>
    <quote id="9" type="0">Greetings! Our village is harassed by the mutants. But these monsters are not a result of the climate - they are produced in a nearby factory built by FunFrock.</quote>
    <quote id="10" type="0">This is not really a good time! </quote>
    <quote id="11" type="0">Thanks for your help. And, whatever you do, destroy the eggs if you are going in the factory! If you don't, new monsters will be produced and will come and attack the village.</quote>
    <quote id="12" type="0">I don't know what that could be all about.</quote>
    <quote id="13" type="0">Good day.</quote>
    <quote id="14" type="0">New monsters are still coming to the village: the factory has not been completely disabled!</quote>
    <quote id="15" type="0">And now, brave stranger Twinsen, follow me to the Door of the Sacred Carrot.</quote>
    <quote id="16" type="0">Twinsen</quote>
    <quote id="17" type="0">Thank you for saving this village, brave stranger Twinsen.</quote>
    <quote id="18" type="0">I don't know what that could be all about, brave stranger Twinsen.</quote>
    <quote id="19" type="0">It's so much calmer since you've come, do you really have to leave?</quote>
    <quote id="20" type="0">I'd like so much to help you, Twinsen.</quote>
    <quote id="21" type="0">Help!</quote>
    <quote id="22" type="0">Whew, safe!</quote>
    <quote id="23" type="0">Carrot, open up!</quote>
    <quote id="24" type="0">I'm looking for the plans for the Teleportation Center.</quote>
    <quote id="25" type="0">Did you know that there is a Clear Water lake very near here. It is located close to the Door of the Sacred Carrot and it has a close connection with a prophecy.</quote>
    <quote id="26" type="0">You will have to interrogate traffickers, people that are in this hemisphere in any case. </quote>
    <quote id="27" type="0">Where do you want to go?</quote>
    <quote id="28" type="0">To Tippett island.</quote>
    <quote id="29" type="0">To Fortress island.</quote>
    <quote id="30" type="0">To Brundle island.</quote>
    <quote id="31" type="0">I'm staying here.</quote>
    <quote id="32" type="0">Where do you want do go, Twinsen?</quote>
    <quote id="33" type="0">Ah, it's impossible to open without a blue card.</quote>
    <quote id="34" type="0">To the rabbibunny village.</quote>
    <quote id="35" type="0">To the mutant factory.</quote>
    <quote id="36" type="0">Leave me alone! I've got work to do, and no time to play!</quote>
    <quote id="37" type="0">Use your red card to use the skilift.</quote>
    <quote id="38" type="0">Sorry, I don't know where they are.</quote>
    <quote id="39" type="0">I don't know where they are.</quote>
  </quotes>
</lbatexts>
