<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1" ?>

<lbatexts>
  <game>1</game>
  <quotes>
    <quote id="1" type="0">Good day.</quote>
    <quote id="2" type="0">You must be Twinsen. Like you, we have rebelled against that madman FunFrock - and you saw what's left of the city. @ We don't believe that the Northern hemisphere has become uninhabitable like the propaganda says it has. There may even be some survivors living there who refused to be deported. This is why we have decided to take the road leading to the Okojo pass by force. It leads to the Northern hemisphere. Unfortunately, our leader, Colonel Kroptman, was captured during the attack. We believe that he is still being held in the small fort that guards the pass. Help us free him by raiding the fort. You will be able to get to the Northern hemisphere if you do so. Go back to the hangar, there is a commando waiting for you in the boat.</quote>
    <quote id="3" type="0">Go give your boss FunFrock this message for me, traitor! </quote>
    <quote id="4" type="0">Hi! If I take your flag to be representative of your intentions, I see that you too have chosen Liberty. Lieutenant Grap is down in the trench, go see him - he'll tell you where our leaders are.</quote>
    <quote id="5" type="0">So, young quetch, you've come to help in the fight against FunFrock? As you can see, this city has suffered because of our rebellion. We are constantly bombed, which is why our leaders have set their camp in the center of the island. You can take my buggy to go see them.</quote>
    <quote id="6" type="0">" Welcome to... AAARRGHH !<linebreak /> @  ... glb "</quote>
    <quote id="7" type="0">Where do you want to go?</quote>
    <quote id="8" type="0">To Citadel Island.</quote>
    <quote id="9" type="0">To Principal Island.</quote>
    <quote id="10" type="0">To the White Leaf Desert.</quote>
    <quote id="11" type="0">To Proxima island.</quote>
    <quote id="12" type="0">I'm staying here.</quote>
    <quote id="13" type="0">Go see Grap first if you want to drive. He's a rabbibunny and he's down in the trench.</quote>
    <quote id="14" type="0">Twinsen, you MUST SUCCEED in this mission. That fort is in a strategic position of the utmost importance. Once we've taken it, the two hemispheres can be united once again. </quote>
    <quote id="15" type="0">We're going to help you take the fort: you will guide me, and I'll follow you with my grenades! Whatever you do, wait for me before you change zones and don't forget to neutralize the emitter. We won't talk during the combats and if I bite it, another rebel will come and take my place, he'll wait for you at the landing site.</quote>
    <quote id="16" type="0">I'm looking for the plans of the Teleportation Center.</quote>
    <quote id="17" type="0">You're now one of us, Twinsen.</quote>
    <quote id="18" type="0">Be careful behind the wheel, this isn't a go cart!</quote>
    <quote id="19" type="0">Calm down! Save your strength for the clones.</quote>
    <quote id="20" type="0">Hey, you look familiar! I just came back from an infiltration mission in Proxim-City and I saw your mug on quite a few wanted posters.</quote>
    <quote id="21" type="0">I've heard about an underground city that the clones use as a meeting place. It's in the Northern hemisphere, on Tippet island. You should check it out!</quote>
    <quote id="22" type="0">Ask Grap. He's in the trench, he'll know where to find them.</quote>
    <quote id="23" type="0">The end is near for FunFrock.</quote>
    <quote id="24" type="0">You must wait for your partner when you change zones if you want to make it through this mission.</quote>
    <quote id="25" type="0">Thank you Twinsen, we couldn't have done it without you.</quote>
    <quote id="26" type="0">Try over at Funky-Town. You can buy anything over there!</quote>
    <quote id="27" type="0">No more gas.</quote>
    <quote id="28" type="0">To the Hamalayi mountains.</quote>
    <quote id="29" type="0">To the rebel camp.</quote>
    <quote id="30" type="0">To the harbour.</quote>
    <quote id="31" type="0">I haven't seen them. @ Sorry!</quote>
    <quote id="32" type="0">Good day</quote>
    <quote id="33" type="0">Good day</quote>
    <quote id="34" type="0">Sorry, I don't know where they are.</quote>
  </quotes>
</lbatexts>
