<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1" ?>

<lbatexts>
  <game>1</game>
  <quotes>
    <quote id="1" type="0">Good day.</quote>
    <quote id="2" type="0">You need me to get into the fort. Wait there!</quote>
    <quote id="3" type="0">Come with me, we'll continue in the tank!</quote>
    <quote id="4" type="0">I'll cover you - go free the Colonel.</quote>
    <quote id="5" type="0">Don't jive me, my predecessor was killed in combat! Well, I guess that's life, huh? Shall we go?</quote>
    <quote id="6" type="0">Quick, get me out of here!</quote>
    <quote id="7" type="0">Hey quetch, hell of a job. If you'd like to carry on down the corridor and, try to open the hatch at the end of the hall.</quote>
    <quote id="8" type="0">From this warehouse we send material to the other hemisphere, we use a shuttle that dates back to the old subway lines. I participated in its construction but I've been waiting for a ferry for two years... Two years!!</quote>
    <quote id="9" type="0">Yes, I know, you also want me to start the transporter. Ok, stand in front of it, I'll start it up.</quote>
    <quote id="10" type="0">I don't know what that could be all about.</quote>
    <quote id="11" type="0">I'm with the rebels who are fighting against FunFrock. We are currently trying to cross the Hamalayi mountains. Our leader, Colonel Kroptman, has been taken prisoner. Welcome aboard if you are joining the fight! Go see my friends on Rebellion island. They will let you dock only if you're displaying the proper emblem: a pirate flag with a skull.</quote>
    <quote id="12" type="0">Use the flag: attach it to your boat and you will be able to dock on Rebellion island. You will certainly be able to help us cross the Hamalayi mountains.</quote>
    <quote id="13" type="0">Hang on! Wait for you partner before trying to change zones. If you are having problems reaching the fort, try neutralizing the radar above the bunkers, in the zone where you landed.</quote>
    <quote id="14" type="0">You're a real hero, Twinsen ! Well uh ... I mean, thanks for freeing Colonel Kroptman.</quote>
    <quote id="15" type="0">Thanks to you, we are now in contact with the Northern hemisphere. And I've received some information about that black-market city, Funky-Town. You will surely find some information over there!</quote>
    <quote id="16" type="0">Hang in there Twinsen, your quest is almost over.</quote>
    <quote id="17" type="0">There are still a few clones left, but with Kroptman at the helm of the tank, we'll take the fort.</quote>
    <quote id="18" type="0">Ask the look-out further on down the road, he'll be able to help you.</quote>
    <quote id="19" type="0">No more gas.</quote>
    <quote id="20" type="0">Ah! I don't know where those plans are. You can find information about everything in Funky-Town, but this city will soon be destroyed by FunFrock.</quote>
    <quote id="21" type="0">Hey, get me out of here! Find a key quick!</quote>
    <quote id="22" type="0">I am Raymond-the-Elf, to show my gratitude, I will indicate the location of the Clear Water Lake to you. It is to the North-West, in the Hamalayi mountains (look on your Holomap). If you play the flute there, you will find an important element of the prophecy. And if you have a membership card you can show me, I've something else for you.</quote>
    <quote id="23" type="0">I am Raymond-the-Elf, to show my gratitude, I will indicate the location of the Clear Water Lake to you. It is to the North-West, in the Hamalayi mountains (look on your Holomap). If you play the flute there, you will find an important element of the prophecy. And in a grotto near the temple of Bù, you'll find one of my fellow elves, he'll be able to get you a blue card.</quote>
    <quote id="24" type="0">Hello fellow elf.</quote>
    <quote id="25" type="0">Never seen them, I don't know anything about teleportation.</quote>
    <quote id="26" type="0">Where do you want to go?</quote>
    <quote id="27" type="0">To Principal island.</quote>
    <quote id="28" type="0">To the White Leaf Desert.</quote>
    <quote id="29" type="0">To Proxima island.</quote>
    <quote id="30" type="0">To Rebellion island.</quote>
    <quote id="31" type="0">I'm staying here.</quote>
    <quote id="32" type="0">To Citadel island.</quote>
    <quote id="33" type="0">I'm looking for the plans for the Teleportation Center.</quote>
    <quote id="34" type="0">Hi, you should go see one of my fellow elves who is in the White Leaf Desert. He can give you a blue card.</quote>
    <quote id="35" type="0">What are you doing there? They're letting anyone in here now! I even captured an elf a little while ago. I don't know what to do with him, officially, that doesn't even exist!</quote>
    <quote id="36" type="0">Surrender!</quote>
    <quote id="37" type="0">Do you prefer to die on an empty stomach, or do you want something special for your last meal?</quote>
    <quote id="38" type="0">Too bad!</quote>
    <quote id="39" type="0">Not hungry!</quote>
    <quote id="40" type="0">You have not achieved a sufficient level of power to defeat the red clones. We will wait for your return.</quote>
    <quote id="41" type="0">Sound the alarm! A prisoner is escaping!</quote>
    <quote id="42" type="0">You've just rediscovered all the objects in your inventory!</quote>
    <quote id="43" type="0">I don't know where they are.</quote>
    <quote id="44" type="0">I'm looking for information about LeBorgne the pirate.</quote>
  </quotes>
</lbatexts>
