<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1" ?>

<lbatexts>
  <game>1</game>
  <quotes>
    <quote id="1" type="0">Good day.</quote>
    <quote id="2" type="0">Catch anything?</quote>
    <quote id="3" type="0">I'm trying to find my bracelet...</quote>
    <quote id="4" type="0">Hold on, I've got something!</quote>
    <quote id="5" type="0">I know this hemisphere very well, for 10 Kashes I'll tell you what FunFrock is concocting here.</quote>
    <quote id="6" type="0">Our leaders don't know that we come here, it's the only place where we can put these blasted helmets down. I'm here for business only: I can sell you information about anything. See you later...</quote>
    <quote id="7" type="0">Did you know that there is a means of getting to Fortress island in my basement? I'll let you in there if you improve the quality of the show. The atmosphere is terrible nowadays, the patrons are bummed out.</quote>
    <quote id="8" type="0">That's much better, go on it! But be careful - there are still a few giant crabs. Thanks again!</quote>
    <quote id="9" type="0">With an atmosphere like this, I'm gonna be rich!</quote>
    <quote id="10" type="0">Our group is sort of lacking: we don't have half the material we need, and we're eight hit songs short of an album. I'm begging you: find a guitar for me!</quote>
    <quote id="11" type="0">I must be hallucinating, look, he found the Space Guitar!</quote>
    <quote id="12" type="0">I think we've got a hit here, thanks pal!</quote>
    <quote id="13" type="0">No more gas.</quote>
    <quote id="14" type="0">" L.B.A. @ Funky-Town sewer service "</quote>
    <quote id="15" type="0">" L.B.A. @ Funky-Town sewer service @ Swindler street "</quote>
    <quote id="16" type="0">" L.B.A. @ Funky-Town sewer service @ Dino-Fly street "</quote>
    <quote id="17" type="0">Good day. Let's see, you can talk to me and you're wearing the Medallion of Sendell: you must be the Heir! I've been waiting for you for centuries and I've got a backache so we'll go carefully. The Hamalayi mountains are too high for me but I can lead you through this entire hemisphere, except for Polar island: it is too well guarded by FunFrock. Where do you want to go?</quote>
    <quote id="18" type="0">Where do you want to go Twinsen?</quote>
    <quote id="19" type="0">I don't know where they are.</quote>
    <quote id="20" type="0">Where do you want to go?</quote>
    <quote id="21" type="0">To Brundle island.</quote>
    <quote id="22" type="0">To Fortress island.</quote>
    <quote id="23" type="0">To the Hamalayi mountains.</quote>
    <quote id="24" type="0">I'm staying here.</quote>
    <quote id="25" type="0">Ask one of the helmet-less groboclones, they come here to traffic and listen to music.</quote>
    <quote id="26" type="0">I'm non-violent.</quote>
    <quote id="27" type="0">Ha ha, I was the watchman on the construction site of the Teleportation Center. So for 50 Kashes I can tell you EXACTLY where those plans are.</quote>
    <quote id="28" type="0">Thief, that's too expensive!</quote>
    <quote id="29" type="0">Sold!</quote>
    <quote id="30" type="0">You don't have enough Kashes, my poor little quetch.</quote>
    <quote id="31" type="0">The plans for this center are in FunFrock's personal safe. In his headquarters on Principal island. But to get in you must be able to defeat the Supergros (the nurses equipped with tablet launchers!).</quote>
    <quote id="32" type="0">Hi, nice weather huh?</quote>
    <quote id="33" type="0">I refuse to fight when I'm not on duty.</quote>
    <quote id="34" type="0">So, which one of FunFrock's factories do you want information about?</quote>
    <quote id="35" type="0">I don't givre credit, come back when you're richer!</quote>
    <quote id="36" type="0">The mutant factory.</quote>
    <quote id="37" type="0">FunFrock cleared out the populations from this hemisphere but there are still a few people that resist like here in Funky-Town. He produces mutant insects in his factory at the foot of the Hamalayi mountains to exterminate us. The factory was supposedly sabotaged, but there are still monsters in the sewers: they were produced before the sabotage. In fact, you can jump on the giant crabs!</quote>
    <quote id="38" type="0">The Teleportation Center.</quote>
    <quote id="39" type="0">It is located on Brundle island, from there FunFrock's cohorts control all the planet's teleportations! The entrance is guarded but they will let you in if you act like one of them.</quote>
    <quote id="40" type="0">The Cloning center.</quote>
    <quote id="41" type="0">The center where all the planet's clones are produced is inside FunFrock's Fortress. It's his headquarters when he is in this hemisphere. Be careful because I heard that he is working on some VERY special clones, it's on Fortress island.</quote>
    <quote id="42" type="0">See you later.</quote>
    <quote id="43" type="0">That type of information is too specific, ask one of the helmet-less groboclones that are here instead.</quote>
    <quote id="44" type="0">Your hydroglider is great! But you won't make it to Fortress island or to Polar island with it. They are isolated by the currents, no ship can find them. You need a Dino-Fly to go there.</quote>
    <quote id="45" type="0">Ask the rabbibunny with the sunglasses, he's an informer.</quote>
    <quote id="46" type="0">Good day</quote>
    <quote id="47" type="0">I'm looking for the plans for the Teleportation Center.</quote>
    <quote id="48" type="0">Calm down, I'll only let you in if the audience likes the group. Work it out with the guitarist!</quote>
    <quote id="49" type="0">Ask the rabbibunny with the sunglasses who is at the entrance to Funky-Town, he's an informer.</quote>
    <quote id="50" type="0">Those guys on stage are fabulous! @ But it's too bad that they don't play anything.</quote>
    <quote id="51" type="0">Wow! Never heard anything like that before, they are too much!</quote>
    <quote id="52" type="0">Be quiet, you'd do yourself a favor if you listen to that, it's fabulous!</quote>
    <quote id="53" type="0">I don't know what it is.</quote>
    <quote id="54" type="0">You don't have enough Kashes.</quote>
    <quote id="55" type="0">Good day, if you like an item, move in front of it and use the ACTION command.</quote>
    <quote id="56" type="0">Thief!</quote>
    <quote id="57" type="0">Ouch!</quote>
    <quote id="58" type="0">Gas for 10 voyages costs 40 Kashes.</quote>
    <quote id="59" type="0">15 hearts of life powder costs 20 Kashes.</quote>
    <quote id="60" type="0">10 flasks of magic powder costs 20 Kashes.</quote>
    <quote id="61" type="0">One meca-penguin costs 3 Kashes.</quote>
    <quote id="62" type="0">I don't know where they are.</quote>
    <quote id="63" type="0">Your Kashes!</quote>
    <quote id="64" type="0">Or your life!</quote>
    <quote id="65" type="0">Mercy!</quote>
    <quote id="66" type="0">Mama!</quote>
  </quotes>
</lbatexts>
